Chapter 727: Whiteriver Valley

‘When did it disappear? Why didn’t I notice at all?’ Leylin’s pupils shrank as he watched the now-empty fountain of blood.

Crackling sounded as the fountain disassembled itself at a faster rate. The bricks, rocks, soil, flowers, and grass all came apart into tiny beads that banded together to form a twisted humanoid figure.

This twisted figure constantly drew in parts of the garden and became increasingly solid, until at last it turned into a woman who had a black beach umbrella with her.

“I heard from Owl that you’re looking for me?” The woman had her back to Leylin, dressed in black clothing and using the large area of the umbrella to cover her upper body. Leylin could only see her black dress and crystal shoes, and hear a pleasant rich voice that could subconsciously intoxicate a person.

“Looking for you? Could you be Madam Minaz? Yes, I’d like to know if there are any ways to freely leave Dreamscape!” A layer of black Kemoyin scales emerged on Leylin’s skin, and his pupils even turned amber and vertical. After all, the way she had appeared was rather mysterious. She looked to be a personification of the garden.

After turning into Madam Minaz, the garden had now turned into an empty land, and even the surface of the ground had disappeared.

‘Dreamscape is far too mysterious. If I have no confidence at all, I should definitely not set my foot here…’ Leylin was slightly jittery, loathing the fact that he was in a world with such factors that could not be controlled.

Perhaps it could be said that no Magi really liked Dreamscape. It’s lack of adherence to rules led to most of their methods becoming ineffective. Of course, some would say that this was because the absolute laws governing Dreamscape hadn’t been discovered yet.

One could simplify the analysis of Dreamscape once that law was found, and the Magus who managed to do so would likely get immense benefits.

“Yes. That owl! It’s the best at causing trouble for others!” The woman holding the black umbrella turned.

Leylin took several steps back. The front view of this Madam Minaz was quite surprising. She had a distorted face with no eyes, and a nose and mouth at different locations. Her visage looked like an abstract work of art. Her upper body had numerous lifeless eyes on it that were staring at Leylin.

“Thousand-Eyed Woman! It’s rumoured that a gaze could cause a Magus to fall permanently!” Leylin exclaimed, and a tremendous Kemoyin Emperor phantom appeared behind him.

“You’re afraid? Why?” At this moment, her voice had undergone a huge change. It lost its previous tenderness, becoming robotic and icy, even hiding a hint of contempt. The eyes on her upper body suddenly released a multitude of rays of light.

Light spread into the skies and blanketed the region, making the so-called death rays of Beholders look like child’s play. The powerful radiance seared Leylin’s eyes, forcing him to cover them.

The moment he opened them again, Leylin was stunned. Around him was a dark forest, and the one-eyed Ent from before had long since disappeared. The earth lizard was still moving up and down underneath him.

Belinda’s voice was heard from the other side, “Do whatever you like! Since I’ve already given it to you, it’s yours!”

‘This scene… It’s when I just entered the Dreamscape Forest and commanded the A.I. Chip to analyse this…’ Leylin’s pupils shrank, and he looked at the records of the A.I. Chip.

However, it left Leylin disappointed, even in shock. The Chip’s records were all blank since the moment he’d ordered it to analyse the methods the Alabaster Devilsnakes used to traverse Dreamscape.

‘Why did this happen?’

[Beep! Unpreventable interference encountered. Records are abnormal.] The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice caused Leylin’s expression to go dark.

Immediately after, he saw the newest records.

[Beep! Analysis of ability of Alabaster Devilsnake to traverse Dreamscape has been completed. Dreamscape can be entered at will by consuming a bloodline imprint. Host lacks enough blood at the moment and cannot refine a bloodline imprint.]

‘That’s impossible. Didn’t it say that a large amount of time was needed?’

Leylin’s eyes showed how deeply in thought he was, ‘So everything that happened was real! The ability to enter and exit Dreamscape was not analysed by the A.I. Chip, but given by the Thousand-Eyed Woman, Madam Minaz…’

‘Time…’ Leylin sighed. Even the concept of time had been warped by Dreamscape. Encountering such a scene, he was still terrified even after it ended.

All the dangers he’d encountered previously with dreamforce paled in comparison to the warping of spacetime that occurred.

It probably wasn’t just him. Perhaps even a rank 7 could do nothing against these illogical events in Dreamscape.

‘Dreamforce, the ability to warp time and space… that’s a realm I can’t even make contact with as I am now…’ Leylin sighed.

“What’s wrong? After going through Dreamscape Forest, we’ll reach Whiteriver Valley. Once we pass that we’ll be at the Serpent Plains. That’s a month away from the holy city.” Belinda slowed down and arrived beside Leylin, her eyes full of concern.

“It’s nothing, I was just lost in thought,” Leylin smiled a little and shook his head.

“Though the Dreamscape zone isn’t as mysterious as Dreamscape, the ample dreamforce here is enough for Magi to unknowingly be dragged into illusions, with even more terrifying wretched Dreamscape Creatures here… Of course, for mixed blood Alabaster Devilsnakes like us, this isn’t a large issue… After all, we’ve already made a contract and have the protection of our bloodlines…” Belinda explained.

‘But that wasn’t what happened!’ Leylin cursed inside, but did not speak. After all, things that dealt with warping time and space were too frightening.

Unlike last time, this trip went very smoothly. There was no clown or Ent coming up and stirring trouble, and the Nightmare Creatures seemed to abide by the contract and did not harass them.

The dark red fog slowly dissipated, and the dark forest became more sparse. Occasionally, bits of clear moonlight shone down from above.

*Whoosh!* An unceasing sound of flowing water could be heard, and the earth lizards grew exceptionally excited, darting forward at a greater speed. Not long after, a vast river appeared in front of Leylin. The earth lizards cheered and lay down at the river, their thick barbed tongues extending into the water as they lapped it up.

“The white river, we’ve arrived!” Belinda’s voice showed her admiration, a glint showing in her eyes.

Leylin turned back. The black forest and dark red fog had long since disappeared without a trace. It seemed that without the summoning of Belinda or other descendants of the Alabaster Devilsnake, it would not appear again.

Unlike the previous barren lands, there was now a river valley nearby. Even the temperature and concentration of elemental particles had undergone a drastic change, allowing Leylin to know that the short period of time where they had run at night had allowed them to traverse a huge distance.

‘Using the indeterminacy of Dreamscape’s space and hurrying along a world crack to leave through a node… This is something like teleportation! The person who thought it up was a genius… Either that or a lunatic!’ Fear still lingered in the depths of Leylin’s heart.

From the port at the edges of Hail Continent, they had travelled about halfway through the continent. Were they to have used a teleportation spell formation, even one from ancient times would have consumed a huge amount of resources.

Here, besides the preparations for the summoning Belinda had not done much. Just from how prompt it was, it was several levels ahead of these teleportation spell formations, if one could disregard its limitations and dangers of course.

As the Dreamscape Forest belonged to Dreamscape, only Alabaster Devilsnakes or bloodline creatures that could make contact with Dreamscape could discover or summon it. This in itself was a huge limitation, and what was more troublesome was the dangers near the end of the journey.

Dreamscape was the riskiest of all the worlds Leylin had seen. What he’d witnessed this day probably wasn’t even the strangest thing about it. In the Dreamscape zone, he couldn’t even disregard any attacks from Dreamscape Creatures despite a prior agreement.

Furthermore, in the eyes of the powerful devils, perhaps their attacks were not intentional attacks and were instead like a show of curiosity or intimacy with other beings.

It was a pity that a rank 5 being could do nothing against that ‘curiosity’.

“After the white river we’ll come to the whiteriver shore valley, another settlement for Alabaster Devilsnakes.” Belinda sounded muffled, and looked towards Leylin, “That’s also where my family is.”

“Oh! Are we going there to visit them?” Leylin nodded.

“There’s no need to. We’ll recuperate nearby. Meanwhile, I’m preparing to go there and take care of some matters, so don’t interfere!” A resolute look appeared on her face. This was a realisation through several life and death experiences, giving Leylin a premonition that this would involve blood. Of course, he wasn’t against it.

‘Looks like Belinda and her family have a very unique story.’ Leylin watched Belinda’s back and stroked his chin.

“This is good timing. The A.I. Chip has already analysed the bloodline imprint to traverse Dreamscape. It’s not bad to gather some materials…”

Chapter 731: Killing and Clone

The large snake figure that was even taller than a mountain stood before him, with large energy undulations of rank 5 emitting from it.

This aura caused many of the family members with the blood of the Alabaster Devil to fall, yet Leylin was not the least bit affected.

His expression did not even change, still assessing this huge beast in front of him as if picking and choosing goods.

Evidently, this attitude had led to Kenta’s great wrath.

“Hss!” The Alabaster Devilsnake hissed and pounced forward.

*Rumble!* The surface of the ground shook unceasingly, and the area at the middle caved in, forming a terrifying large pit.

The tremendous snarls and the figure of the white snake streaked across from the pit.

Terrifying explosions sounded continuously. A tremendous white snake figure was sent flying at the end, large droplets of blood sprinkling across the sky.

“Impossible!”

The large snake rolled in the sky and then regained Kenta’s human figure, though there were now numerous tiny wounds all around his body. His clothes had long since become tattered, and his expression showed his disbelief.

“How’s that possible? How can there be someone more powerful than me? I am favoured by the Mistress, a rank 5 of the noble Alabaster Devils!”

*Boom!* Immediately after, a streak of black flashed, and Kenta coughed up blood as he frantically retreated.

“There’s nothing that’s impossible! While a giant rank 5 serpent is powerful, there’s still a huge disparity when compared with the primordial Thousand-Eyed Giant, Golden Titan and the like.”

Leylin’s black figure slowly emerged, a mysterious Multi-Limb Race appearing at his back. The figure was now shimmering with gold and seemed to have solidified, turning into a golden deity statue.

Though it looked very delicate, there seemed to be a primordial giant beast concealed under Leylin’s black cloak. The strength hidden within caused even the Alabaster Devilsnake to look fearful.

“Hand over your blood and soul obediently, and I might even let you die more comfortably.”

As Leylin closed in step by step, Kenta let out a strange shriek and transformed into a streak of white, preparing to abandon his family and escape.

*Pak!* Many dark red chains appeared once more, sealing the whole White River Valley.

“Your strength and speed are all lacking! Even your manipulation of dreamforce can’t measure up to me.”

Leylin stated the truth calmly while ambling over.

“No!” Kenta kept falling back, almost pressing his body on the chain walls.

Such a ridiculous pose filled Belinda with pleasure and eased her desire for revenge, but she then found this pitiful.

“Mighty Mistress, I am willing to give up everything that I am. Please release a clone and protect your descendant!”

At his wit’s end, Kenta’s expression suddenly flashed with ruthlessness and began an offering spell formation.

Silver rays of light flashed, and immediately after, blood and flesh splattered everywhere. An arm that was still dripping blood fell onto the spell formation.

“The offering shall be the flesh and blood of your child!”

*Rumble!* Crimson flames flashed, and the attention of a conscient in the void descended on the area.

Under the red flames, Kenta’s arm was melted till it turned into a blood-red mask, the tremendous conscient making use of this item and descending.

“Oh Mistress, please protect your descendant!” Watching the mask take shape, Kenta might look pale and had an arm on the shoulder with a gaping wound, but his eyes were filled with elation.

“Begin the experiment!”

In front of him, Leylin merely muttered something.

“Chirp chirp…* Grey rays of light flew from his chest. Within which was a grey feather that was like an illusion, bringing with it the power of chaos.

The grey luster spread in the surroundings, forming an overcast sky.

“While the Feather of Chaos might be able to conceal and have the power of misleading others, how effective would it be after the Snake Dowager’s clone is summoned and descends? That’s worth investigating!”

Leylin’s eyes glinted with intelligence. While the Nefarious Filthbird had already told him this, Leylin preferred to determine this for himself.

If he found there was an issue here, he wouldn’t need to head to his death in the holy city.

“A.I. Chip! Record the following scene carefully. Remember to collect data!” Leylin commanded inside.

[Beep! Mission established. Beginning scanning of surroundings, recording data!]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned.

The crimson mask opened its eyes, revealing a pair of bewitching pupils. Just meeting the gaze caused the bloodline force in Leylin’s body to begin rebelling.

“The clone of the Snake Dowager!” Leylin muttered to himself.

“Mighty Mistress, it is he who futilely tried to kill your descendant and even tried to refine us into beast spirits. Such evil behaviour must be punished!”

Kenta roared, while the conscient in the crimson mask stared at Leylin silently.

“We finally meet, Snake Dowager!” Through his truesoul, Leylin’s voice was transmitted to the mask in the offering spell formation.

“Emperor of the Kemoyins, you dare appear before me?”

The eyes in the mask showed doubt followed by ire, a great voice sounding in Leylin’s mind, “The power of chaos! You’ve sided with the Nefarious Filthbird and sealed off this region?”

Eyes swivelling, they rested on the gray feather in the air.

“Let’s just say this is a temporary cooperation.” Leylin’s expression showed his sincerity as he bowed towards the clone of the Snake Dowager and greeted her carefully, “Well then, mighty Mistress, is there a possibility of us settling this?”

“If you take the initiative and abandon your Kemoyin Serpent bloodline and let me seal you myself!”

The clone went silent for a while and then answered coldly, as if this was the furthest she was willing to go, while Leylin’s pupils showed his hostility in answer.

Sealing his emperor bloodline meant there was no chance of advancing forever, and his Warlock rank would fall to 4.

That was not something he could bear to let happen.

“Then… This discussion will come to naught? As expected,” Leylin sighed and manipulated the feather of chaos in his hands.

A crystal with the power of chaos from before appeared in his hands, burning up fiercely.

Great amounts of the power of chaos, mixed with Leylin’s own strength, swallowing up the offering spell formation like a tsunami.

*Whistles* Crimson rays emanated from the mask and quickly showed signs of being unable to endure the pressure, and was then drowned out by large amounts of gray power of chaos.

“How- How’s that possible? Kenta watched the scene, stunned, feeling like all the faith he had had crumbled.

Leylin and the Snake Dowager’s clone had chosen to communicate through the soul, which was why these outsiders could not understand what had just happened.

All they saw was that the black-cloaked being, Leylin, and the Snake Dowager’s clone in the mask had gazed at each for an instant and, immediately after, the clone had been swallowed by the grey strength.

The Snake Dowager was a mighty dignitary for them, and was everything to all bloodlines. How could it be extinguished so easily?

The shock rendered them speechless, and Kenta lost all will to resist.

[Beep! Recorded all data. Confirmed that no information has been leaked.]

The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice sounded, allowing Leylin to heave a sigh of relief.

He had used the power of chaos to seal off the area, so that the clone had no way of returning, and even all information would not be transmitted back.

If not, even if he were to dispose of the clone, he would immediately be found by the Snake Dowager herself.

Thankfully, with the help of the Nefarious Filthbird and its strength being proficiency in misleading, it had even temporarily cut off all connections between the clone and the Snake Dowager.

“The reason the clone had lost was not that it had lost to the Nefarious Filthbird, but because it was caught by surprise, as well as a boost from me…”

Leylin clearly understood the situation and would not be proud that he had been able to destroy an energy clone.

The loss of a clone was, to the Snake Dowager, like a human losing a strand of hair. It was not worth even mentioning.

However, this was a good start. At the very least, Leylin was certain that with help from the Feather of Chaos, he could conceal himself completely and sneak into the holy city without trouble.

“By concealing myself with the law of chaos and help from the A.I. Chip. I’ll be able to hide myself unless I meet with the main body.”

Leylin completely sighed in relief, gaining more confidence in his plans.

“How can the Mistress of all snakes, a dignitary, be defeated and die so easily? How can that be?”

He headed over to Kenta. This guy was now not in his right mind. For bloodline holders, the Snake Dowager was everything to them, and they could not accept this fact.

“Once he regains his wits, he might begin to harbour doubt towards her. I’ve planted the seed, allowing them to understand that she’s merely a powerful existence. That seed will then sprout and grow till he begins to seek to surpass his limits and obtain more power… With that tiny possibility of one in a million, that could awaken the emperor bloodline of the Alabaster Devilsnakes and allow him to become a rank 6… Next, he’ll be like me and try to break away from the restraints of the Snake Dowager, or be sealed with the Curse Mark of Ten Thousand Snakes and have his bloodline absorbed till his death!”

The A.I. Chip analysed, and a large number of possibilities in the future appeared.

This was not the power of destiny, but precise estimations based on a massive amount of analysis and behaviours of individuals.

Though its rate of having inaccuracies was quite high, Leylin was confident that someday, the A.I. Chip could be like a god of the future, simulating everything that had happened and could happen in a world.

“If it reaches that point, I would probably have reached rank 9 by then…”

Leylin sighed, “It’s a pity, but you won’t get that opportunity!”

Dark red blades of light slashed, and Kenta’s head fell to the ground.

Chapter 732: Serpentes Plains

After death, Kenta’s corpse swelled and regained its form of a giant snake that was tens of thousands of metres long.

A flicker of a truesoul abruptly emerged, as if about to accept guidance into the cosmic world and turn into a floating island for all eternity.

“Trying to leave?”

Leylin sneered, terrifying power sealing the surroundings. Dark red chains trapped the truesoul and was emptied into the black crystal ball in Leylin’s hands.

“The soul of a rank 5 is the main ingredient for a rank 5 beast spirit!” Leylin muttered to himself, keeping the crystal ball properly.

“The materials for the dream imprint have been gathered!”

Leylin came before the gigantic carcass of the Alabaster Devil. After having much of its blood extracted, the body looked like it had shrunken, but was still tremendous.

“Return!” With a flash of spatial undulations, the large snake carcass disappeared without a trace. This was the body of a rank 5 giant snake, and even without blood, it still had a very high value.

“Next is all of you!”

Leylin surveyed his surroundings. The nobility of the Alabaster Devils who saw that Leylin had killed their family leader without any trouble and they themselves affected by the Intoxicated Serpent Flowers, they were now completely in despair.

“Their bloodline force is too varied. What a disappointment.”

Leylin grabbed forward, and crimson blades of light appeared, decapitating the giant Alabaster Snakes that had been lying on the ground. Leylin gathered the materials and only left behind Belinda and the rest of the mixed bloods.

Leylin set up a humongous, grey offering spell formation where he placed the rest of the materials that he did not need.

*Chirp chirp!*

The figure of a giant grey bird appeared, large amounts of grey flames absorbing these offerings.

“You did well! Not only did you kill one of the clones of the Snake Dowager, you even sacrificed the descendants of the Snake Dowager. I am very satisfied!”

Large amounts of the power of chaos descended. If Leylin was willing, he could raise his offerer ranking up to rank 5, but Leylin did not want to do so.

After rank 4, he would need to place the dignitary’s markings on his own body, which was completely unacceptable for Leylin.

Hence, he chose to gather all this power and turn them into crystals to be stored.

Leylin then charged into the mansion, gathering all the treasures and documents before leaving in satisfaction.

……

“It’s over? So that powerful person is a follower of the Nefarious Filthbird! The offerer rank should be at or above rank 5…”

A long while after Leylin left, Belinda struggled to get up and gazed at the White River Valley that had turned into a pile of ruins.

Only a few mixed bloods survived. Due to her traps and the Intoxicated Serpent Flowers, many had lost most of their strength and could be killed easily.

Noticing Belinda looking over, these people immediately gazed at her imploringly.

“Hehe… family!”

Belinda shook her head. While she had already completed her revenge, it still felt like something was missing.

Elated, she was just about to leave when, at the entrance to the valley, she saw two people that left her in shock.

“Why did you come here? Are you trying to create trouble?”

“Sister!” Sophia yelled and threw herself into Belinda’s arms.

“Brother Nick and I were so worried for you! Sister… boohoo…” Sophia’s eyes went red, and while Belinda consoled Sophia, she glared at Leylin venomously.

“Hehe…” Seeing the sisters embracing each other, Leylin merely laughed and rubbed his nose.

He had already retrieved the shadow clone secretly. With his strength, he wouldn’t find any trouble hiding from a bunch of rank 4 or 5s, much less a little lass.

“So? Is everything settled?”

“Everything’s settled!” Belinda turned and gazed at the White River Valley that was now in a very sorry state, patting Sophia’s head, “Let’s go and never return…”

“Mm, alright!” Sophia answered, looking excited. It seemed that she did not have many happy memories here.

……

On the plains that were moving up and down occasionally, gigantic snake paths could be seen, as well as moulted skin and scales.

The round moon in the sky emanated a purple luster and looked especially evil.

An orange-yellow bonfire flickered on the plains with a warm luster, with several simple tents nearby.

“There are descendants of the Mistress on the Serpentes Plains, as well as many mixed bloods. We need to be careful and try our best to be as far as we can from these snake paths…”

Belinda gazed at Leylin meaningfully, “Also, try your best not to attack. These large snakes have parentages that can be traced back to various large families…”

Amongst the descendants of the Snake Dowager, even in the family of the Alabaster Devilsnakes, there were many branches. The top were of course the tens of pure-blood families, where practically every member was a pure blood.

Belinda’s family was a mere distant branch with a bloodline that was not very pure. In the whole family, only her father was a pure blood, and his lifelong wish was to refine the family’s bloodline till it was pure. He did not mind committing sins for this reason, which had resulted in much suffering during Belinda’s childhood years.

Of course, all of this was already over. Belinda was now just warning them.

“Alright!” Leylin smiled tenderly, passing over the grilled meat with sizzling oil that was emitting steam.

“Thank you…” Belinda extended her arm and took it, and then passed the food to Sophia. He watched her tear it into pieces carefully, smiling so much that his eyes were like crescents and traces of gentleness could be seen on his expression.

“Did you notice anything?”

Leylin had a varying opinion, “Yes! Even if I get Sophia to be an alibi, the timing at which I appeared both times is too coincidental. Anyone would suspect that. Of course, that’s merely a suspicion…”

Belinda was no fool. At most, she had guessed that Leylin had hidden his true strength as he was a follower of the Filthbird, but would definitely not connect him with the fugitive Magus.

“Besides, the few times I acted were all for her sake. Even if she discovers anything, she won’t leak news of it…”

Leylin was confident in this. He could tell Belinda’s nature, and her reliance on those of her own race was so much so that it was almost abnormal.

This time, especially, she had passed her sister to him. That already indicated that she regarded her as someone close to her.

In this situation, the possibility of her betraying Leylin was low. Furthermore, she didn’t know Leylin’s true identity.

“But I still need to guard myself against this situation!” Leylin rubbed his chin. He had yet to retrieve the stardust bugs he had left on her.

Whether it was on the Serpentes Plains or the holy city, he needed a guide. Take for instance the traversing. Without her providing the Dream Forest, Leylin would probably still be hastening along along the coast, and it would take about half a year to even reach the Serpentes Plains.

For Leylin, who was tight on time, this was very useful.

“You guys can eat first. I’ll go get some rest!” Gobbling up his food, Leylin elegantly bade the sisters farewell and entered his tent.

On the surface, he merely lay on the soft mat and closed his eyes to rest. Inside, however, he was conversing with the A.I. Chip.

“A.I. Chip, have you reorganised all the materials gathered yet?”

Leylin asked. These were naturally items gathered from Belinda’s family. After killing the leader, Leylin had charged into their mansion and plundered it, taking not just treasures and resources, but also all sorts of books.

This information was then passed on to the A.I. Chip to tidy up.

If Belinda were to find out that the thief who had robbed from her family was now flipping through her family’s collection unabashedly, he wondered what her expression would be like.

She had made some guesses in the past before, and was even subconsciously denying this thought.

[Beep! Reorganisation complete. Calculated to be 34 printed resources, 13 with beast skin, 142 with content stored with spiritual force. Conversion to stats completed.]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned.

[Others have been categorized. Related to strength systems: 16. Related to geography: 24. Related to materials: 9. Others have been deemed to be general or miscallaneous information.]

With the A.I. Chip’s abilities, it could quickly scan and categorise the information and form a complete library for Leylin to browse through.

“Mm! Show me information regarding rank 5 beast spirit masters, especially the part about the spell formation to seal beast spirits!”

Leylin commanded.

[Preparation of related information has been completed. Transmitting to Host’s memories.] Along with the A.I. Chip’s voice, Leylin felt there was another portion of content in his memory that was related to the training of higher-ranked beast spirit masters. It felt very familiar to him, as if he had recorded everything painstakingly himself.

“When it comes to training, rank 5 beast spirit masters need to have a good truesoul as a base. One must completely destroy the remaining conscience that remains in the rank 5 beast spirit and use a rank 5 soul sealing spell formation. The boosts and support from using beast spirits will also be on a higher level.”

Leylin carefully pondered over the differences between a rank 5 beast spirit master and one weaker. Power at rank 5 and above was academic knowledge that was tightly sealed. In the Elias port, Leylin had only gathered information up to a rank 4 beast spirit master. Anything above that was strictly against the rules.

However, Belinda’s family was Alabaster Devil family and had a long history and even a rank 5. The content on this was therefore very detailed and thorough.

“I have the theory and knowledge, and the beast spirit is also in my possession. What’s left is to do it…”

Chapter 737: Beast Spirit Seal

“But before that, I should finish doing everything else.” A crystal ball emerged in Leylin’s hands, with a red-eyed little snake, with scales as pure white as jade, wriggling around within.

Bound within the ball was Belinda’s father, a rank 5 pure-blooded Alabaster Devil. This was the beast spirit of Kenta! If Belinda were to find out, things might get troublesome, but Leylin didn’t really care about her anymore.

Besides, Leylin was very confident in his concealing techniques.

Now, the hatred and obstinate look in the beast spirit’s eyes had disappeared, and all that was left was bewilderment.

Leylin was very satisfied upon seeing this.

[Beep! Scan of target completed. All hostility in its subconscious has been removed.]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip prompted in a robotic tone.

“Good! My hard work for almost a whole month hasn’t been in vain! I’ve finally tamed him.”

Leylin pressed his fingers against the crystal, allowing the little white snake to break free of its bindings. It flit between his fingers, and even seemed to have a sense of dependence on him. A month ago, that would have been unthinkable.

“No matter how poor my spirit sealing spell formation is, it seems that there’s a chance of success over 50%!”

Leylin’s lips quirked in a smile, “Just as well. I’ll seal him completely tonight!”

Leylin was very attracted to the Purgatory World’s strength systems. In this period of time, he had almost completely figured out and understood the strength systems here.

In Purgatory World, besides the innate abilities of the various races, these two strength systems were the most widespread: The path of offerings and the path of beast spirits!

The path of offerings entirely depended on the dignitary. If you gained the dignitary’s favour, you would attain more power and reach a higher Sacrificer rank even if you weren’t as devout, or even if the offerings were lacking. However, the price was having your body completely branded by the power of the dignitary, or even breaking off all possibilities of entering rank 7, the realm of laws. Of course, for devout followers, this method of ‘existing together with one’s god’ might perhaps satisfy their thirst and desire even more.

The path of beast spirits was more primal. This path depended on hunting large beasts and refining them into beast spirits, and then sealing them to be ordered around in combat.

Though it sounded simple, every time they sealed a beast spirit there was a huge challenge to a beast spirit master’s own soul, in terms of its cultivation and strength. If the seal failed, there were far too many instances in Purgatory World of the beast spirit devouring the master instead.

The higher-ranked the beast spirit, the more terrifying their resistance was. Hatred that retained from the soul were extremely dangerous for all beast spirit masters.

Of course, once a beast spirit of a certain rank had been successfully sealed, the beast spirit master would naturally rise to that rank.

After sealing, the beast spirit master could not only order the beast spirit to fight, one could also enjoy the many benefits to the soul from the beast spirit.

For this reason, there were so many beast spirit masters who did not fear death and pursued high-ranked beast spirits and did their best to seal them, though failure was very common.

While Leylin had a deep understanding of the path of beast spirits, beast spirits were very difficult to obtain. He only had a Gudrick beast spirit that was rank 3 and yet to mature. Hence, his beast spirit master ranking was only 3!

That was fine though. At the White River Valley, Leylin had massacred Belinda’s family and extracted the soul of her father, refining him into a beast spirit.

A rank 5 Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit was very rare even in the whole Purgatory World.

Even on the Serpentes Plains, there weren’t many rank 5 giant snakes. Leylin hadn’t seen any, and most of them travelled around in groups. If it were to move, the whole race would move along with it.

In Leylin’s eyes, these giant snakes were less outstanding compared to the Alabaster Devilsnakes.

“Whether as a bloodline imprint or as a cover, this beast spirit will be the most helpful to me!”

Leylin observed the little snake in his hands. The snake even flicked its scarlet tongue, constantly licking at his fingertips.

He had gathered much of the bloodline of the Alabaster Devilsnake and even attempted at creating bloodline imprints, giving him the key to entering the Dreamscape at will.

If he had the beast spirit of the Alabaster Devilsnake as well, whether a bloodline imprint was made, used, or if he were to explore Dreamscape, he would have great advantages. Leylin had always liked preparing things well, and if his plan were to fail, then dreamforce would be his trump card. Hence, Leylin’s research had been focused on exploring Dreamscape.

Besides this, for Leylin who had snuck into holy city, having an Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit was another insurance for him.

While he had the bloodline traces on the Mask of the Dreamless, as well as the cover from the Nefarious Filthbird’s power of chaos, Leylin didn’t mind adding another layer of security.

“What comprises of a life form is both the bloodline and the soul.’

Leylin mumbled, “With replenishment from her family, the consumption to the Mask of the Dreamless’ bloodline has been made up for. With this beast spirit, I can use it in place of my soul at crucial moments. Even if the Snake Dowager were to scan over a large area, I’m sure I can hide from her…”

Using the aura of a beast spirit as a substitute for his own might be just a dream to the inhabitants of Purgatory World, but this was no issue for Leylin. What was more important was that the main material for the beast spirit was a soul. Hence, there was nothing that would not merge. With the A.I. Chip, Leylin was very confident.

“Hence, the beast spirit of the Alabaster Devilsnake is my best choice!”

Leylin’s eyes shone with determination, “Furthermore, after becoming a rank 5 beast spirit master, my truesoul will probably reach full-moon.”

The increase of strength in any amount was a chance hard to come by.

[Beep! Beginning seal of beast spirit. Setting up rank 5 soul sealing spell formation.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded. Meanwhile, an intricate soul spell formation diagram was shown.

Leylin was only a rank 3 beast spirit master now, and if inhabitants of Purgatory World were to hear that he wanted to seal a rank 5 beast spirit, they would say he was merely dreaming.

Even rank 4 beast spirit masters did not dare do this even after obtaining a rank 5 beast spirit. At the very least, they would have the confidence to attempt this after sealing more rank 4 beast spirits and nourishing their soul for centuries.

A rank 3 beast spirit master? The body would probably not be able to bear the powerful undulations of a rank 5 beast spirit and just crumble, with there being a chance of exploding into bloody mist!

But Leylin was no ordinary person. His truesoul was at half-moon, and his body, which had been strengthened by bloodline force and various techniques overtime gave him this confidence.

“Compared to rank 5 beast spirit masters of Purgatory World, rank 5 Magi souls have already condensed their truesoul. The density and quality is incomparable. The power of their soul, what the soul can withstand and precision in controlling it exceeds that of a rank 5 beast spirit master by several levels! Besides, my body and vitality has already gone through bloodline force and Multilimb Strength and received boosts from body tempering spell formations. A mere rank 5 beast spirit…”

Beast spirit masters of Purgatory World could seal beast spirits as long as they were lucky enough. Their bodies would then be nourished by the beast spirit, which meant just lying around would allow them to increase their strength. Once they hit the limits of the beast spirit, they could just seal a new spirit. This turned into a cycle.

Compared to Magi who had to be cautious at all times, study continuously and advance, their method might seem comfortable and easy, but it lacked the most important experience and knowledge!

At the soul level, Magi of the Magus World could definitely look down on these beast spirit masters. If they obtained suitable beast spirits, the speed at which Magi would adapt to and seal the beast spirit would be faster than beast spirit masters.

“The reason the path of beast spirits did not prosper in the Magus World is related to the different laws of the world, and might have something to do with the extinction of species in the central continent. After all, which world has as many beast spirit resources as in Purgatory World?”

Making sense of his thoughts, Leylin looked solemn.

The path of beast spirits was worthy of Magi looking into. At the very least, the soul sealing spell formation, the beast spirit turning on the owner, coordination between the soul and the flesh were all huge inspirations for Leylin to conduct experiments.

While he focused on the path of bloodline Warlocks, Leylin would not look down on other strength systems. No matter how insignificant it might seem, anything that was passed down was definitely worthy of looking into.

Only by constantly studying would the path of Magi be filled with fervour and life.

[Starting atomic microscope. Helping with carving of rank 5 soul sealing spell formation.]

Along with the A.I. Chip’s voice, an intricate spell formation began to appear at the back of Leylin’s hand.

At the heart of the profound spell formation was a twisted pentagon diagram and many soul runes filled with mystery and savagery. These were key to subduing beast spirits, and even led to beast spirits turning on the beast spirit master.

Even the A.I. Chip was unable to analyse some of the runes and could only use them as much as possible.

The rays emitted from the spell formation enveloped the Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit, and the little snake began to float.

“Hss…” While already tamed, the little white snake showed signs of resistance.

However, the familiar soul force from Leylin’s eyes felt very familiar to the little white snake, and it now had an internal conflict.

Gradually, the bundle of light around the little white snake came closer to the spell formation on the back of Leylin’s hand.

“Now’s the time. Seal!”

Along with Leylin’s cry, the soul sealing spell formation suddenly emitted rays of light that absorbed that bundle of light.

“Next up… is a contest between souls!”

Chapter 738: Fullmoon Truesoul

Leylin closed his eyes.

Now, in his gloomy soul space, his half-moon truesoul showed itself. Opposite it was the little white snake from before.

“Hss…”

This contest had already happened many times in the past month. Hence, after sensing the familiar soul aura that belonged to Leylin’s truesoul, the Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit immediately became fearful.

“Obey or die!”

Leylin did not give the beast spirit much time and immediately warned, boundless half-moon truesoul strength descending and pressing the little white snake to the ground.

“Hss…” The snake flicked its tongue and chose to obey. A flash of cold, clear moonlight entered through its eyes, controlling it completely.

Gradually, the eyes became dazed, and a half moon appeared…

[Beep! Host has successfully sealed rank 5 Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit. Promoted to rank 5 beast spirit master!]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded. Everything had gone extremely smoothly with how everything had been set up.

A beast spirit above rank 4 usually had some malicious intent or memory fragments from the body. For a soul like this that had lost all its will and was defiant, beast spirit masters found this very troublesome.

Even if the beast spirit was successfully tamed eventually, a part of the beast spirit’s soul source would be consumed from battle and cause it to weaken.

However, Leylin had long since tamed it, which allowed the sealing process to go smoothly.

The soul sealing spell formation had already been optimised by the A.I. Chip, which raised the compatibility between the beast spirit master and the beast spirit to the highest. Hence, not only had Leylin successfully become a rank 5 beast spirit master, but he also could display the full strength of the original Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit!

“But the process of sealing a beast spirit has already been deduced by the A.I. Chip to have a success rate of 90%. The process of the boost is the most important…”

At this thought, Leylin looked more grim than before, and placed his focus deep in his sea of consciousness amongst the point mass nebulae.

[Beep! Boost of rank 5 beast spirit beginning.]

Along with the A.I. Chip’s voice, a fantastic change happened in his sea of consciousness.

On the back of Leylin’s hand, a vivid tattoo of a little white snake appeared and roved around. A stream of pure soul force spiralled as it was absorbed and devoured into the point mass vortex in his sea of consciousness. The refining process was repeated and then abruptly poured into the point mass.

The point mass of a Radiant Moon Magus had already formed, the two innate runes on it were extremely dazzling.

Within the point mass, Leylin’s half-moon truesoul was cheering excitedly. The point mass, that was like a full moon that was already half filled with light, suddenly expanded, charging towards filling the other half.

After entering the realm of a rank 5 Radiant Moon, a Magus’ truesoul was like a full moon, signifying fullness.

The strength of soul force would show on the surface of the round moon. From the crescent to the half-moon, and then to the most powerful full moon; these would show the various phases of rank 5 Magi as they trained.

Leylin’s truesoul had only been at half moon, but with the help of the Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit, he began to make a burst for the full moon!

[Beep! Rank 5 beast spirit boost has begun. Host’s soul force is being enhanced. All stats are changing…]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded at this moment.

[Beep! Detected that Host’s soul force has reached threshold. Beginning upgrade. Now at 210.] [Beep! Host has absorbed a large amount of purified soul origin. Soul force upgrading. Now at 220.]

The A.I. Chip’s prompts kept refreshing, and accompanied by its robotic intones, Leylin’s half-moon truesoul within his point mass filled up, beginning to transform into a full moon rank.

230! 240! 250! With the boost from the rank 5 beast spirit, the rate of progress of his truesoul could be said to be terrifying.

His truesoul that was already full began to expand in size, the luster from a full moon practically filling the whole truesoul.

At this very moment, something strange happened!

“Hss!” At Leylin’s forehead, a black snake rune that was bound by thorny chains appeared, with a seal from the concentrated power of chaos circling it.

[Beep! Detected disorder from the Curse Mark of Ten Thousand Snakes. Determined to be triggered by sudden increase of soul force. Now flaring up.]

With the A.I. Chip’s voice, Leylin felt that there seemed to be a terrifying black hole in his body that began to absorb much of his bloodline and soul force.

“No!” Leylin’s eyes were filled with wisps of blood immediately.

Though he’d already known that with the seal of the curse, it would be difficult to increase his strength, Leylin did not expect it to be this serious.

Based on his plans, after raising his truesoul to full moon, he would then reach peak rank 5. Even with the suppression of the curse mark, he could still regain his strength and even surpass it.

After all, if Leylin’s previous strength was 10 and the seal decreased it by 2, the strength he had left would only be 8.

But once Leylin reached peak rank 5, the limits of his strength would rise to 15, and even with the weakening of the seal by 2, he would still have 13 which far exceeded what he currently had.

However, the terror of the curse mark and the Snake Dowager’s adeptness at curses exceeded his expectations.

“Power of chaos!” A grey illusory feather appeared in Leylin’s hand. Large amounts of crystallisation of chaos combusted, beginning to support the seal on his forehead.

“The curse mark even has the function of automatically increasing strength along with the increase of strength in the host body!”

Leylin looked terrible at this point, and his expression turned into one of determination. He’d already had a contingency plan for this, but it wasn’t a crucial time yet and he didn’t want to waste this.

“Fine! Don’t you want to absorb me? I’ll give you everything!”

With his eyes red, Leylin ordered. A fiery-red jade-like crystal suddenly appeared from his spatial item, with flaming red luster and the indistinct phoenix cry!

The Soul Unique Item— The essence of the fragments of the phoenix egg, also the gem of Lava World! It could enhance soul force as long as the host’s vitality could withstand it.

Though Leylin had already reached the limits before, after sealing a beast spirit, his own vitality had been enhanced. On top of what he had been amassing all this time, it was enough for him to use this essence again.

*Chirp Chirp!*

A black demonic fire phoenix suddenly emerged from Leylin’s back, devouring the phoenix egg.

*Rumble!* Golden, brilliant flames burnt around him, and turned a demonic black.

Terrifying soul force that brought with it boiling fiery rays appeared around Leylin’s body, and filled the black hole of the curse mark.

*Chirp chirp!* Compared to bloodline force, the soul force that had the burning powers of the ancient phoenix caused the black hole to ripple, fiery-red rays flashing from deep within the black hole.

“Get lost!”

With Leylin’s roar, the curse mark on his forehead abruptly pulled back and even had a red scratch on it. Great amounts of the power of chaos formed a seal around the mark, suppressing it.

[Beep! Host has absorbed essence of phoenix egg. Obtained much soul origin. Soul force numbers increasing.]

With its voice, Leylin’s soul force numbers shot forward like a rocket, and in almost that instant, broke through the 250 bottleneck. After a few jumps, it broke through the critical point of 300!

[Beep! Host body’s soul force has broken through 300, reached full moon. Host’s stats have all changed. Recalculating.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice was still transmitting, but Leylin had no energy to investigate. His attention was now on the truesoul in the point mass.

The truesoul that was like a full moon had not only swollen up to the extreme, its whole body was filled with clear luster that gave off a feeling of perfectness.

“This is… the truesoul of peak rank 5 at full moon?”

Leylin mumbled as he gazed upon the gigantic full moon truesoul, looking drunk. The full moon not only had a clear luster, there was also a golden line that shimmered in and out of existence at the heart of it. However, it was covered by the brightness surrounding it. Unless he stared at it, he wouldn’t notice it.

“This is… when soul force has a qualitative change…”

Leylin’s eyes momentarily showed confusion, but was then filled with elation.

“I know, this is rank 6 truesoul force! Once Radiant Moon Magi reach full moon, their truesouls have already reached the limit. The next thing to do is to change the soul force from negative to positive energy, turning into the truesoul like a scorching sun of rank 6 Breaking Dawn Magi!”

“This golden line signifies my truesoul has already reached the limits of rank 5 and is beginning to transform into rank 6!”

Leylin sighed. For regular rank 5 Magi, getting their truesoul to full moon was already exceptionally difficult. They would have to work unceasingly to get their truesoul to fill completely and then automatically upgrade. That would take centuries, but Leylin had reached full moon in an instant.

“With negative soul force, I need to produce positive energy from this dark negative energy in order to gain solidified positive force. It’s not something a rank 5 beast spirit can achieve. The only explanation would be the essence of the phoenix egg!”

Leylin’s pupils brightened, “The phoenix egg contains not just a large amount of soul origin force that can strengthen a Magus’ soul, but also possesses anode soul force, and its the guide for full moon Magi to promote. That’s saved me hundreds of years of hard work!”

In that moment, Leylin thought of the reason.

Chapter 739: Life Curse

The method to refine negative soul force into positive and obtain the essence of positive soul force was the key for a rank 5 Radiant Moon Magus becoming a rank 6 Breaking Dawn Monarch.

The phoenix egg was the treasure of the Lava World after all, and the positive power it possessed could save most Radiant Moon Magi centuries worth of hard work.

If this was seen by those Breaking Dawn Monarchs who had broken through with hard work or peak rank 5 Radiant Moon who were still training desperately, they might be so jealous of Leylin that they might go crazy with envy.

“But that means the phoenix egg has been completely used up…” Leylin found this result quite a pity. With the boost from the rank 5 beast spirit, that was enough to push him to full moon. The phoenix egg left behind could be used in training at rank 6.

With the abundance of positive soul force in the egg, which could even help a Breaking Dawn Monarch advance at lightning speed, using it recklessly now as a rank 5 made him feelextremely wasteful.

Due to the limitations of his bloodline, Leylin’s truesoul already had signs of transforming into an substantialised positive soul, and he would never be able to succeed unless he completely rid himself of his bloodline curse.

“It’s too early to talk about rank 6. I’ll need to focus on the benefits that I now have!” While he found it a pity, Leylin was optimistic about the use of the phoenix egg. Due to the interference of the Allsnake Curse, he would not have been able to reach full moon if not for the power of the phoenix egg.

If the same thing were to happen again, Leylin was sure that he would make the same choice.

Ridding himself of other thoughts, Leylin gazed at the A.I. Chip’s stats column. As he had forcefully broken through to full moon, much of his stats had undergone huge changes.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 5 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (Complete form). Strength: 70 (85), Agility: 53 (66), Vitality: 175 (200.7), Spiritual force: 2315 (3001.2), Magic power: 2315 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul force: 232 (300) State: Boost from full moon truesoul and status as rank 4 Sacrificer. Rank 5 beast spirit seal: Alabaster Devilsnake. Estimation of Allsnake Curse’s next flare-up : 19 years.]

“As expected, after advancing, all the limits have increased. Even with restrictions of the curse marks, I’ve basically returned to my most powerful state before, with some increases even!” Leylin’s eyes shone as he felt the power in all parts of his body and couldn’t help but clench his fists, “Only this power would be enough for my plans in the holy city!”

“But…” Leylin, who had regained his calm, watched the insides of the tents that now looked messy and could not help but laugh wryly, “Thankfully, I set up a seal. Otherwise, Belinda and Sophia would have been alarmed.”

“The flare up of the Allsnake Curse happened with the Snake Dowager so close…”

Leylin looked incomparably serious, “A.I. Chip, activate strongest preventative measures!”

[Beep! Mission established. Initiation underway.]

Numerous white scaly patterns formed the most intricate patterns on Leylin’s face. Meanwhile, the Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit tattoo on Leylin’s body began to wander around, emitting a unique soul undulation.

After making all the preparations, a tremendous conscient was like a tsunami, spreading from the holy city.

“What is it, Mighty Mistress? Who dares go against you and caused you such ire?”

Such a terrifying conscient shocked many in that instant. Belinda and Sophia had walked out of their tents and knelt in the direction of the holy city, bodies trembling in the moonlight.

“She’s naturally looking for me!”

Leylin snickered inside, though on the surface, he looked to be kneeling in reverence and trepidation, praying that the Mistress would calm her anger. Of course, Leylin knew that before he was captured, this would be impossible.

Sensing this conscient roaring above him and passing him by, yet not doubting him at all, his lips quirked in a smile.

“As expected, the double cover of my soul and bloodline, as well as support of the feather of chaos, makes it impossible for the Snake Dowager to find me with this kind of scan with her conscient unless she sees me personally.”

This was definitely good news to Leylin.

Though the Nefarious Filthbird had guaranteed this, Leylin did not dare place too much hope on it.

When it came to life and death situations, he would not mind using all methods possible to increase his rate of success.

“Hss!” Realising that doing that would not help her find Leylin, the temporary wave of soul undulations passed and instead, a bright bundle of light rose like the sun from holy city.

Within the sun was a gigantic snake ball figure that was like a sun, and there were even sounds of sacrificial chanting from there.

These sounds were very ancient and had some strange pitches that caused one to be intoxicated in it.

“This…” Just after hearing a little, Leylin’s expression immediately changed.

[Warning! Warning! Host’s curse mark is acting up.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded in time, before a rune began to flicker on Leylin’s forehead.

Thankfully, Belinda and Sophia now had their heads down as they closed their eyes to pray, or else they’d definitely notice the change in Leylin.

“Feather of Chaos, ignite the crystals and get back!”

The blood vessels on Leylin’s face writhed, and immediately after, two forces began a dangerous confrontation inside.

*Chirp chirp!* At this moment, the flame imprints that were already on the curse mark began to flash with red lights, and Leylin seemed to hear the cry of a primordial fire phoenix.

With the joint work of the two, the flare up of the curse mark was suppressed.

Only after the illusion from the holy city disappeared did Leylin sigh deeply, and hastily reinforced his appearance-changing methods to hide any external changes, which was how Belinda did not notice anything different.

Even so, it was impossible to hide everything that had happened.

No matter what repercussions there were from the Snake Dowager’s sudden anger, Leylin and the others had to carry on their journey.

“Nick! I…” Belinda glanced at Leylin, who was the same as before, and seemed to have something to say.

“What’s wrong?” Leylin turned, a tender look and smile on his face as if nothing had happened.

“Oh, no, it’s nothing!” Belinda looked dazed, and also a little confused, “It just feels like something about you has changed, but I don’t know what it is for sure.”

“It’s the smell!” Sophia, who was ahead, turned back, eyes full of happiness as she sniffed at Leylin.

“The smell on Brother Nick’s body is even more aromatic, and Sophia feels more close to him!”

“Stop it!” Belinda grabbed at Sophia’s little face, causing her to frown.

Meanwhile, Leylin was stunned at her keen senses.

“I was discovered so quickly! Such a pure and sensitive soul is rather rare.”

Leylin naturally knew the reason why Belinda felt something was off, since a peak full moon truesoul was worlds apart from what things had been the previous day. Even if Leylin did all he could to conceal this, there would still be a subtle difference.

Besides, the rank 5 beast spirit that Leylin had chosen to seal was Belinda and her sister’s father! The bloodline aura from someone of the same kind and family had caused Sophia to realise what was off.

“However, from her experiences, I doubt she’s discovered this. If she found out the feeling of feeling closer to me came from her father, she might be fearful. After all, Kenta didn’t give the siblings a good impression…”

Pondering over this for a while, Leylin continued the journey with the sisters.

Though nothing had changed from the previous day, and Leylin was still chatting and joking with them cheerfully on the way, he was actually reading the contents of the prompt on the A.I. Chip, and his heart could not calm.

[Beep! Affected by Snake Dowager’s undulations. Variation to Curse Mark of Ten Thousand Snakes, increasing corroding ability.] [Curse of Corrosion– High grade variation of the curse mark. After entering region of Snake Dowager’s influence, Host’s life force will constantly be absorbed till death. The process is irreversible.]

“After realising she can’t find me, she’s used this method to force me to show myself?”

Feeling the life force in his body unceasingly being seized from his body, and his body heading towards death gradually, Leylin’s lips quirked in a smile instead, “But… for you, who can only do this much, does it mean you have no other ways of limiting me?”

“It’s not just my bloodline and soul force, but even my life force is being absorbed by the curse, subduing my strength.

Leylin raised his arm, his pale skin and firm muscles full of life. However, he could feel a sense of losing something.

“Under the effects of the corrosion, my body’s life energy is quickly dissipating. Though there aren’t obvious changes on the outside, in just a few years time, my appearance will become that of an old person… Even with appearance changing techniques, it wouldn’t be able to conceal these changes…”

“Just from the bloodline curse, I have about 19 years left, but with the curse that corrodes my life force…”

He smiled wryly.

He had a feeling that this sort of complex curse would have even worse effects the closer he got to the Snake Dowager.

This would go on till the day the curse mark completely flared up and ruined his soul, causing him to die, or until he would be discovered by the Snake Dowager.

“So many restrictions and so much pressure! How… enjoyable! This is too enjoyable!”

Leylin brushed the back of his hand against his lips slowly, “Such power restrictions is so enjoyable! The greater the pressure, the worse the backlash! I can’t wait to see the day I destroy these restraints and soar!”

Chapter 740: Reaching Holy City

“The Hail Continent’s holy city!” Leylin muttered as he sized up this city that seemed to have been built by giants.

The entire city was filled with brilliant lights, and what was the most unforgettable was the giant sculpture at the very heart of the city.

It was a very bewitching female with long hair with separated out and transformed into exotic snakes of all kinds. There were the iant Kemoyin Serpents, the Alabaster Devilsnakes, Three-headed Pythons, and many other species could be found within the hair of this snake chieftess.

“The sculpture must have been made with the Snake Dowager as the model. I can see it so clearly even outside the city, and if I were to determine the scale, it must be over tens of thousands of metres tall…”

Leylin’s eyes were full of admiration. If not for the spell formations and other assistance from other worlds, a statue of this scale could never have been accomplished.

The secret undulations hidden in various parts of the holy city made Leylin’s expression change slightly. While he was unable to detect rank 7 existences, the radiation from rank 6 Breaking Moons could no longer resist the A.I. Chip’s scans.

Hence, Leylin was certain that there were at least ten rank 6s in the holy city, and they were all descendants of the Snake Dowager!

‘From the intel and what I saw yesterday, the Snake Dowager is here, but I don’t know where she is.’

“Keke…” Leylin suddenly began to cough.

“What’s wrong, Nick?” Belinda and Sophia looked over, their eyes full of concern.

“It- It’s nothing!” Leylin laughed forcefully, hiding his palm that now had traces of blood.

“In the holy city, where the Snake Dowager’s aura is even more concentrated, the rate at which my life force depletes is even faster. With this rate, I might not be able to hold on for a few years, but thankfully, these few years should be enough!”

“I was just a little emotional after seeing such a huge city. Let’s get in! Have you notified your friend yet?”

“I’ve already notified Aegnis. She’ll be here soon!” Belinda laughed.

The three of them now stood outside the huge holy city. There were three huge triumphal arches, and a bridge that was tens of metres long. Below it was a surging moat, though the waters were black and gave an ominous feeling.

The gates of the city opened, and many half-snake people and even pure-bloods passed by in an orderly manner.

“That’s…” Upon seeing this, Leylin’s eyes narrowed.

The queue that wound around like a long snake suddenly had a small disturbance near the gates, and immediately after, a half-snake person with black scales on its face wailed as he was separated out, and was pushed into the black moat.

“Ah…” Its mournful cries vanished in an instant, and Leylin immediately saw only white bones, and even then, they melted quickly.

“Just now…” Leylin’s eyes shifted to the stone sculpture of snakes on the city gate. The vertical pupils of the sculptures were now flickering with green light.

“Seems like when that snake being passed by, the eyes of the sculptures turned bright red! Is that some sort of bloodline identification system?” Leylin was slightly afraid, because he had not found anything strange about that snake person earlier.

“That is the Snake Sculpture found everywhere in the holy city. As long as there are residents whose souls or bloodlines aren’t pure, or have not gotten permission, all will be detected and thrown into the Howling Abyss!”

There was a grim look on her face, “Based on the system of the holy city, whether it’s bloodline beings with unknown origins or wanted criminals, none can stay in the holy city!”

“Oh! In other words, if you and I were to enter, the sculpture’s eyes would turn red, and many soldiers would be attracted?”

Leylin stroked his chin, “What benefits are there, for so many of them to scramble there?”

“Benefits?” Belinda smiled wryly, “There are obviously a lot! First of all, all those who get permission to stay in holy city will have their safety guaranteed. In the Hail Continent, there are few organisations who dare treat residents of the holy city roughly!”

“Absolute protection?” Leylin nodded. In this era of living from hand to mouth, absolute protection was a dream come true for the weak.

“Also, the holy city is the core of the Hail Continent. You’ll be able to get anything at all here, even the most highly-ranked strength systems, the best offerings and beast spirits… but most importantly…” At the mention of the holy city, she evidently became excited.

“What’s most important is that the entire holy city has gained the favour of the Mistress, and all of those who live here will have the purity of their blood not fall in rank and even continuously increase based on the length of time they stay here.” Another voice sounded from the side, and along with a streak of black light, there were two more figures appearing.

“Aegnis!” Upon seeing who had arrived, Belinda grinned brilliantly.

“Belinda, my sister! We haven’t seen each other in around 132 years!” Someone headed over and gave Belinda an enthusiastic hug. This must be the good friend that Belinda had constantly mentioned, Aegnis.

Leylin could not help but size up this being. She had short brown hair, a tall stature, fair and glowing skin, and she wore tight-fitting armour that seemed to be made of crystal. Her fine nose was raised, and she had a heroic air to her. While a female, she had a gender-neutral beauty to her.

What surprised Leylin was the bloodline aura of her body. This even caused him some fear. This was definitely the bloodline of a rank 6 giant serpent, and Aegnis herself had already reached rank 5.

‘She evidently has the formidability of pure blood nobility! She’s only half-mature, and already has rank 5 strength. Once her bloodline completely matures, reaching rank 6 isn’t an issue! I can’t tell her Sacrificer and beast spirit master ranks though…’ Leylin silently began to judge her strength.

Compared to a mixed-blood like Belinda, she had a pure bloodline from a giant serpent. In other words, her main body was a python, and her human form was just for convenience.

“It must have been a miraculous coincidence that these two could have become good friends from the beginning!”

“Don’t worry! I won’t let off those people of the Trial’s Eye organisation for treating you that way! I told you before not to go to that sect made out of lunatic eyes. Only the might Mistress is worthy of our faith!” Aegnis warmly held Belinda’s hand, completely ignoring Leylin’s existence.

She held Sophia, eyes sparkling, “This must be your sister, Sophia, right? How adorable! I’d only seen her in portraits before. Don’t worry! I’ll take care of you and your sister’s identities. You’ll definitely be able to get the residence permit and gain the right to stay in the holy city permanently!”

Seeing how she was itching to hug Sophia close and her facial muscles twitching, Leylin suddenly thought of another word from his previous world.

“Alright, alright. Aegnis! I have a friend who I’ve yet to introduce to you!”

Her friend’s invasive gaze full of fervour was a little too much for Belinda, and she huffed as she struggled out of the devilish grasp of Aegnis, before pointing at Leylin.

“This is the person I talked to you about, and a good friend who’s rendered me a lot of help: Nick!” Belinda placed emphasis on the two words, ‘good friend’.

“Good friend? Him?” It was only at this point that she noticed Leylin and glared at Leylin challengingly.

“He doesn’t seem all that strong? He’s only a rank 5 mixed blood Alabaster Devilsnake! Oh, sorry, my beloved Belinda, I wasn’t talking about you. Whether it’s the blood from your father or mother’s side, they have combined magnificently on you, whether it’s your ruby-red eyes, or long silver hair full of luster… they are so intoxicating…”

“Aegnis, Nick is my friend just as you are!” Belinda smiled wryly and had to repeat herself.

“Alright, alright. Friend!” Aegnis flicked at the hair at her forehead, “Since it’s your friend, I’ll do it too!”

“Wait, sister, how can you let people with unknown origins just enter the holy city? Did you forget our work?” At this moment, the person behind Aegnis suddenly spoke.

“Hm?” Leylin noticed the person at this moment. He had short brown hair like Aegnis, and there was a faint resemblance. It seemed that they had blood relations.

“Oh, Belinda! So this is the useless brother I’ve mentioned before, Thomas! Thomas! Come here and say hello!”

“Good morning, beautiful ladies!” Thomas bowed respectfully, he looked enchanted and intoxicated as he gazed at Sophia, who was like a little girl,

“Aegnis!” Noticing the siblings ignoring Nick, obviously trying to infuriate him, Belinda was slightly annoyed.

“If you still keep that attitude, I’ll leave with Nick! Anyway, besides the holy city, there are tons of places we can go.”

Based on what she had mentioned, after obtaining permanent residency in the holy city, they could receive preferential treatment everywhere in the Hail Continent. It was the best method to counteract the fact that they were on the wanted list. Now for Leylin’s sake, she was unexpectedly discarding this opportunity, it could be said that this was very unusual.

‘But come on, don’t you know that the closer you seem to me, the more trouble you’ll bring to me?’ Leylin was speechless. He could already sense two pairs of eyes that were willing to burn him to ashes.

Chapter 742: Settling and Loft

‘Rumours say the Snake Dowager favours the holy city, granting huge benefits to all her descendants…’ Leylin thought, watching the siblings who were drunk on the feeling. ‘Truth be told, the holy city is just affected by the presence of her main body. The radiation from it refines their bloodlines.’

Of course, there was a limit to this process. However, the guarantee that their bloodlines wouldn’t deteriorate was enough for all of them to scramble here without delay.

‘Pity. This sort of high energy radiation is basically poison to me now.’ Sensing the curse mark continuously absorbing radiation and gaining strength, Leylin could only smile wryly. The Allsnake Curse had been sealed, but the closer he was to the Snake Dowager the more obvious the flare ups would become.

Hiding any signs of abnormality and taking the initiative to get closer to the Snake Dowager day by day, he was dancing on the edge of a knife.

‘But at least it’s confirmed that the Snake Dowager’s main body is close to the holy city.’ Leylin’s eyes lit up. Just for that, he had to stay here in spite of the threat to his life.

“The Matriarch’s sculpture is the core of the city, with the circles extending outwards from it. In the business district are Night of the Beast Spirits and Imagia’s Cabin, which are pretty good. Once you’ve settled down, I can accompany you on a stroll.” Aegnis was evidently extremely excited as she brought them to a region with majestic mansions around.

“This region belongs to us Stewarts. I’ve arranged for Belinda to stay in a villa near me. We can—”

*Trring! Trring! Trring!* Before Aegnis could finish speaking, she was interrupted by a series of rings from her vambrace. She opened a notification on her arm, her voice showing her discontentment. “What is it? Didn’t I specifically mention that you are not to bother me no matter what happens tonight?”

“My sincerest apologies, Lord Aegnis, but this incident is so strange that it requires your personal attention.”

“What is it?” Aegnis grew serious. For a subordinate who knew her personality to still trouble her, it would be something difficult to deal with.

“It has to do with a mutant contamination. It’s at least grade 4 in danger.”

“Fuck!” Aegnis cursed, evidently surprised. Immediately after, she closed off the communications and apologised to Belinda, “I’m so sorry Belinda, Sophia! There’s something I need to handle, but I’ve already booked a room at the Spiral Serpent Restaurant. Please do go!”

“Alright Aegnis, hurry on with your work!” Belinda nodded in understanding, pressing her cheeks onto Aegnis’ causing the woman to smile cheerfully.

“Thomas, I’ll leave the rest to you. If Belinda and little Sophia are the slightest bit unhappy, you know what will happen!” Aegnis left hastily after assigning this task. Leylin’s lips quirked up in a mysterious smile as he watched her leave.

“Alright then! My ladies, and this Mister Nick, please come with me!” Thomas said with a clap. He evidently wanted to act like a gentleman in front of the sisters.

Belinda and Sophia held no distaste for him and cheerfully chatted and joked around with hm until they reached a gorgeous villa. The entire villa lit up there with a snap of his fingers, warm light flooding every corner with a beep sounding.

Motes of multicolour light flew out into the little garden like fireflies, like little stars as they appeared before Sophia’s hands.

“The lights are voice controlled, and dust removal spells activate at specific timings everyday. There’s another spell formation here that can set the temperature. And every piece of furniture here was prepared specially by my elder sister. Since she didn’t know your preferences, she’s prepared for it and allowed you to choose things like your servants…” Thomas smiled warmly.

In the meanwhile, Belinda and Sophia were very satisfied with this villa.

“Most importantly, sister’s place is nearby. It’s easy to contact her.” Thomas smiled as he handed the keys over to Belinda.

“Thank you both, for everything you’ve done for us. What about Nick’s place?” Belinda glanced at Leylin.

“Mister Nick? I’m sorry, but this is area is restricted to female guests,” Thomas waved his arms helplessly. He made an alternative suggestion, “How about you two ladies get some rest while I bring Mister Nick to his room?”

Though Belinda and Sophia were slightly discontent with this, Leylin appeared to very enthusiastically agree, and let the two sisters stay behind.

……

Thomas waited until he and Leylin left the villa to show his true colours.

“Listen to me, kid. I don’t care who you are or what happened with those siblings on the way here. Just remember this. This is the holy city, and they aren’t people you should expect anything from. Understand?” he asked, levelling a threatening gaze at Leylin. He already had a plan; if Leylin tried to resist or look for the sisters, he would get the guards and throw this guy into the moat.

In any case, the Stewart family was strong and had powerful defences. It was simple to get rid of a lone traveler with nobody to rely on.

As for those sisters? After wailing over Leylin for a while, they could only end up accepting it.

‘Such is life!’ Thomas laughed wickedly. He loved that phrase.

However, contrary to Thomas’ expectations, ‘Nick’ actually seemed to be terrified and even hada flattering grin on his face, saying, “Alright, Mister Thomas. I have no expectations towards those sisters, and I’ll break off all relations with them from hereon. This humble servant here only wishes to have a stable life in the holy city, and I am already extremely satisfied. Why would I expect other things?”

Leylin looked completely sincere as he continued, “Only Lord Thomas is worthy of Miss Sophia!”

“Mm, you’re absolutely right!” This huge change in attitude dazed Thomas momentarily. He quickly recalled Leylin’s indifference to his provocation, and passed it off as a show of cowardice and weakness in retrospect.

‘Such a weak personality. He’s probably someone the sisters made friends with on the way here,’ Thomas wondered to himself, and suddenly found Leylin less of an eyesore.

A dark thought reared its head in the depths of his heart, ‘In the future, if I bring the sisters over here, Nick’s amazed expression will be very amusing…’

Leylin’s position had lowered in his mind, from a love rival to a mere tool to be used. His malicious intent abated.

‘If those sisters won’t agree, wouldn’t it be fun to have Nick knock them unconscious and then send them to my bed?’ Thomas stroked his chin, daydreaming of this beautiful scene in the future. His lips arched.

“Well then. Lord Thomas, may I know where my lodging is? The prices in the holy city, they’re really… Without anyone vouching for me, I can’t rent a good place,” Leylin seemed to hesitate before making his request.

However, Thomas, who now found Leylin less of an eye-sore, did not hesitate to agree. How could he make life difficult for Leylin if he did not have anything over him? In addition, placing the man right under his nose was better than having him going out by himself, where he could even try to hit on the sisters.

“Come with me!” Having thought this through, Thomas brought Leylin to another region. Compared to the luxurious villas before, this packed place seemed to be cheap. It was the difference between heaven and earth.

Thomas brought Leylin to another district, “This is the place! This estate belongs to our family, just that I don’t know which idiot bought the rights to it then…”

Before him was an attic room. There were swirls on the wood of the walls and floor, and the place seemed dark and wet. It looked to be on the verge of collapse. It was also extremely small. There was a huge disparity between this and Belinda’s luxurious villa.

Of course, this wasn’t half bad considering the neighbouring residences.

“What do you think? This one isn’t too bad compared to the surroundings. At the least, you wouldn’t be able to pay a year of rent here even if you used up all your money…” Thomas laughed meanly without a care, “But I’m kind. You can live here as long as you want, no need to pay rent. I’ll tell the guards.”

“Thank you so much, my Lord!” Leylin bowed down nearly ninety degrees with a humble smile as he took the runic keys from Thomas. After multiple agreements not to look for the sisters, he finally managed to send a content Thomas away before activating them and sizing up his residence.

The wooden door let out sad creaks, as if unable to handle the stress. Leylin began to suspect that if this wasn’t supported by the strength of spells, the whole building would immediately turn into a pile of rubble.

Chapter 743: Rationality and Reality

‘However, it’s still not bad!’ After scanning the room, Leylin nodded lightly.

The place was a little small, lacked furniture, and was covered in a thick layer of dust, it would still fetch a sky-high rent in the holy city, where an inch of land was worth as much in gold. Since he could live here for free, why would he be dissatisfied?

What made Leylin feel even more satisfied was that this place was the Stewart family’s property, and Thomas had even specially registered it for him. With Thomas vouching for him, even if the entire city was thoroughly searched in the future, this place would be as steady as a rock.

Leylin had his own reasons for his actions today. They were only performed after careful deliberation. The holy city would be entering troubled times, and without a strong patron a simple search would be very troublesome. Why else would he live here? He had no lack of valuable materials to sell.

For one, he didn’t want to offend Thomas. Another reason was that he was borrowing the Stewart family’s tiger skin. Putting on a false facade to intimidate others] to shield himself. Of course, once his plan was exposed it would implicate the Stewart family, especially Thomas. That would be an incredibly sad matter for them, but it was all within Leylin’s considerations.

In reality, the idea had flashed after he saw Aegnis and her brother’s infatuation with the sisters. Once they got him into the holy city, Belinda and her sister had almost exhausted their potentials, and they would just spell trouble in the future. In this dog eat dog world, beauty without strength was the most troublesome.

His options were clear. On one hand he could maintain his relationship with Belinda and her sister, but in the process offend Aegnis and her brother. By extension, he would offend the Stewart family who backed them. On the other, he could renounce his relations with Belinda and gain the family’s understanding and protection. From Leylin’s perspective, the answer was obvious.

Some people chose to head down a path of ruin, refusing to live quietly and even blatantly standing out despite being weak. Only an author sticking out their Golden Thumb1 would be able to save such cases.

Although Leylin couldn’t be considered weak, in the Purgatory World, and especially this holy city, he was as frail as someone who would die to light being shone on them!

Indeed, he could reveal his strength and ruthlessly strike Thomas down. That would be followed Aegnis, then the Stewart family’s position in the top ranks. He could move the entire holy city! All for a single moment, it would be an incomparably glorious scene.

That is, until his origins aroused suspicion. Then, with one glance the Snake Dowager would know immediately that he was the one she was looking for, and he would’ve delivered himself to her on a plate. Then Leylin truly would have lost everything.

And looking back at the root of the problem, it would be for what? Two women? Were they really worth all that?

Leylin had no feelings for Sophia and Belinda, they were simply companions he had met on the road. Belinda had a vaguely good impression of him, and would at most casually joke around from time to time. For Leylin to have to fight for her and ultimately lose everything- wouldn’t that be outrageous?

With the Allsnake Curse on his body, and at a time where he was slowly inching towards death, worrying about trivial matters like affection was just foolish.

‘What I need now is to spare no effort in hiding myself, and conflict with the Stewarts, a tyrannical snake family, is clearly very unwise… And especially over two women…’ Leylin shook his head. Compared to directly clashing with Thomas and finally triggering that situation of completely exposing himself, Leylin simply chose to implement a plan which would minimise his influence and give him the greatest benefits.

‘However, Thomas couldn’t tell that his greatest enemy in getting Belinda and Sophia isn’t me, but his sister Aegnis!’ Leylin stroked his chin thoughtfully, with a trace of an sneer on his face.

With Aegnis at the sisters’ side glaring covetously like a tiger watching its prey, Thomas’ plan could be declared a successful failure before it even began. And of course, once he broke through his bloodline shackles Leylin could naturally make Thomas pay the price for today’s insults.

With this thought, he’d handed Sophia and Belinda over to Aegnis for a while, letting her safeguard them while he received a rare guarantee of safe entry into the city. It wasn’t a difficult thing for him to accept, and in fact he had more important matters to attend to than this.

Without greeting the envious neighbours around him, Leylin immediately shut the door. This two storey apartment building with a little courtyard outside it met his expectations.

After seeing a small flowerbed in the enclosure, Leylin’s face blossomed into a smile.

‘Not bad. It really is decent! All that’s left wanting is for nobody to come and bother me. Unfortunately, that is impossible…’ Leylin sighed, looking at the palm of his hand.

Blue-green veins were revealed under the light, and he could still faintly feel his life force ebbing. His body even looked a little weak.

‘This situation…’ Leylin laughed bitterly, ‘A.I. Chip!’

[Beep! Calculating data on host’s life force…… Analysis completed! The Allsnake Curse’s corrosive ability has been amplified in the holy city. New estimated time: Three years and two months!]

“Even if I seal off my bloodline and soul, this life drain is still unavoidable… It really is too difficult to break through the shackles of a rank 8 existence…” There was a trace of a sigh in Leylin’s expression. No matter how carefully he prepared, how far-reaching his plans were, the effect of a single seal from the Snake Dowager could instantly put him back in square one.

This was the result of an absolute gap in strength. Leylin himself always liked to bully the weak, and what he hated most was a situation where he was forced to challenge those who were much stronger than him.

Those thrillseekers who liked giving themselves heart attacks instead of safely profiting from a situation were all lunatics!

‘Fortunately, I have my experience. Along with my Full Moon truesoul and all the preparations I’ve made, I still have a chance… Ha!’ Leylin coughed, and entered the apartment building.

After spending half a day, Leylin had inspected almost every corner of this shabby apartment building, and had even secretly replaced all the defences with his own.

Leylin couldn’t trust this kind of property that belonged to a family, there could be monitoring and probing equipment inside. With the A.I. Chip’s atomic-level scanning and Leylin’s own sight as a Grandmaster of spell formations, the few devices that had been set up couldn’t escape him.

Naturally, Leylin did not choose to dismantle them immediately, which would cause him to completely fall out with the Stewart family. Instead, he prepared a layer of seals apart from the monitoring devices, to make the family feel that this place was still in their grasp. In reality, not a single trace of Leylin’s actions would be leaked out to them. Once night fell, the fence surrounding the courtyard was covered with a layer of grey runes which slowly vanished from sight.

“Although it’s just a temporary construction, it should be enough to deal with my neighbours!” Leylin muttered to himself, arriving at a completely sealed room with no windows.

The rotten floorboards emitted an unpleasant odour, and there was even a lot of dust on the floor. As it did not have any windows, the entire room looked extremely gloomy.

He immediately prepared a sacrificial spell formation, with a rune depicting a giant bird in the middle. Traces of grey power flowed above it continuously, making the rune of the giant bird seem as if it had spread its wings to fly.

“Almighty Ruler of Chaos! The Wings of the Storm! Free will from another dimension! Your majesty, the Nefarious Filthbird! Your Sacrificer requests that you give me your attention!”

A wave of intent burst forth from Leylin’s body, containing the power of a Full Moon truesoul. It instantly linked up with someone through the spell formation.

“Kemoyin Emperor! You have actually already entered the holy city! Good! Very good! Excellent!” Excitement could be felt from the Nefarious Filthbird, although it didn’t have a body to descend to. After all, they were in the Snake Dowager’s back garden, and they were under strict surveillance.

In reality, were Leylin discovered to be making a Sacrifice to the Nefarious Filthbird, leave alone himself even Thomas would be hunted down and killed immediately.

This was the Hail Continent’s holy city! Only one dignitary could ever rule it, and that was the Snake Dowager. Even an ally like the Trial’s Eye couldn’t spread its influence here, let alone the Nefarious Filthbird.

Consequently, seeing that Leylin had unexpectedly infiltrated the enemy’s frontlines without a hitch, the Nefarious Filthbird’s excited mood was understandable.

“Almighty dignitary, I appeal for you to bestow your chaos power, and conceal all the affairs in this apartment building so that I can escape from the gaze of the Snake Dowager!” Leylin sincerely prayed, but he did not offer any sacrifices.

“Of course! It will be your reward for bringing the power of chaos into the Holy City! If you are willing to sincerely offer sacrifices to me, in the future you will definitely become my helping hand, a rank 6 Sacrificer!”

A gentle chirp could be heard, and shortly after a grey circle began to rise up from the floors and walls, rapidly covering the entire apartment building. Everything was done in the dark and in secret, without emitting any strange undulations or radiance.

Watching the spell formation’s radiance dim, a strange expression flickered within Leylin’s eyes. Although he had not offered any sacrifices this time, the Nefarious Filthbird still magnanimously assisted him in concealing himself, and had even bestowed a great amount of power. This was obviously not just out of kindness.

The Nefarious Filthbird seemed to not have given up on the plan of using his chaos power to thoroughly contaminate him, and for him to finally become its underling. However, they were both currently reluctantly united due to their common enemy, the Snake Dowager. If a difference in opinion occurred in the future, they would very possibly become enemies instead.

“It looks like my success in infiltration excited the Nefarious Filthbird!” Leylin laughed coldly, “Unfortunately the bird has nothing to do with my future plans, and I will never find it again! The Nefarious Filthbird’s plans are destined to be all for naught!”

Chapter 745: Allsnake and Tyrant

‘There seems to be some disturbance in the holy city today.’ Leylin looked at the sky. The sound of a piercing alarm could be heard, but he ignored it as he continued to water his garden.

‘According to my plan, those serpents contaminated by gluttony should have reached this place. It seems like the guards have discovered something,’ Leylin was unhurried, busying himself with his own matters.

In reality, with all the time that had passed gluttony had already permeated the Serpent Plains. This epidemic wouldn’t disappear unless the plains were completely destroyed. That was how certain Leylin was of his own work.

With a push on his end, the original power of gluttony on the plains had become unstoppable. The large amount of giant high-energy snakes, combined with this terrifying power that made use of food intake to break through, created a horrifying effect that exceeded even Leylin’s expectations.

‘With this speed, perhaps even those rank 5 or 6 creatures won’t be able to avoid being contaminated by the power of gluttony,’ Leylin’s lips quirked up in a smile.

Even a rank 6 snake nest on the plains had no choice but to run away or be consumed by their gluttonous desires, and ultimately consume others or become fodder. There was no other way out.

As for the Snake Dowager? She might an incredibly powerful rank 8 being, and the dignitary who ruled over the Hail Continent, but the Sovereign King of Gluttony, Beelzebub, was no pushover either. As a being who was equally at rank 8 and someone who had grasped the laws of gluttony, he ended up discovering the Purgatory World and making use of his power to take over the whole plains.

Now, it was too late even if Beelzebub decided he wanted to halt the war with the Snake Dowager. After all, as an invader, how could he give up such a huge, splendid area in the Hail Continent?

Consequently, unless the Snake Dowager were to abandon the entire holy city and hand over the Serpent Plains, the two of them would not be able to come to an agreement.

If she chose to give in and gave up the plains, it would be an invitation to share rule over the Hail Continent. This was equivalent to slowly committing suicide, which was obviously unacceptable. It was foreseeable that the conflict between them could only increase in intensity.

The earth trembled, sending pebbled jumping around on the ground. A ball of coiled snakes that was like a star rose above the skies of the holy city.

“It’s the Matriarch! The mighty Holy Mother!” In that moment, the residents of the holy city all began to pray. Leylin appeared to be doing the same, but on the inside he was raising all of his defences.

*Rumble* Like an earthquake or an erupting volcano, a conscient that was extremely terrifying began to spread in all directions, with the sculpture at the very centre of it all. Leylin could sense the Snake Dowager’s immense fury from the terrifying wave. The other free residents could only lie on the ground, trembling.

‘The laws the Snake Dowager has grasped… Are they of bloodlines, serpents, or reproduction?’

Leylin seemed to react the same way as his surrounding neighbours, even looking more devout than some of them. However, he was inwardly attempting to trace the source of the Snake Dowager’s laws through her conscient’s undulations.

‘It seems to be the mix of a few. There’s also a trace of darkness.’ His astounding knowledge, coupled with the A.I. Chip’s tremendous database, allowed Leylin to somewhat identify these laws.

‘The Snake Dowager is terrifying. Not only does she grasp multiple laws, but she has already begun to refine her comprehension of her laws and fuse it with the law of shadows to form an entirely new law…’

The realm of rank 8 was naturally superior to rank 7, where only one law had been grasped. From this wave, Leylin had pried into the path that she had probably taken.

‘Rank 7 Magi have to grasp the powers of a single law, but in order to grasp multiple laws, rank 8 beings have to attempt refining them?’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘Then what about rank 9 Magi? The legendary most powerful realm of all? Does it mean containing all laws in one body and trying to create something more powerful?’

A murky understanding seemed to dawn on Leylin’s mind. The Snake Dowager’s path might be wrong, but her actions still gave Leylin, who was going in blind, a great enlightenment.

‘Let’s leave that aside for now. The Snake Dowager must have discovered the contamination from the power of gluttony, but I still don’t know how Beelzebub will react.’ Leylin watched the battle from the shadows.

“I am the Snake Dowager, source of all snake bloodlines.” The ball of snakes uncoiled, revealing the charming face of the mother of all snakes. Every strand of hair represented an astounding amount of power that caused the air to distort.

While she was transmitting her will, Leylin abruptly felt the Snake Dowager launch a probing force even more powerful than before.

‘Seems like she still has yet to give up on finding me. Or, has she guessed that I’m the one behind all this? But even if she has noticed it, what can she do?’ Leylin snickered.

He was now using an obvious scheme. Using the Purgatory World and the Allsnake Plains as bait, Leylin had attracted Beelzebub over. And, as long as he had the desire to take over this world, Beelzebub would never reach an agreement with the Snake Dowager.

Beelzebub had previously suffered great losses under Leylin’s hand, and nothing would change this fact even if they had a common enemy in the Snake Dowager.

In their eyes, Leylin was merely a tiny bug that could easily be pinched to death. Why would they pause their conflict to work together and attack him?

This was reality. As long as there was a victor, either side would have no problem dealing with Leylin later. This situation gave Leylin the amount of time he needed.

“Purify!” The eyes of the Snake Dowager held benevolence and compassion as she spread her arms. Holy golden rays of light rained down in every direction, with the holy city at the heart of it all.

Bits of a dark red liquid were repelled from the roots, water sources and even pores of some giant snakes, and then neutralised by the golden rays, turning into pure water droplets.

‘The Snake Dowager of the Shadow World has such knowledge on light-type purification spells? As expected of an ancient being who has lived through the ancient war. She has no weaknesses…’ Leylin’s pupils shrank as the the A.I. Chip recorded the information, trying to simulate the limits of her power.

While the A.I. Chip couldn’t really tell how much power an existence like the Snake Dowager had, just having a vague idea was still helpful for Leylin.

Under the golden holy light, the region around the holy city was completely purified. The area continued to expand all the way to the depths of the Serpentes Plains.

Watching what should be a worrisome scene, Leylin’s eyes glinted with delight, ‘It’s a pity. If I was the only one behind this, just a few purification processes by the Snake Dowager would save the Serpentes Plains. However, there is someone else who lords over the power of gluttony.’

At this very moment, a strange happening occurred with a loud crash!

Large amounts of the dark red contaminated liquid that should have disappeared began to boil. The red motes of light converged and formed a huge ball of red light that soared into the air like a bloody moon.

“Hail to master Beelzebub! You are the Sovereign King of Gluttony, the child of original power, the master of everything in this world.” A resonant praise that held traces of insanity began to echo in the holy city, striking the Snake Dowager’s holy light display.

“This feeling… you’re…” The Snake Dowager’s enraged voice was heard from within the holy light, before it was drowned out by large amounts of crimson lightning.

The crimson lightning looked like long lines that danced in the air, tearing out cracks and revealing huge terrifying spatial rifts.

Two webbed hands with seven fingers each pressed on the side of a rift, causing it to roar as it expanded. There seemed to be a terrifying existence at the other end of the spatial crack trying to squeeze in.

“Ha, Beelzebub! You can’t endure it anymore? That makes sense– a place where the World Will is this chaotic must be heaven for you.”

Leylin laughed as if he had the upperhand. With the temptation of a huge world lacking a will, Beelzebub decided to take the risk. Even if this wasn’t his real body, it was at least a clone with 50% of the strength of the real body. For Beelzebub, the losses incurred if he were to fail would cause his main body to be severely injured and enter a deep sleep, or he could possibly die. It made obvious his intentions.

“You dare trespass on my territory? Do you attach any importance at all to the treaty of alliance, which has been in place since time immemorial?” If Beelzebub was full of determination, then the Snake Dowager was full of fury. After all, anyone would be in a foul mood if they were relaxing at home and someone else just decided to barge in.

While the Snake Dowager fired her questions, the golden holy light seemed to transform. A layer of darkness appeared like a huge web, vast and layered, dispelling the crimson lightning out of the holy city.

After being challenged by someone of the same rank, the Snake Dowager finally showed her true strength.

Chapter 747: Dreamscape Waning

“Soul undulations, bloodline detection, identity testing— pass!” A mechanical voice transmitted from a small sculpture of the Snake Dowager held by the squad leader.

Sensing the detecting undulations sweeping past him, Leylin inwardly sneered. With his soul force and bloodline concealed, and especially with Aegnis inadvertently protecting him as his original information had been entered into the database, the identity test that was most likely to expose him had its leaks completely sealed. Even if they examined him again, it would be to no avail.

“Haven’t you finished the inspection? Shouldn’t you get lost then?” Thomas looked at the bunch of guards who hurried away in confusion, with a satisfied look in his eyes.

“Little Sophia! These guards all belong to the Stewart family. If you encounter them in the holy city, don’t be frightened, just give them my name!” Shortly afterwards, Thomas made this solicitous offer.

Leylin secretly rolled his eyes. He knew that if it wasn’t for Belinda and her sister, Thomas wouldn’t have so hot-bloodedly rushed out to support him.

“Nick, are you alright?” Belinda and her sister went into the little courtyard, and when they saw how narrow the place was and how cramped the apartment was, they wrinkled their brows. “Would you like to come and live with us instead?”

“That’s not necessary!” “That’s not necessary!”

Leylin and Thomas spoke almost at the same time, and seeing the threatening expression in Thomas’ eyes, Leylin inwardly sneered. He switched to a smile and said to Belinda, “This place is very nice! And besides, Young Master Thomas is letting me live here entirely for free, this is very rare in the holy city… To be honest, being able to become a free citizen of the holy city, even if it’s only for 10 years, I can’t ask for anything more than this……”

Leylin intentionally emphasised the last few words, and from Thomas’ point of view, this was Leylin surrendering to him, so he nodded his head with satisfaction.

Belinda, on the other hand, looked at Leylin with astonishment. From her impression of him, Leylin definitely wouldn’t behave like this.

“But… Brother Nick! How can you live here? Sophia’s heart is distressed…” Sophia tugged at Leylin’s sleeve.

“Alright, alright! The both of you, don’t come back and give me trouble!” Leylin didn’t care, pushing Belinda and Sophia out with an impatient expression. He then shut the door in their faces/

“Very good. You’ve done well.” Once the door had been shut, he heard Thomas’ secret message, but at the same time he heard other news.

Immediately after, Thomas’ arrogant and proud voice could be heard just outside. “Don’t bother with that Nick anymore. Look! He actually treated you both like this. Little Sophia, shall I bring you to play at the Holy Mother’s Sculpture?”

As their voices grew more distant, Leylin shook his head with a laugh.

“Sometimes, when you don’t want trouble, trouble comes to find you instead! Did I put on too good a performance when we were on the road?” He currently wished for the entire world to forget him, and let him quietly farm properly.

However, now it looked like—

……

Night had fallen, and the purple halo of the moon had slipped down. Inside the holy city there was none of the clamor of the day, and even the places filled with holy light had all dimmed down.

After a full day of searching the entire city, and with dozens of unlucky people without papers thrown into the moat, dissolving until their bones couldn’t be found, the streets were completely deserted with a desolate atmosphere.

“Activate the bloodline imprint!”

In the small courtyard next to the flowerbed, Leylin looked at his right arm. On his wrist were ten small white snake imprints lying side by side.

These were naturally the bloodline imprints he had made using the Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline.

*Hss—* A rank 5 beast spirit tattoo appeared before his eyes, making Leylin’s control over the bloodline imprint much easier.

“The beast spirit’s power has an effect of resisting suppression, and can maximise the imprint’s effect!” There was a trace of a smile on Leylin’s face, and soon he saw the brand on his hand fading rapidly and disappearing.

[Beep! The host has consumed the Alabaster Devilsnake’s bloodline imprint, initiating connection with Dreamscape!]

The innate skill of the Alabaster Devilsnake was the ability to travel to Dreamscape. Leylin himself had acquired this ability through the bloodline imprint.

However, in his heart, he had some doubts about it. After all, this was something he gained from the Thousand-Eyed Woman on his previous adventure in the Dreamscape. As a result, when his truesoul connected to the monstrous and dazzling world, Leylin did not choose to immediately enter it. Instead, he attempted to draw on some dreamforce.

*Ssss—* The air seemed to shimmer and warp like in a hazy heat, and traces of dark red dreamforce began to fall in without end, sinking into the earth of the flowerbed.

The green Seed of Wisdom seemed to welcome it, and absorbed the dreamforce. It even budded a little green shoot, and seemed to be filled with the breath of life.

The dark red dreamforce was like a fog, and lingered on around the small bud. It was continuously absorbed by the bud, and appeared to have become a nutrient source.

At this moment, it sounded as if a bowstring had snapped in the void. An oppressive voice sounded, and the dreamforce rapidly faded, disappearing in a flash.

“What’s going on? I used the bloodline imprint to pull dreamforce in, and it’s just this little… It’s not equal to the previous times I’ve used it… Don’t tell me…” Leylin’s expression immediately turned gloomy.

[Beep! Dreamforce has rapidly decreased, determined to be at the nadir.]

“What bad luck! To think that it also had this uncertain and deceptive characteristic…” Leylin could only laugh bitterly.

Although dreamforce at its peak phase could be compared to the power of laws, it was full of uncertainty. Now it had declined, dropping from the zenith to the nadir. Currently, it was perhaps far weaker than bloodline force.

“I can feel it! The entire Dreamscape seems to have sunk into stillness, and all dreamforce has vanished!” Leylin had a solemn expression. He could feel a lot of things through the Alabaster Devilsnake beast spirit and bloodline.

Not only had dreamforce fallen into its weak phase, even the Dreamscape itself had sunk into silence, meaning that if he wanted to draw out dreamforce, he needed to waste even more power than before. And its effects would be greatly reduced as well!

‘As expected, choosing not to rely on dreamforce was the correct decision; this random and uncertain behaviour is basically used to cheat people…’ Leylin shook his head, and at the same time he suddenly understood, ‘No wonder the Snake Dowager’s performance today was so poor! She seemed evenly matched with the divided truesoul clone of a rank 8, it was because dreamforce had fallen into its trough phase and reduced her strength… ’

The weakness of dreamforce was both a blessing and a curse for Leylin. The best advantage was that the Snake Dowager clearly could not use dreamforce without restraint, which was the same as cutting off an arm.

‘If it’s like this, the advantages of Dreamscape entering its silent phase outweigh the disadvantages for me!’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘Besides, I have my reserves of chaos power and so many bloodline imprints. I can afford to use them up a little, I can still complete the plan.’

From Leylin’s point of view, if one bloodline imprint from before could draw over 10 units of dreamforce, then now it was only enough to draw over 1 unit. For those who primarily used dreamforce, this terrifying reduction was a complete nightmare!

Once dreamforce grew weak, perhaps even existences on the level of the God of Evil could only withdraw into Dreamscape or even take the initiative to lie dormant and reduce their consumption until dreamforce was restored.

However, Leylin staked it all on his abundant bloodline imprints; even if he wasted a few, it wasn’t as if he couldn’t make up for it.

In any case, he had reaped many bloodlines from Belinda’s family and it was enough to support his consumption, and it wasn’t as if the Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline was limited to that family.

“When you think of trouble, trouble will arrive!” Leylin’s brows pressed together, and he sighed helplessly. With a wave of his right hand, a whirlwind of energy particles appeared and swept across the flower garden.

Although he had already prepared for this, the energy aura from earlier could leak out some things, and Leylin naturally would not leave such a huge leak without caring.

After a moment, a dreamlike figure came out from the moonlight.

“Nick!” She looked at Leylin with a complicated expression on her face.

She had long golden-white hair which shone with vibrant lustre under the moonlight, scarlet eyes which were as beautiful as rubies. She seemed like the very personification of beauty, and she had a strange attractive force about her.

“You’ve come!” Leylin greeted her without even turning his head.

“I already left a message for you earlier, you know this!”

Belinda went directly to Leylin and looked at him with her beautiful eyes that were devoid of restraint, “I know that the outsiders from earlier could have given you trouble so I’ve come secretly, the other’s don’t know. Did Thomas, that disgusting fellow, pressure you?”

It had to be said that Belinda was a very intelligent girl, she was after all a senior Sacrificer for the Trial’s Eye who even mercilessly exacted vengeance on her own family. How could she not be scheming? Leylin’s transformation was far too obvious, anyone could see the difference.

“Even if he did, so what?” Leylin spread out his hands helplessly: “In the holy city, do we have any other choice?”

“I’ll kill him!” Belinda let out a murderous aura, and it wasn’t faked.

“And after that? After becoming a wanted criminal of the holy city, and really flee to the other end of the world? How childish!” Leylin coldly refuted her.

“So what?” Belinda bit her lip, and her eyes seemed to sparkle a little: “Even if I don’t kill him, we can just move out and become mercenaries and do missions, we will still be able to live in the holy city…”

Chapter 748: Tacit Understanding

At the end, Belinda’s voice was choked with sobs.

Leylin looked at how Belinda was speaking in her tearful voice, and was rendered speechless. ‘Alright I didn’t think my acting would have such a great effect, did the mental suggestions affect her too deeply?’

However, what he needed now was to be low-profile, and he couldn’t be together with Belinda and bring trouble onto himself. The beauty of the two sisters would be a source of chaos anywhere.

Knowing this, how could Leylin put himself in danger?

“Become mercenaries? Hah, how would we afford the holy city’s rent and prices? Particularly with the Stewart family, you can’t just break away from them just because you want to. Against this family who have extended their tentacles in all corners of the holy city, what can you possibly do?”

Leylin could only play the role of a realist, and coldly strike down Belinda.

“Nick, you’ve changed! You weren’t like this before!” The callous words made Belinda a little dull, and she looked at Leylin with a rather foolish expression.

“I haven’t changed, I’ve only accepted reality! Go!” Leylin seemed to wave his hand impatiently, and also violently began coughing at the same time.

“Uh, no!” Belinda stepped forward and directly brushed away Leylin’s palm, and finally saw the blood that Leylin had coughed up.

“Your life force! How could it became this weak, and why do you have all these symptoms? What happened to your strength? Has it disappeared?”

Leylin’s life force was continuously degenerating, and although his appearance was the same as before, his vitality was constantly sapped away. Compared to before, it was like the difference between a candle and a torch.

“It’s an old wound from past adventures, it’s nothing!” As for this, Leylin did not try to hide it, and it could no longer be concealed either.

This was the reason he had done his best to avoid conflict. With his strength in decline, unrepentantly provoking formidable powers could only be described as foolish.

“I knew it! You were afraid! Afraid of burdening me and Sophia!” On the contrary, Leylin’s condition made Belinda seemingly join the dots.

“Are you afraid of becoming a burden to me? It doesn’t matter, I can certainly cure you!” Belinda looked deeply into Leylin’s eyes, her figure disappearing into the moonlight.

Leylin stood there somewhat speechlessly: “She actually thought of something? Although it’s not quite the case at all…”

However, if Belinda wanted to think of it like this, it didn’t seem like it would do him any harm. Leylin thought about it a little, but did not intend to expose himself.

“Now… perhaps after the Sovereign King of gluttony’s appearance today, the structure of the holy city is likely to have changed dramatically…” After Belinda had left, Leylin took up his sprinkler again and attentively tended to the budding shoots in his flowerbed. His expression was peaceful and serene, and he seemed to have nothing to do with the outside world.

In fact, this truly was the case. On the second day, along with a heavily injured Aegnis returning home, an even more terrifying news came about— mad beasts contaminated by gluttony had appeared near the holy city!

Even if the Snake Dowager had already discovered this and carried out her purification, with Beelzebub’s disruption her schemes clearly could not succeed.

However, her earlier purification still had some effects. At the very least, Aegnis still managed to retain her life, but she had suffered severe injuries, which filled many serpent guards with endless fear.

According to Aegnis’ report, a group of giant serpents contaminated by gluttony had already broken through into the holy city. The neighbouring half snake people had suffered enormous losses.

The members of the squad that was with her had all unfortunately perished, and even their corpses had been swallowed up by those insatiable beasts, until there was nothing left.

After all, compared to ordinary food, snake flesh of a superior species was abundant in energy, especially those snake people who were of high rank. It was even easier for them to become the targets of the gluttonous beasts!

gluttonous beasts! This description had come from Aegnis, and was very quickly widely adopted to distinguish them from other giant serpent species.

No matter what creature it was, once it was contaminated by the power of gluttony, it would enter a horrifying state of hunger where it didn’t mind what it ate. They were all called gluttonous beasts.

The holy city and the Stewart family attached great importance to this report, They prepared both the city defence soldiers and a great number of reserves. They declared that the holy city was imposing martial law, and even released a large number of tasks for mercenaries and adventurers to target the gluttonous beasts invading the holy city.

In a short while, the entire Serpent Plains seemed to ripple unpredictably with activity, and this chaotic scene seemed to spread ceaselessly in the Hail Continent.

What the ordinary citizens of the holy city didn’t know was that this situation would continue for a very long time. Furthermore, in a short span of time, the gluttonous beasts would replace all the previous natural and manmade calamities to become the primary threat to their survival.

……

Time seemed to pass in a flash, and a year went by before he knew it.

“Brother Nick! Sophia is here to see you!” Looking like a younger Belinda, Sofia pushed open the door and walked in. She wore a hunting outfit and looked very exuberant and heroic, overflowing with the vitality of youth. Looking at her, Leylin felt a little envious.

“You’ve come, Sophia!” Leylin smiled and greeted her, inwardly shaking his head.

Although he had come to a tacit understanding with Belinda, Sophia clearly did not know much. Not only this, neither Leylin or Belinda could possibly tell her that much, because with her intelligence it was impossible for her to keep secrets.

As a result, although Belinda had cut back on coming to Leylin’s place, Sophia still remembered her brother Nick, and came over from time to time.

“Brother Nick, haven’t you recovered from your illness?” Sophia drew closer to Leylin, with obvious worry in her eyes. It was now possible to tell that Leylin was beyond saving. Although his appearance had not changed too much, wrinkles had appeared on his forehead and the back of his hands. His body’s life force continuously disappeared, giving an account of just how weak he was.

“*Cough*… It’s alright! *Cough*…” Leylin took out a white handkerchief and covered his lips. The back that stood so tall and straight in the past seemed to have become a little hunched.

“It’s already become like this, how could you say it’s alright? The Spring of Life that elder sister Belinda asked me to bring last time, are you using it?”

“I have!” Leylin smiled, and picked up his sprinkler.

A milky-white spring water with a rich fragrance was poured into the soil.

The budding shoots in the flowerbed before had now grown into a small tree, the glistening verdant leaves appeared even more full of vitality after being watered.

“Oh! This small tree has unexpectedly grown so tall?”

Sophia was a little surprised: “Only… Brother Nick, why are you giving your medicine to the small tree? Is it also ill?”

“No. To be honest, it needs this more than I do…” Leylin had a deep expression in his eyes, but did not continue his explanation. Instead, he picked up a small gardening hoe and slowly plowed the soil and removed weeds, just like an earnest gardener.

Sophia appeared very familiar with Leylin’s behaviour, and immediately sat by his side and began to talk to herself:

“Recently, the Calamity of Gluttony has gotten even more serious! Sister Aegnis said many garrison squads have suffered heavy losses, and the frontline reached the Crescent Moon Lakeside for a while, which isn’t far at all from the holy city. There are still lots of giant serpents that have been contaminated, and even rank 6 Serpent families cannot escape. Over half of the Serpent Plains are now occupied by gluttonous beasts…

“The entire Serpent Plains already does not have many places for us to live, and recently even a lot of the holy city residents are beginning to flee, which complicates things for sister Aegnis…

“And sister Belinda, she recently keeps on accepting missions, it’s said that she’s thinking of exchanging it for the highest grade Holy Light Crystal, and to get it she took on a very dangerous mission, and will leave tomorrow…”

“Oh!” Leylin’s hand stopped slightly, but then continued to move. He could understand Belinda’s current situation a little, she seemed to accept the holy city’s missions without stopping, and exchanged her contributions for materials full of life force, then secretly sent them to him.

These things were almost of no use to him, otherwise with Leylin’s methods, he wouldn’t need to keep living in seclusion here.

“The Holy Light Crystal?” Leylin shook his head, this type of life crystal was full of life force, and had good effects on purifying and suppressing various curses, it was said to be the Hail Continent’s peak grade material, and even though Belinda was rank 4, obtaining this was not an easy task.

An even more crucial point was that this material wouldn’t be of much use given his current condition, but it could have an even better effect on the Seed of Wisdom.

*Bang! Bang!* At this moment, a rough sound sounded out. “We’re inspectors!”

“Ah…” Leylin sighed in recognition and came to the door. “Please come in, sirs!”

Seeing a large group of guards boorishly rush in, Sophia stuck out her tongue: “There’s a lot of people. Sophia doesn’t like them. See you, brother Nick!”

The young lady prepared to say goodbye and left, and soon after the guards did the same, fully explaining that they were absolutely not here for inspection, but to serve as a reminder and a warning.

Leylin could only bitterly laugh.

Although in the space of this year, borrowing the Stewart family’s and Thomas’ name saved him a lot of trouble, Sophia was still an enormous problem. Leylin had already felt that as Sofia came to visit him more often, that Thomas had the tendency to become even more impatient.

“Ah… Just how is Belinda managing her sister?” Leylin helplessly massaged his temples.

He had a very bad feeling that if Sophia’s vague affection for him was discovered, the good relationship that he had with Thomas would be gone forever. He’d already failed at shutting her down after several attempts.

He was afraid that his position would go back up in Thomas’ mind, from the tool he was currently to something along the lines of a love rival or competitor.

Chapter 749: Green Leaves

The small courtyard that had been peaceful and quiet for over a year had recently received more and more visits from guards, and that was because of that Thomas’ secretly hostile behaviour.

‘Perhaps he will come and have a showdown with me soon?’ Leylin sighed, ‘This sort of situation is so troublesome, especially at this crucial moment…’

Shortly after, Leylin shut his eyes. ‘In this situation, even if I don’t fight back and make some vows instead, Thomas won’t ever believe me again. After all I’ve done that many times already, and having Sophia pretend is also not desirable. With her intelligence, she’d be found out.

‘Unless, I directly take over her consciousness, but that would demand too much from me… Or I could send her over to Thomas’ bed? No, Belinda would probably go crazy. It’s fine if she does, but if she mobilises Aegnis, that’ll be more troublesome than that moron Thomas…’

In just a moment, Leylin had completely thought over the outcomes from the situation, and discovered that it seemed as if he had no other option apart from running away.

But that would be impossible! After entering the holy city and planting this seed of Wisdom, Leylin had not taken one step out of the courtyard.

After all, the thing that held the power of life or death over him was here, how could he possibly divert his attention to something else? Besides, if he left his camp for too long, with all these hidden rats around, he wasn’t sure he would be able to continue hiding in the holy city.

‘I can’t show weakness… It looks like I can only demonstrate my strength!” Leylin stroked his chin. Sometimes a reasonable show of force could still be put to good use.

However, he would definitely face Thomas’ counter-attack afterwards, but from Leylin’s perspective he only needed a little bit of time for his plan to succeed.

“This period of hesitation, I think it can still be obtained!” Leylin’s eyes flashed.

“Keke…Sophia, wait a moment!” After thinking clearly about his plan, Leylin immediately called out for Sophia.

“Brother Nick, is there anything else?” Sophia jumped and hopped to Leylin, the fragrance of a young lady mixed with the vitality of youth lingering in Leylin’s nose.

Shortly after, the warning gazes from the guards from earlier could be seen.

“Oh! I have something that I need you to give to your sister!” Leylin acted as if he hadn’t seen the warning glares from the guards, and smiled at Sophia.

“What is it? Is it delicious food? The roasted meat that brother Nick made last time tasted good!” Sophia’s eyes lit up.

“It isn’t something to eat, you little glutton!” Leylin shook his head and smiled, he never thought that his cooking skills from his previous world would have fans in a different world, “It’s a protection amulet! Take it to your sister for me! Perhaps it will be of assistance to her in her mission.”

It needn’t be said that a mission where the holy light crystal could be obtained would have a frighteningly high difficulty. Just relying on Belinda, even if she was Rank 4, even if she had support from Aegnis and the Stewart family, it would still be extremely dangerous.

However, in his current situation, it was not suitable for him to go out by himself, so he could only entrust it to Sophia and believe that no matter how naive she was, she would be able to hold on in the face of her own sister being in danger.

“Alright! Sophia will definitely bring her this thing to her!” Sophia clenched her first and nodded her head.

“I believe in you!” Leylin immediately went to the side of the flowerbed and plucked a single leaf from the small emerald-green tree.

“It’s this, help me pass it to your sister!” The dark green leaf had a faint lustre, and Sophia’s eyes lost a little of their spirit.

“I know!” Sophia put away the leaf like it was something precious, and even her eyes seemed a little more quick-witted.

It appeared that coming into contact with the leaf for such a short time had already changed her a little. This was beyond Leylin’s expectations.

“Let’s go! Unless you want to be scolded by Brother Thomas?” Sophia shot a glance at those guards who watched her like a tiger guarding their prey, and immediately walked out aloofly, just like a refined princess.

And these guards looked at each other and hung their heads down in dejection, following behind Sophia like bodyguards protecting their princess.

‘The effect is this good? She merely touched it a little!’ Leylin’s pupils contracted as he looked at the little green tree in the flowerbed.

‘The Wisdom Tree’s branches are so inconceivably formidable. They can provide such great enlightenment and wisdom!’

‘No! Sophia was so diligent in coming here, so perhaps she had been influenced by it. Knowing that this place could bring her great benefits, she did not hesitate to disobey Belinda’s guidance as a result!’ Slowly, Leylin suddenly understood the reason behind Sophia’s determination to visit him, and it seems that her previous goodwill was only a small part of it. To break through her sister’s command, perhaps only the craving for wisdom could do that.

‘This is good, it gives me more confidence in my own plan!’ Leylin secretly clenched his fist.

……

At the same time, next to a street not too far away from the courtyard stood Thomas, with a gloomy expression on his face.

“That slut!” Seeing Sophia leaving Leylin’s courtyard with a brilliant smile, Thomas’ expression grew very dark.

“And that Nick, he actually dared to ignore my warning, and continue to meet Sophia!”

*Bang!* Thomas’ fingers directly left long marks on the nearby wall, and a lot of powder fell from it.

“Get ready to go down there! I want to properly teach that Nick a lesson! It looks like I have been far too lenient to him this year……”

“As you command, Young Master!” the other two appeared to be captains of the garrison, but they respectfully knelt before him.

“Also, carefully investigate his background and strength!” Thomas added.

As a descendent of an influential family, although he was infatuated with Sophia, he couldn’t lose his head over her. After all, he understood restraint before power. As a result, if he was prepared to fall out with Nick, he would first investigate him as much as possible.

However, his influence as the heir of the Stuart family, as long as Leylin wasn’t the top of a small family of descendants, he could easily be crushed like a little ant. Still he would first investigate, just in case.

“An Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline! Even if you are rumoured to be the purest White Devil nobility, I’ll still send you to hell!”

Thomas looked at Leylin’s courtyard, with a cold light flashing in his eyes.

……

“Sister! Sister!” Sophia threw herself into Belinda’s arms and began to act spoilt, but Belinda’s expression was like ice, “Did you go to Nick’s place again? Haven’t I told you many times not to do that, or you will bring him a lot of trouble? Why don’t you ever listen?”

Belinda rarely spoke so strictly.

“But… I wanted to go!” Sophia felt wronged. She twined her fingers as she said, “I feel comfortable and very happy in Brother Nick’s place.”

“Oh? What did he do to you?” Belinda’s expression suddenly grew alert, even her finger joints began to crack.

“It’s not like that! It’s the small tree, just smelling it makes me feel good!” Sophia’s face flushed red.

“Nick’s darling tree?” Belinda shook her head, and felt that she had thought too much.

Belinda could not understand why Nick treated that tree like a precious treasure, and because of it she had consulted many resources and almost considered the Seed of Wisdom as some demonic thing that could bewitch a person’s heart.

She felt somewhat dissatisfied by his continuous attention to the tree, without even a care for himself.

“Mm! Also, Brother Nick let me give this to you, and said it would be very useful to Sister’s mission!” Sophia’s expression seemed a little reluctant, but she still gave the leaf to Belinda.

“What is this? Is it a calming amulet?” When the leaf touched her palm, Belinda did not feel any powerful sensation, only a slight chill from the leaf helping her mood to calm down a lot.

“It’s just some calming amulet? It doesn’t seem to be of much use! Why did he give this to me?” Belinda’s eyes seemed puzzled.

“No! Sophia feels that this leaf will be very useful to Sister, so you must bring it!” Sophia nevertheless had an imposing expression on her face.

“Alright, alright! I really can’t deal with the both of you…” Belinda’s face was brimming with a warm smile, she put away the leaf safely and stroked Sophia’s head, then her expression changed: “This is wrong!”

She looked Sophia up and down and stared at her sister without pause, “Sophia, why do I feel like you’ve gotten smarter…”

Due to an accident in her childhood, Sophia’s intelligence was like a child’s, but today her speech was very orderly, which was a ceaseless surprise to Belinda.

“Have I? I’ve always been very smart, it must be that sister has gotten it wrong!” Sophia smiled sweetly, but a crafty light flashed in the depths of her eyes.

“What? Perhaps the stress of tomorrow’s mission is too much! Has it driven me insane?” Belinda touched her own forehead.

“Belinda!” At this moment, another figure charged towards her, with an expression of unconcealed rage.

“Why did you take that mission? Don’t you know that the Crescent Lake has already become a dangerous area of gluttonous beasts?” Aegnis asked. The armour on her body hadn’t even been removed, and was still stained with blood… As the leader in charge, Aegnis spent almost every day active on the battlefield with the gluttonous beasts.

“I’ll leave first!” Seeing this situation, Sophia stuck out her tongue and slipped out of the door at lightning speed.

Chapter 750: Crescent Lake

“What mission are you talking about?” Belinda said, with a blank look on her face.

“You’re still trying to deceive me?” Aegnis’ voice rose an octave higher, “Don’t forget that as the leader of the holy city’s garrison, I have jurisdiction over both the adventurer and mercenary guilds!”

“The Crescent Lake Acquisition mission is extremely difficult, and has a Rank 5 danger level! Even those who are Rank 5 will have to face certain dangers, and you think you can do it?”

Aegnis bitterly exhorted her: “If you’re doing this for that holy light crystal, then just leave it to me!”

“Thank you Aegnis, but I have my own reasons……”

Belinda forced a smile on her face.

“I know, is it because of Nick? Even though you haven’t gone to find him for over a year, I know all about how you ask Sofia to bring things to him.”

“Is it because of him that you aren’t willing to accept me?” Aegnis’ said in a dark voice.

“It’s not what you think it is!” Belinda didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry.

“It’s exactly because of him! That bastard, sooner or later…” Aegnis slammed her fists together fiercely.

“Aegnis!”

“I only consider you my good friend. I’m giving you a final warning, if anything happens to Nick, you’ll definitely regret it!” Belinda’s expression grew darker.

“For him… You’re acting like this for a filthy man! You dare to actually argue with me?”

Aegnis emanated a terrifyingly powerful aura, and many shadows converged at her back to become the likeness of a three-headed python.

“Precisely!”

Even under the innate oppression of her race, Belinda still staunchly looked Aegnis in the eye.

Seeing Belinda acting this way, Aegnis’ chest heaved violently. “As you wish!” she panted out vulgarly.

The sound of armour dropping to the floor rang out, followed by the distant footsteps of Aegnis as she left.

Once she had left the villa, Aegnis’ expression grew completely dark.

“Bang!” A snake whip slashed out suddenly, and many rose petals and tulip petals flew into the sky.

“Nick!” Aegnis ground her teeth in frustration, but it soon became a cold laugh.

“I promised Belinda not to harm him, but Thomas hasn’t agreed. However, shall I go about this a little more secretly?”

……

“It should be here!”

Belinda looked at the map in her hand and appeared to be very cautious.

Currently, she was in a wasteland which had an aura of death and decay, which made her unconsciously become nervous.

Ever since the Calamity of Gluttony broke out, the entire Serpentes Plains was not how it used to be.

War, hand-to-hand combat and gluttony spread with incredible speed, leaving the plains covered in blood.

Even the Snake Dowager’s radiance could not move those savage gluttonous beasts, because they were also protected by an Exemplary.

The Sovereign King of Gluttony– Beelzebub. Although it had not been 2 years since Beelzebub’s descent into Purgatory World, his name was known by everyone. It was to the extent where it could immediately make little snake children cry.

In this situation, because of the gluttonous beasts’ terrifying consumption, food shortages had broken out in the holy city. In the past, this would have been an absolute joke, but now it was something that had really happened.

In fact, the gluttonous beasts were facing the same food shortages, which were even more serious for them than the snake people. They were already at the stage where they were killing each other for food, otherwise they would have already invaded the holy city.

It was different from previous calamities. Belinda had a feeling that once the gluttonous beasts had occupied a territory under the Sovereign King of Gluttony’s command, it wouldn’t easily be relinquished ever again.

The Snake Dowager’s large-scale purification that had happened in the beginning could never happen again.

When she thought of this, a fog immediately shrouded Belinda’s mind.

“Once I pass through here, I will be very close to the Crescent Lake!”

Belinda muttered to herself, although she had disguised herself, she felt very unsafe in this sort of place.

“If Becker and the others had come, perhaps I would be able to relax more easily. It’s a shame……”

Belinda smiled bitterly. In her career as a mercenary, she had gained a few subordinates and the like, but once they heard that she had taken on this mission, they had rejected her one after another.

If Belinda had just a little more time and used her own methods, it would be effortless to unite some powerful and loyal subordinates. But just a year wasn’t even enough to bind them to her through familiarity, and certainly wasn’t enough to persuade them to take risks with her.

“However, my mission this time is just to collect blue quartz within the Crescent Lake. If I don’t disturb those gluttonous beasts, the danger should be quite low!”

Belinda pondered over this in silence, and soon passed through the plains.

Past the sloping fields, the scene ahead was reflected in her eyes– a blue lake shaped like a crescent extended across the plains as far as the eye could see.

A sparkling radiance and a hint of chilliness was emitted from the Crescent Lake.

“This was once the holy city’s valued resource point, but after falling to the gluttonous beasts, it has already grown wild. If the holy city wasn’t so short of resources with they urgently need to replenish, perhaps they wouldn’t have put such a high price on this mission…”

Belinda bit her lip in distress.

With Aegnis there, she simply did not need to come out and take risks. If she was willing to forget her pride and plead with Aegnis, a piece of Holy Light Crystal would easily fall into her hands.

However, Belinda did not want to owe her so much and moreover, she was not willing to give up her dignity to do this.

Because of this, Belinda had not hesitated to risk her life to do this mission.

“If only the gluttonous beasts weren’t here, then I would have more of a chance,” Belinda’s eyes lit up. A tattoo of a white eyeball appeared and flew up to a high altitude, and images of the scene were transmitted to her.

“Roar…” “Hiss…”

It was unlucky that there were several gluttonous beasts lingering next to the Crescent Lake, tearing apart the corpse of a giant serpent.

Powerful undulations that were on par with a Rank 5 were emitted from a gluttonous beast that was the size of a small mountain

“Oh damn it! My luck is awful today!’ Belinda cursed silently.

Through the surveillance eyeball, Belinda had already received images of the scene which were transmitted directly into her consciousness. Amongst those gluttonous beasts, one was a giant serpent with many tentacles that had been split open from head to foot. There was also a giant rat with two heads, one bigger than the other, which gnawed its food at lightning speed.

The final beast appeared to be the corpses of different animals stitched together into a giant ball of meat, with a giant crack in its centre. A red tongue licked its white teeth incessantly, and it gave off the strongest undulations. It seemed to have reached the peak of Rank 5.

The corpse of the giant serpent on the floor was clearly also Rank 5, but it was definitely not a match for these three gluttonous beasts and had become their food.

“What a pity……” Belinda tightly clenched her fists.

That Rank 5 giant serpent was clearly a giant serpent descendent of the Thousand Snake Plains, but it couldn’t escape from its fate and became prey.

Although the Snake Dowager and the holy city had done their utmost to rescue and evacuate the giant serpents, the Thousand Snake Plains were too vast, and these unlucky ones often surfaced.

Although Belinda was furious, she was rational enough to not rush out hot-headedly and die.

“Gluttonous beasts have to eat very frequently, so sooner or later they will leave after they finish eating here…”

Belinda very patiently waited and hid herself.

These gluttonous beasts had astonishing military power and a frightening ability to consume, but their intelligence and detection were rather weak. This gave her a chance.

“Click! Click!”

These three gluttonous beasts ate very quickly, and not even the bones were spared. Even the drops of blood on the floor were greedily lapped up until there was nothing left– The blood of a Rank 5 giant serpent was full of nutritious energy, and one drop of it was said to be better than eating ten low-ranked beasts.

When food is short, the gluttonous beasts probably massacre each other! In that case…”

Belinda’s eyes lit up a little as if she was a lone cheetah, waiting for the opportunity.

“Roar…” “Hiss…” “Coo! Coo!”

After eating the prey they had caught together, the three gluttonous beasts sized each other up and let out a huge roar which shook the void.

After obviously testing each other, the sewed-up monster and the tentacle snake left one after the other in opposite directions.

The gluttonous beasts digested things quickly, so they almost had no time to rest. They had to spend the rest of their lives fighting and hunting for food.

The two-headed rat that was left seemed thirsty. Leaning against the Crescent Lake, the two rat heads began to drink up the water in the lake. The surface of the lake seemed to drop in volume continuously, exposing the dried up lakebed.

Within the lakebed, small blue rays of light began to flicker.

It was a blue ore that looked very bright under the rays of light.

“Blue quartz!” After seeing the goal of her mission, Belinda grew very excited.

However, the actions of that two rats made Belinda feel endless frustration.

After the two-headed giant rat had drunk its fill from the lake, it unexpectedly lay next to the lake and sunk into a deep sleep.

The rat’s body emitted traces of black gas to its surroundings, and it breathed it in again. In this process, its body grew even more enormous, with a sarcoma growing on its neck. Its aura grew even more powerful, and was approaching the peak of Rank 5.

“Damn! I’ve unexpectedly run into an evolving gluttonous beast!”

Belinda’s expression grew exceptionally unsightly. gluttonous beasts rarely rested, one exception was when they absorbed too much energy and started to evolve!

After their deep sleep, the power of gluttonous beasts would undergo an earth-shattering transformation!

Chapter 752: Successful Growth

*Chik! Chik!* The large two-headed mouse bellowed, a pair of sharp claws being enveloped by yellow light. A huge wound was torn open on Benny’s ches, but for the Ent who didn’t have any weak points or even flesh and blood, there was naturally nothing like a scene of blood spurting out.

On the contrary, there was no pain on Benny’s face. Instead, a green circle of light was emitted from his chest and it began to heal immediately. Even the giant claws were caught inside, inducing the large rat’s fury.

“Bind!” Green leaved vines were like the most terrifying of law-shackles, extending from Benny’s arm and twining around the giant rat.

‘Powerful regeneration abilities and such physical strength… Could this be the Primordial Ent rumoured to be from ancient times?’ Belinda watched the two monsters fighting and gritted her teeth, making use of this hard-to-come-by chance and beginning to flee. Meanwhile, the mysterious feelings she had for Leylin grew even stronger…

*Rumble! Rumble!* Terrifying earthquakes wreaked havoc near the crescent lake, causing dust to fly everywhere. Two huge figures could vaguely be seen in battle. Wooden arms or vines were sent flying on occasion, and this would be accompanied by a terrifying crunch.

The Ent was evidently not a match for the giant mouse, but due to its characteristics it could buy a lot of time for Belinda to escape. By the time the giant mouse achieved victory, it could only roar in fury at the pile of wood shavings.

Someone else was spying on the battlefield from the darkness.

“This darned old mouse. Get an entire brigade over here for me. I want it dead!” Aegnis glared at the giant two headed rat hatefully, her eyes showing her wrath. The few soldiers behind her could only agree meekly.

‘Thankfully, Belinda’s fine.’ Aegnis patted her chest, a pondering look in her eyes. She was obviously worried about Belinda going on a solo mission and had followed her secretly. If not for the appearance of the Ent, she probably wouldn’t have been able to keep from acting herself.

‘Nick seems rather interesting! Are otherworldly summoning techniques his trump card?’ While sacrifices and beast spirits were the norm in the Purgatory World, there were also other paths to power. Even Magi existed here, hence Leylin’s summoned Ent didn’t surprise Aegnis too much. At most, she would think he’d inherited some relatively obscure abilities.

‘But this Ent that he so casually summoned has the power to hinder a rank 5 gluttonous beast for a while…’ Aegnis stroked her chin, ‘I should warn Thomas and get him to stop his plans for now. I should look up Nick’s history, he might be someone who’ll give us a huge surprise.’

However, Aegnis had no idea that when Leylin’s true identity was revealed, she wouldn’t be surprised, but horrified.

“Yes, ma’am!” one of the guards immediately bowed and withdrew.

“Next up, it’s you, you disgusting old mouse. How dare you harm my adorable Belinda? I’m going to tear your bones apart and use your brain juices as gravy!” A vast and horrifying three-headed snake appeared abruptly in tandem with her announcement, pouncing towards the giant two headed rat.

The rest of the soldiers exchanged glances. In the end, despite their unwillingness, they could only follow their leader and charge forward as well. A massive battle was about to ensue…

Aegnis had grown slightly fearful after Leylin revealed that tiny bit of his strength. Thomas’ plan for revenge had been put on hold, which gave him valuable time.

However, battles generally grew more intense, and things had almost gotten desperate.

In order to contain the wave of gluttonous beasts, the holy city had already arranged campaigns against them several times. Even the Snake Dowager herself had sent out a clone, but in the face of Beelzebub’s huge army of gluttonous beasts, they yielded tiny results. Several of her clones were even destroyed. The bloody loss of life caused the holy city to be in an extremely unstable situation.

A few months later, after several attempts to meet the beast wave, the battle line was pushed to the edges of the holy city. The city walls, and the triumphal arch that used to be filled with holy light, had now turned into the last line of defence for the snake beings.

Furthermore, compared to the spread of gluttony itself, the Gluttonous Army had Beezlebub himself in charge. Even the Snake Dowager would not be able to deal with them easily.

It could be said that the holy city was now in a desperate state of emergency and on the brink of life or death.

There were many residents within the holy city, and they would often hear the roars of the gluttonous beasts as they slumbered. They had no choice but to contribute and help with the holy city’s defences.

“I’ve told you many times already! This is property of the Stewart Family, and I am a guest of Young Master Thomas. Unless you get his consent, you have no right to look through anything here. Scram!” Leylin sent a group of patrolling officers away sternly.

Even while using the name of the Stewarts, Leylin had no choice but to take the risk to use a mental hint, and only then did the patrolling officers leave obediently.

After sending them away, Leylin laughed wryly. “Is it already the fourth time this month? Each time they seem to be even more urgent. Looks like rumours of the gluttonous beasts being on the verge of breaching the holy city have spread widely…”

He then came to the flowerbed. The little green tree had already grown quite tall and was completely emerald green, like a flawless work of art.

Even with concealing spell formations, this strange scene had attracted some attention from others. If not for Leylin spending most of his time close to it, perhaps there would be someone brazen enough to come in and steal it.

“The ‘holy light crystal’ that Belinda sent over seems to have a good effect on the Wisdom Tree! Cough cough…” Leylin sized up the little green Wisdom Tree, looking quite satisfied. Even while he was coughing, the hope in his heart grew.

‘I had to courteously bow to Thomas in the past, hiding my true strength for later. It’s given me two years, which was just enough for this stump to successfully grow. Destiny is on my side!’ Leylin’s eyes burned with passion.

Ever since he found out that holy light crystals were beneficial for the little Wisdom Tree, he had secretly acted and committed a few alarming crimes, gathering large amounts of crystals and bringing the growth of the Wisdom Tree forward.

Leylin had always acted with caution and did not leave any traces behind. Since they were at war, their intent to hunt down criminals was weaker than usual. With this as a cover, he had been able to hoodwink them easily.

After all, who would suspect an old geezer on the verge of death?

Yes, in two years the Allsnake Curse had practically extracted all of Leylin’s life force. Even with facial transfiguration techniques, many wrinkles still appeared on his forehead and palms.

“A.I. Chip, how much longer do I have?” Leylin inwardly asked.

[Beep! Gathering data on Host’s life force… Establishing conjecture model! … Experiment completed. Estimated time till death: 34 days 12 hours 23 minutes 32 seconds.]

The A.I. Chip intoned faithfully.

“A little more than a month? It’s shorter than I expected. Is it because I helped out the last time? Cough cough…” Leylin began to cough hard again, his handkerchief covered in scarlet blood.

“The rejection is also becoming more and more serious,” Leylin smiled wryly and threw the blood-stained handkerchief aside.

He was now already at his very weakest.

The frightening part of the Allsnake Curse was that it was essentially fatal for all of the descendants and Warlocks who made use of the Dowager’s serpent bloodlines. It was already an incredible thing that Leylin had managed to hold on for so long.

*Roar!* *Awoo!* *Rumble!* *Clatter!* Load roars, multi-coloured flames and the cries of many snake beings could be seen and heard. The ground shook underneath them all continuously. This was another attack from the gluttonous beast wave outside towards the holy city.

The Snake Dowager and Beelzebub had yet to act, and seemed to have come to some tacit agreement, handing down the responsibility of victory to their subordinates. Thus, these attacks happened a few times everyday, resulting in many sacrifices and refugees.

With the protection and the support they believed he had, many neighbours came to Leylin and prayed for help. Leylin ruthlessly rejected all of them.

“No!” “I don’t want Daddy to go!” “Please, don’t send me to the battlefield! I don’t want to die!” Noise could be heard from the streets, and the moans and cries of wretched souls travelled into Leylin’s ears.

“How chaotic.” Leylin shook his head and returned to his deckchair, narrowing his eyes as if taking a nap.

“Grandpa Nick, we’ve come to visit!”

*Bang!* The door was pushed open, and Sophia as well as Belinda walked in. In Sophia’s eyes was an unconcealed sense of sorrow. From his life aura undulations, Leylin did not have long left. Even Belinda no longer had any reservations and came to visit him often.

“Hey, you’re here!” Leylin’s smile was like that of a lonely old geezer, kind and friendly as he watched little children dropping in, “I’ve just made some tea!”

The dilapidated courtyard was the same as before, just that beside the green tree Leylin had made a round table and deck chair, not leaving the area at all. On the wooden round table was a porcelain teapot that was emitting steam.

“Come and try my new brew!” Leylin was very friendly and made a cup of green tea for Belinda and Sophia.

“Oh, it’s very fragrant!” While holding the teacup, Sophia looked extremely content.

Chapter 753: Imminent Crisis

“Sophia seems to be recovering well, she doesn’t need to come here anymore!” Leylin reclined on the deck chair and spoke leisurely.

“Mm, thank you very much!” Belinda’s eyes seemed to become a little emotional. For some reason, ever since Sophia began drinking the mysterious ‘tea’ Leylin made from his little green tree, her condition had greatly improved. She had become much more mature and intelligent.

“By the way, what is this ‘tea’? Is it some sort of medicine?” Belinda was puzzled, but at the same time was filled with gratitude towards Leylin. She naively believed that Leylin had grown the tree in order to treat Sophia, and Leylin obviously would not uncover this beautiful misunderstanding.

“Oh! It’s just the name of a drink from my hometown. It’s made from plants, where the essence of leaves is extracted through liquid. It is rather similar to this drink,” Leylin obviously did not want to elaborate.

“Is it the culture of some overseas isle? I really hope I can travel there with you one day…” Belinda’s eyes seemed to be luminous and sparkling.

“Mm, there will be chances!” Leylin yawned, not seeming to be in good spirits.

“Alright, Sophia. What stories have you brought for your Grandpa Nick?” He turned to Sophia. She had already drained the tea.

“Oh! I heard from sister Aegnis that the holy city is preparing for a huge counterattack. Even the disciplinary corps will be moved…”

“Also… The entire holy city is now under a strict curfew. There are even plans to gather all the residents and manage them all together.”

……

“Thomas is really incredibly stupid! If I just throw a random tantrum, he’ll divulge all the sensitive information he knows. Isn’t Sofia amazing?” Sophia raised her head arrogantly with a crafty glint in her eyes.

“Yes, Sophia is the best!” Leylin nodded slightly in praise. He had gained a lot of information about every corner of the holy city from her daily accounts. However, the more she spoke, the more his head began to droop, until his eyes finally shut as he sank into a deep sleep.

Sophia immediately stopped speaking when she noticed this, and her eyes reddened with emotion.

“Let’s go,” Belinda’s voice trembled as she draped a fur coat over Leylin. She then led Sophia away. They were very busy everyday, and their free time was limited. Perhaps it was also because they were unwilling to see Leylin in this state.

However, after they had left, Leylin’s eyes sprang open brightly and animatedly, “So it’s already come to this? It seems like the big decisive battle is approaching soon, it’s about time to start my plans.”

“Meanwhile… I’ll take care of a few little rats,” Leylin’s eyes slanted to the side, as if he could see through the wall to watch another place far away.

After that he closed his eyes, and like a tired old man sank into a deep sleep.

……

*Clatter!* A valuable crystal bottle fell to the ground, shattering into fragments.

“At a time like this, as a noble of the Stewart Family, even I have an obligation to fight on the battlefield, and yet he stays there doing nothing. I have no idea what sister is thinking!” Thomas huffed. The armour he wore was covered with bloodstains.

“Young Master Thomas, our Stewart family has been part of the garrison over generations in the holy city. Protecting the holy city has always been our duty! As for that man, he is just a free resident…” The white-haired middle-aged butler advised. He had completely lost one eye, and there was only a deep hole left there.

“Furthermore, my Lady seems to have discovered that he he is hiding some trump card and ordered us not to offend him. I believe that with the Madam’s foresight, she won’t be wrong!”

“But… I can’t take it! And then there’s those two bitches… It’s not just Sophia but even Belinda goes over to visit him so regularly. What do they take the Stewart Family for?” Thomas yelled, and the butler could only sigh.

They were clearly free residents, and Belinda had even taken the initiative to help out with the guarding of the holy city. She was merely taking some time to visit her friend, and there was no reason to get mad over that. Of course, this good-for-nothing young master wouldn’t listen anyway.

“I can’t take it! I can’t take it anymore! Mumbas, find a way to make Nick disappear forever! It should be easy since it’s wartime!” Thomas’ expression turned dark, bloodlust evident in his eyes.

“Yes, honourable young master! Your will is our command! However, the second elder is now preparing to lead the counterattack of the disciplinary corps. Please be patient…” The old butler bowed a full ninety degrees.

“I know, I know! This damned situation!” Thomas groaned in annoyance but did not retort further, allowing the old butler to heave a sigh of relief. What he did not realise was that the bloodlust in the depth of Thomas’ eyes did not fade. It instead grew more forceful…

Night had fallen. Aegnis was wearing her crystal armour as she stood on the walls of the holy city. Her line of sight extended past the triumphal arch, fixed on the dense army of gluttonous beasts outside.

They had already been contaminated by the law of gluttony, and it was difficult to make out what their original bodies looked like. The only similarities they shared were their terrifying and powerful energy undulations, as well as their desire for food. Aegnis shivered in fear at this sight.

Days were short in the Purgatory World, which was why many beasts were more active at night. These gluttonous beasts rarely rested, and when their physical strength declined they would feed on their own kind that had died in previous sieges, which was why they seemed even more full of vigour than ever. What this meant was that their appearance was even more frightening at night than during the day.

Watching this uproar at the frontlines by the nearby beasts, the experienced Aegnis knew this was a signal for them to attack.

She abruptly turned to watch the soldiers on the city walls with her. They were mostly the troops that the Stewart Family were in charge of. Some of them were volunteers, and some were labourers who were forcefully conscripted.

Aegnis took a deep breath, her voice spreading through the frontlines. “Mighty Matriarch! My blood brothers, can we allow those filthy and despicable beasts to set foot in the holy city and pollute the glory of our dignitary, the holy mother?”

“No!” “No!” “No!” The residents in the holy city were now so loyal that they were ready to die for the Snake Dowager, and they naturally howled loudly in denial.

“Very good. Tear them apart for me, our holy city must be victorious!” Aegnis brandished the nine-tiered whip in her hands that had a snake head, thundering.

“To Victory! “To Victory!” “Long Live Stewart!” “Long Live Stewart!” Many soldiers shouted loudly, the atmosphere heated to the extreme.

Seeing that she had taken care of the soldiers’ morale, Aegnis sighed in relief and retreated from the city gates.

“You did very well, Aegnis!” Belinda walked over in martial attire.

“Is that so? I feel that it’s far from enough though,” Aegnis smiled wryly and draped an arm around Belinda’s shoulders, “How are the second elder and the disciplinary corps?”

“Preparations are complete. We are prepared for battle anytime!” Belinda did not struggle against her and sounded calm, “If all goes well and this operation is a success, we can probably push the battle line close to the Crescent Lake…”

“Hah… if it goes smoothly?”

Aegnis chuckled, pressing her lips close to Belinda’s ears, and spoke to her in a low voice, “Belinda, leave! Take Sophia and maybe even Nick. Leave this place; go as far as you can!”

“Why?” Belinda was stunned, Aegnis’ warm breath tickling her ears as they flushed red, “Do you have no faith in the holy city?”

“If my enemy is an army from another dignitary, I wouldn’t be afraid even if they surrounded us, but…” Aegnis shook her head, “You know how the gluttonous beasts work. Belinda, what’s most terrifying isn’t their strength but that they are infectious! 14 of our own family have been infected by the power of gluttony in battle. In order to prevent the infection from spreading, we had no choice but to obliterate them.”

“So that’s what happened!” Belinda’s eyes widened, extremely shocked.

“If that damned Sovereign King of Gluttony isn’t eliminated, there will never be a victory over those gluttonous beasts. Do you get it now?” Aegnis coquettishly lifted Belinda’s chin.

“Then come with me!” Belinda gritted her teeth. After all, she had treated Belinda and Sophie quite well, and Belinda wasn’t willing to watch her die here.

“Hehe… you can all leave, but I can’t.” Aegnis laughed, though this gave a bad feeling.

“For your family?” Belinda’s expression was complicated.

“Yes. Our Stewart Family has been protecting the holy city generation after generation. As the next in line, how can I leave now?”

Aegnis pushed Belinda while laughing maniacally, “Go! Pursue your freedom!”

“This is giving me an ominous feeling!” Belinda’s eyes reddened, on the verge of tears. So many things had happened recently, and even this strong girl could not really endure it.

‘Mighty Matriarch, please show mercy and save us all!’ Belinda looked towards the statue erected at the heart of the holy city and could not help but kneel piously, making a silent prayer.

The mighty statue watched everything expressionlessly, as if it had seen through everything with a slight smile. It seemed like everything was guided by her hand, but nothing really changed. The wind blew, and Belinda felt a chill come on, a sense of terror rising within her.

Chapter 755: Another Clash

The disciplinary corps was the most elite squadron in the entire holy city. Every snakeman there was a blood descendant of the Stewart family, and possessed strength at least at Morning Star. The leader of the disciplinary corps was the Stewart family’s esteemed second elder, who had no faults as a commander.

If these troops were appropriately deployed, they could indeed reclaim the perilous situation they faced, and would at least bring the battlefront to the same level.

However, Aegnis felt a fluttering feeling lingering in her chest.

“What’s happening?” She climbed onto the tower and immediately saw the disciplinary corps. Compared to the last few times she had seen then, the disciplinary guards had an even more tyrannical aura around them, and Aegnis could not help but breathe a sigh of relief.

“The preparations for the guardian technique have been completed!”

“Activate the technique, and initiate activation of the holy city protection matrix!”

“Rank 2 Alchemy Cannon is ready, and can fire at any time!”

Commands were continuously issued, and a spell formation that permitted free movement into the holy city was engraved onto the disciplinary corps’ armour.

“Attack!” At the heart of the guards’ square formation, where a large golden flag waved in the wind, a gentle but firm voice rang out.

“Disciplinary corps, move out!” Standing at the very front was a white-haired elder shouting, an explosive aura at rank 6 undulating from him.

‘No, this is wrong!’ Aegnis finally realised that something wasn’t right. All of a sudden, her eyes widened and even her voice became shrill, “Second uncle’s aura, how could he have suddenly grown so strong? Even if he used forbidden magic it wouldn’t be possible, unless…”

Aegnis suddenly roared out, “Be careful!”

However, it was too late.

“Disciplinary force, with me!” The numerous soldiers of the disciplinary corps roared. Their bodies secretly swelled, and ghastly demonic energy erupted from them in an instant.

With a loud rumble, many spells were fired out, and the power of the guards were concentrated into one force, merging together in the second elder’s hands.

“Thunder of discipline!” The second elder cried in a frenzy, and a massively destructive attack landed straight on the city gate. Several deafening crashes could be heard, and black lightning swept across the area with a blazing radiance.

The guards on the city gate were vaporised in an instant, burnt to ashes. Then, they were obliterated right down to the atomic level. Soon after, the holy city’s entrance was also destroyed by the spell, and many protective runes began to fall apart completely.

“No, not this!” Aegnis held her head as tears began to subconsciously flow from her eyes.

The holy city’s defensive techniques were extremely powerful, with even laws being inscribed in the arrays. Even the disciplinary corps would have found it difficult to take it down in one strike; it was the method they were most confident in for obstructing the gluttonous beasts.

Now, however, the disciplinary corps had the defensive array’s approval, and it was destroyed from within. Immediately, the holy city had lost its greatest defense.

It wasn’t just that. The ones who had suffered the most under the earlier attack were the elites of the Stewart Family, Aegnis’ clansmen! Even her father, the patriarch of the Stewart family, was there.

“In the name of gluttony, kill!” The traitorous second elder began to laugh wildly. His body exploded into a gruesome three-headed python, with deeply twisted blood vessels rooted in its irregular scales. It looked inconceivably horrifying.

Afterwards, the turncoat disciplinary corps immediately began to attack the stunned allies around them. Blood-curdling screeches could immediately be heard as the carnage began.

“Why? Why?” Aegnis rushed in front of her uncle. She was lucky that the area she was responsible for wasn’t the most important section, and it had suffered fewer losses. However, the most important defensive array had now been destroyed. The battle now had lost all its meaning and suspense.

“Why, second elder? Why did you betray our guardian family’s honor?” Aegnis’ eyes were full of tears, and she was still in disbelief.

“Why?” The three headed python’s slit eyes were full of ridicule and madness.

“The guardian family?” he chuckled, “Do you rejoice in being the Matriarch’s guard dog? With our bloodline shackles and chains, unable for all eternity to break through our roles as gatekeepers… I have had enough!”

The three-headed python hissed menacingly, and the snakemen who couldn’t escape in time were swallowed up. Its blood vessels incessantly circulated blood-red energy throughout its body, making the python grow even more demonic and enormous. It even appeared to reach the peak of rank 6, sprinting towards rank 7.

“This is true power, how amazing!” The three-headed python had an intoxicated expression in its slit eyes.

“Gluttony, the power of gluttony! So you’ve been contaminated by the Sovereign King of Gluttony?” Aegnis felt slightly relieved. If her uncle was being manipulated, then it would make her feel a little better.

“Contaminated? No, I asked for this! This is the only way I could become strong. And it wasn’t just me, every single guard of the disciplinary corps chose this.” As the second elder spoke, the disciplinary corps’ guards all laughed wildly and transformed into giant serpents. They too had grotesque appearances, and had clearly been contaminated by the power of gluttony.

“Aegnis, retreat! He has gone completely mad!” With a giant crash, the ruins of the city gate exploded, and the figure of an elegant three-headed python emerged. The scales on its body had begun to come loose, and it had severe injuries.

“Father!” Aegnis cried in surprise.

“Teehee! My beloved brother! You haven’t died yet?” The second elder laughed.

“Demon who actively sought the power of gluttony, you are no longer a clansman of our family. I want to correct our family’s mistake!” The three headed python charged immediately at the second elder.

At the same time, a tremendous force flung Aegnis far away and called to her, “Leave immediately!”

“Teehee! Elder brother, now I will prove that I have always been better than you, and better-suited to lead our family!” The three-headed python that had been transformed by gluttony aggressively tangled with the patriarch.

The rank 6 beast’s bloody crushing ability had instantly created a blank space and isolated area. Whether it was guard or gluttonous beast, all who approached it were shocked to death.

Deafening roars filled the air as many gluttonous beasts immediately poured through the gap into the holy city. The surviving guards entered bloody close-quarters combat.

Aegnis’ face was filled with tears, and in the end she could only faintly see the tremendous smoke that filled the air as her father’s powerless body fell, accompanied by the second elder’s mad laughter.

……

The sounds of explosions filled the air. As gluttonous beasts devastated the holy city, the giant statue of the Snake Dowager at the center began to emit dazzling light, as if she had heard the innermost prayers of her citizens.

In this layer of light, the entire holy city seemed to experience an enormous earthquake and many deep cracks began to appear in the ground.

Many buildings in the holy city began to twist and collapse with loud crashes, as if the heavens were torn and the earth had been split asunder. The giant statue of the Snake Dowager began to sink down without stopping. Finally, an immensely deep hole appeared in the ground.

“The power of gluttony, and the concealing power of chaos! Beelzebub, have you joined hands with the Nefarious Filthbird?” A coiled ball of snakes floated up from the depths of the hole like a star. Many giant snake heads uncoiled, exposing the Snake Dowager’s puzzled face.

Overwhelmingly powerful undulations spread out at rank 8, and the entire holy city grew quiet in an instant. Many gluttonous beasts were engulfed by the shadow and burnt to ashes.

At the holy city’s most critical moment, the Snake Dowager finally appeared!

“The Matriarch!” “Almighty dignitary!” “Invincible ancestor!”

The surviving inhabitants of the holy city immediately knelt down, and tears of joy began to overflow from their eyes. The one who had just appeared wasn’t a phantom image or a clone from sacrifices; it was the real body of the Snake Dowager!

Every scale on the Matriarch’s body had the most realistic feeling of true flesh, and even exhibited the aura of laws. Just the aura that emanated from her body gave innumerable benefits to her descendants.

“Dowager! It was you who first violated our agreement, and began to meddle with my affairs!” Accompanied by wild laughter, a demonic python emerged from the gluttonous beast army outside the holy city.

No, calling it a giant python would be inaccurate, as it had only the body of a python. However, it had grown a pair of extraordinary demonic wings, and its purplish-brown muscled arms had sharp talons at the end of its legs. It had many compound eyes just like an insect.

It looked as if Beelzebub had fused his soul with a mixed-breed snakeman’s body, whose power had reached the limit. It could even meet the Snake Dowager as an equal.

After seeing Beelzebub’s form, the Snake Dowager’s eyes flashed with amazement.

“Haha! This body’s raw material appears to be your descendent, but my gluttonous power has made it even more perfect than before. That’s all thanks to a gift from a certain little fellow,” Beelzebub split open his huge mouth, a purple-black barbed tongue licking his sharp white teeth and said, “In return, I’ll swallow him up later and let him forever be part of the almighty Beelzebub…”

The impulsive power of gluttony and the omnipresent power of shadows began their confrontation with the holy city’s walls as its boundary. In a moment, many guards and gluttonous beasts turned into ashes.

For two rank 8 existences to cross swords, it could be said that this bout decided the Purgatory World’s future to an extent. Many powerful conscients descended here, and the faint chirps of the Nefarious Bird and traces of the Trial’s Eye’s power appeared.

“That crafty little fellow, I didn’t think that he would bring me this much trouble!” The Snake Dowager’s eyes became a little dispirited, and she looked directly into an area within the holy city.

Chapter 758: Halfway to Rank 7

“Your Wings of Gluttony will belong to me!” Along with Leylin’s announcement and Beelzebub’s miserable cries, the monstrously dark wings were forcefully torn off, splattering blood everywhere.

*Hss—* The phantom Kemoyin Emperor behind Leylin opened its mouth wide, and it seemed like there was a black hole at its depths. It immediately devoured the entirety of the devil’s fleshy wings.

*Pila! Pila!* Two lumps of flesh surfaced on the snake’s back. It then spread out a tremendous pair of fleshy wings that looked similar to Beelzebub’s own.

“The law of gluttony…” Leylin sounded rather bewitched by them, “Combined with my own abilities, what kind of result will there be?”

The terrifying black hole wreaked complete havoc, devouring Beelzebub’s entire body. In front of the Kemoyin Emperor’s innate skill of control, the devil’s mortal body which had been created with the Black Horrall Snake as its source material was suppressed to a huge degree. Beelzebub’s body gradually disappeared as the Kemoyin Emperor devoured it.

The Kemoyin Emperor easily digested the power of gluttony that came from the source body of the Black Horrall Snake. A comprehension of the power of gluttony combined with Beelzebub’s memories as it surfaced in Leylin’s sea of consciousness, surging towards Leylin’s truesoul barriers like a raging tide.

“Keke… I am the true master of the law of gluttony, its contamination isn’t something the likes of you can resolve. Thank you very much, this body is great!” A barely visible shadow appeared above the Kemoyin Emperor, and Beelzebub’s voice sounded from within the blazing demonic flames.

Under his influence, the Kemoyin Emperor quickly digested that large bundle of energy. Even as it evolved, Leylin’s own will was being eroded.

Beelzebub had completely comprehended the law of gluttony, and to steal this power Leylin would first have to face the retaliation of his conscient. It released a large amount of power that mixed with the laws of gluttony as they approached Leylin. “Gluttony’s corruption!”

Seeing that demonic palm, Leylin maintained an icy expression. He didn’t look to be in pain, only releasing a powerful green lightning containing the power of the world origin force in his body. His cold voice sounded, “Strike three!”

*Crackle!* “NOOOOO!” Leylin’s gigantic body immediately disintegrated, and an unwilling bellow rang out. Under the suppression of the Purgatory World’s will, Beelzebub’s conscient melted away like snow in the sun, leaving behind only the purest energy and comprehension of laws.

[Beep! Genetic recombination complete!]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded, and the Kemoyin Emperor behind Leylin behan to transform once again.

Two sharp claws stretched out, and the horn on its forehead protruded even further. The devilish wings became increasingly mystical, and black rhombus-shaped scales covered its body, emitting a mysterious luster.

“A new bloodline? No!” The Snake Dowager who watched this scene from afar could no longer keep her calm. Even though she was afraid of the protection of the World Will, she still attacked.

“Allsnake Shadow!” The murky Shadow World almost appeared to have been summoned by the Snake Dowager, attacking the Purgatory World.

Leylin did not counterattack. Instead, he spoke a few words, “I am Leylin Farlier, lord of all Kemoyin. As of this moment, all of the Kemoyin bloodline shall leave the control of the Snake Dowager!”

Leylin’s eyes held traces of turmoil within them as he made this solemn announcement. His voice practically rang throughout the world; as long as it was a descendant of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline they heard his voice and couldn’t help but kneel respectfully in subservience.

*Hss—* The giant snake behind Leylin completed the core of its transformation. No longer feeling the suppression of the Snake Dowager, it snarled at her.

“Ugh!” The pain on her expression was even clearer than before. Power from another plane seemed to be surging into Leylin’s body.

“I shall destroy your godly status,” he murmured, and with a vicious bite from the giant serpent behind him the sound of glass shattering could be heard. A huge gap had formed in the network of blood vessels on the Snake Dowager’s back The excruciating pain caused the enormous serpents in the sphere of snakes to groan piteously below the Snake Dowager, and the faint image of the Shadow World promptly crumbled.

Losing a part of her bloodline force caused great damage to the Dowager’s authority. It was enough to grievously injure her, and force her into a deep sleep.

“Leylin… Leylin!” The Snake Dowager snarled, no longer daring to stay here. The gigantic sphere of snakes rammed against the shackles of chaos.

Even more giant serpents were continuously struck by the lightning. However, they opened up a gap in the World Will’s restrictions that allowed the Snake Dowager to escape. She had the feeling that if she’d stayed here longer she would’ve died.

‘She escaped? Makes sense, she doesn’t know I’m limited to just three uses of this power. Furthermore, with my control of the bloodline and devouring power, as well as the attention of the World Will, she’d be in trouble if she stayed any longer.’ Leylin’s eyes flashed, and he did not chase after her. He currently had more more pressing matters at hand to attend to.

[Beep! Optimisation of host’s bloodline is completed. Law of gluttony and Allsnake origin blood have been added, currently at rank 6. Please rename the bloodline.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded.

“Targaryen. Call it the Targaryen bloodline!” Leylin decided on a new name.

[Beep! Recorded. Bloodline evolution has been completed. Targaryen has been saved to the database, currently at rank 6.]

As it sounded out, the A.I. Chip formed images of Leylin’s new bloodline patterns, naming them Targaryen. A circle of blood-red energy enveloped Leylin’s body.

The bloodline force of the Kemoyin Emperor had been changed to an entirely new bloodline. This change even extended to Leylin’s truesoul. It was like glass shattering as a bottle exploded; the feeling of breaking through a bottleneck of the soul caused Leylin to tremble involuntarily.

The new bloodline force surged violently, and with irresistible power the golden line in Leylin’s Full Moon truesoul expanded to envelop the entire thing. It was like a flame had been ignited.

[Beep! Host has broken through bloodline shackles. The positive energy of the truesoul is beginning to advance to rank 6]

the A.I. Chip transmitted.

For a Magus to advance from rank 5 to rank 6, the most important point was to completely convert negative soulforce to positive soul force. Leylin’s truesoul had already shown signs of the transformation, but due to the bloodline shackles the full process had been interrupted. Now, without the shackles, the process could be completed.

[Negative and positive soul force are yin soul force and yang soul force. Just didn’t use those names because most of the novel has stuck to a western theme so far and actual chinese concepts weren’t prevalent before.]

The bloodline shackles had been like an enormous mountain weighing down on Leylin, putting him under a lot of pressure. With them gone, the power he had amassed allowed him to soar. His truesoul rumbled in that instant, the moon set ablaze as it turned into a blazing golden sun. It grew severalfold in volume, emitting powerful and concentrated energy.

With the strength he possessed, Leylin’s success in breaking through to rank 6 was a given. Yet, that was not all. The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded once more.

[Beep! Host has reached rank 6. Huge changes have been made to body’s condition. Recalculating…]

It then intoned loyally once more,

[Beep! Host’s rank 5 innate skill Devour has been affected by law of gluttony. Devour has reached rank 6, now able to digest any energy, even that powered by opponents’ laws.]

‘Devour has been upgraded to rank 6 from rank 5… So I can devour laws from now?’ Leylin’s eyes twinkled, ‘Great! This innate bloodline ability is worthy of the rank 6 Targaryen bloodline!’

Past rank 6 was the realm of laws, and a bloodline that could devour laws and make them his own was obviously terrifying. This was also why he had spared no effort in getting Beelzebub to come to the Purgatory World. The law of gluttony and the innate skill of Devour complemented each other just too well. They were the best pair in Leylin’s view.

The ability to break through without end as long as one possessed enough energy was something Leylin coveted. He considered it to be the best catalyst in the process of breaking through his bloodline shackles.

[Beep! Host’s comprehension of law of devouring(transformed from law of gluttony) now at 99%]

[Beep! Host’s body has been converted to a body of laws. Progress: 99%. Body’s stats have surpassed standard limits, unable to be quantified. A switch to the Heavenly Astral Race’s measurement units is suggested.]

Seeing the last prompt, Leylin’s lips quirked as he burst into a wild laughter. Such terrifying strength caused even the air around him to shake. Since he had taken such huge risks in this adventure, he would obviously want to get the best benefits.

After reaching rank 6, the soul of a Magus would basically reach its limits, and its soul force would become tangible. Once they grasped a certain law, they would reach the realm of a rank 7 Magus. While Beelzebub’s law of gluttony was pretty good, Leylin did not like it all that much. After all, he still felt some lingering fear towards that insane appetite.

Having the abilities of his bloodline influenced by the power of gluttony, he could thus form the law of devouring. It was something Leylin had long since anticipated.

Leylin had grasped many laws even as he reached rank 6. He was no ordinary Breaking Dawn Monarch. In fact, he could be said to be halfway to rank 7!

Once he completely comprehended the last bit of the law of devouring, there would be nothing holding him back from becoming a Magus who comprehended laws.

Breaking Dawn Monarchs couldn’t grasp the power of laws the moment they broke through. They would have to wait to enter the peak of rank 6 before they could even peer into the world of laws.

But Leylin had done it! He had done something that was practically unprecedented in the Magus World’s history.

Chapter 759: Aftermath

The challenging risks had paid off. Leylin had staked everything on a desperate gamble, and it came through. Not only had he broken through his bloodline shackles, he had even grasped the power of laws! He was now comparable to a rank 7 law wielding Magus, and there was only a small barrier to his advance.

He was now so powerful that the A.I. Chip’s original units of measurement couldn’t quantify his strength any more. He had to switch to another unit of measurement.

‘Near rank 7 in power… If I stay in the Magus World, I won’t even need to be afraid of the Snake Dowager.’ Leylin was now completely relaxed, and he even had the urge to yell out into the heavens. ‘It’s a pity that I couldn’t lure Beelzebub out completely, and the law isn’t complete. However, just the damage to his soul is enough to cause him to go into a deep sleep or even die. Worse comes to worst, I’ll attack his lair and then seize the last bit of the power of laws. Naturally, I’ll be able to enter rank 7 after that.’

‘As expected, the power of a Magus changes drastically in rank 6. Those who grasp laws can’t even be measured by the A.I. Chip…’

“A.I. Chip, show what can be displayed,” Leylin commanded., immediately discovering a drastic change in his stats.

[Leylin Farlier, rank 6 Warlock. Bloodline: Targaryen (rank 6). Estimated stats, Strength: 5750, Agility: 4690, Vitality: 8290, Spiritual Force: ???, Magic Power: ???, Soul Force: ???. Comprehension of laws, Devour: 99%]

‘Hah… What a change!’ Leylin’s eyes narrowed, ‘This boost is much greater than that of my previous advancements. It’s basically tens, or even hundreds of times! The boost from the power of laws is so terrifying…

‘Based on the calculations, I must have over 10000 spiritual force, causing an overflow…’ Leylin stroked his chin and commanded, “Alright. Recalculate with the stats of the Heavenly Astral Race as the model.] [Beep! Recalculating host’s data… change completed] the A.I. Chip loyally intoned and showed the stats to Leylin.

[Leylin Farlier, rank 6 Warlock. Bloodline: Targaryen (rank 6). Strength: 172.52, Agility : 125.07, Vitality: 253.77, Spiritual force: 449.42, State of soul: Peak Breaking Dawn. Comprehension of laws: Devouring, 99%.]

The units of the new data were based on the Heavenly Astral Race. Every unit was more than ten times its previous standard. The numbers in spiritual force had condensed a hundredfold, allowing it to be quantified. Because Leylin’s soul force and power of laws had been merged into one, it was not shown on the A.I. Chip.

‘Mm! The A.I. Chip’s method of calculation is rather direct. Doesn’t this mean even the slightest of my actions equate to hundreds of Heavenly Astral Morning Stars?’

Leylin stroked his chin, ‘Our strength might be similar, but the boost from laws hasn’t been calculated into it by the A.I. Chip…’

Things would’ve been different if he was an ordinary Breaking Dawn, but Leylin had already stepped into the realm of laws. The boost from the power of laws caused his strength to increase so violently that it was terrifying.

*Rumble…* Large spirals of chaotic energy dissipated gradually in the air, and that pair of green eyes also vanished without a trace.

The sacrificial rune on Leylin’s body disappeared quickly, crumbling in practically the blink of an eye.

“The will of the Purgatory World has left…” Leylin muttered to himself, looking slightly desolate. As he had already reached rank 6 and comprehended laws, the World Will had sensed that Leylin had already surpassed many Monarchs.

“While I helped the World Will to gain some wisdom, it has helped me defeat my opponents and allowed me to advance. We’re even now…” Leylin could tell that his status as a Sacrificer had dropped as quickly as it had risen. He was now back at square one.

“The Purgatory Will is merely a robotic intellectual body. The help before was merely a transaction. If I want to become a child of Purgatory, I’ll have to join its side and allow its intent to pervade my body, becoming half a puppet.” Leylin stroked his chin. World Wills were rational and unfeeling. Even if Leylin had helped it before, were he to reveal even the slightest intent to harm the Purgatory World it would still treat him as an enemy.

Wills worked like artificial intelligences, programs with procedures programmed into them. While he could not influence such a thing with emotions, he would be safe against backstabbing. Settling the transaction once and for all was quick and convenient.

This was unlike dignitaries like the Nefarious Filthbird. With it, no matter how devout one was in their prayer it would still think of ways to take control of them, turning them into a bargaining chip. Something like that would never happen with the Purgatory Will.

“But my path is still that of magic— the path of truth. Turning into a half-puppet doesn’t suit me,” Leylin shook his head, abandoning all thoughts of settling in the Purgatory World. It wasn’t just becoming a subordinate of the Purgatory Will; just the thought of the other dignitaries here left Leylin’s scalp numb.

Leylin may have grown close to rank 7, becoming an existence that was thousands of times stronger than before, but he was still no match for a rank 8. He might have seemed courageous and unstoppable, but that was because he had the cheat that was the Purgatory World Will.

With the World Will around, those rank 8s had to deal with its suppression. They would only have about 50% of their original strength, and on top of that they had to deal with Leylin who had reached rank 7 as a Sacrificer with it. That obviously made things dangerous.

However, Leylin had depended entirely on an offering of the genetic clone of the ancient Wisdom Tree, which had given him great support from the Purgatory Will. In the future, he would not have an offering of that grade. If he were to meet with the Snake Dowager and duel fairly, even escaping could be difficult.

“I’ve awakened the will of the Purgatory World. That’s akin to finding an owner above those rank 8 existences who’s constantly thinking about ways to expel them from the Purgatory World.” Leylin felt pins and needles on his scalp.

In order to break through the bloodline shackles, he had roused the Purgatory Will from its slumber. That had had a great effect, but also thoroughly offended all the foreign dignitaries of the Purgatory World. However, if the situation were to repeat itself, Leylin would still make the same choice.

Still, staying in the Purgatory World was now a very irrational thing.

With so many rank 8 existences hostile towards him, and with him being an arch enemy of the Snake Dowager, not even the tiny bit of him would be left behind if they joined hands.

“The only choice is to hide in the Magus World,” Leylin’s eyes were filled with resolution. He was a native of the Magus World, and the powerful Magus World Will would naturally not suppress him. If foreign beings like the Snake Dowager were to enter, the suppression would be more terrifying than in the Purgatory World.

After all, the Magus World was one of the two most powerful worlds!

Weighing his options, Leylin was confident the rank 8 existences could reach the Magus World, but they would not be able to leave. Of course, there was a higher possibility that they would just give up. After all, they were no fools and would not seek death.

“Alright! Since I have a bit of time left, I should wrap everything up and leave as soon as possible!” Leylin’s expression was rather urgent.

*Roar—* *Wooo—* At this moment, the restrictions from the World Will dissipated, and the world resumed its movement. Numerous gluttonous beasts roared at Leylin with an air of provocation.

There was no lack of rank 6s among the beasts Beelzebub had nurtured. They had astutely sensed that if they could kill Leylin and steal his comprehension of laws, there would be a drastic transformation to their bodies.

If they were alone, they might not have dared do this. Now, however, the many gluttonous beasts turned into a horde. Leylin could be a peak rank 6 on the surface, but with the horde and many rank 6s surrounding and attacking him, there was a slight possibility of him being killed.

“Kill him!” “Kill him!” The three-headed python that was the second elder of the Stewart Family provoked the gluttonous beasts around him to advance.

The earlier events had progressed too quickly, and on top of that there was a seal from the World Will. Many gluttonous beasts and even residents of the holy city were yet to react to it.

Only the rank 6s felt a sense of fear when it came to Leylin, but the hope to break through to the power of laws enticed them to take the risk.

*Roar—* The gluttonous snakes that were as enormous as mountains surrounded Leylin, accompanied by the terrifying zombified monsters.

“Is this clever?” Leylin watched the three-headed python hiding behind the berserk rank 6 beings, a slight smile on his face, “Even an ordinary peak rank 6 would find trouble when attacked like this, no? It’s a pity though… I’ve already passed through the realm of rank 6. The power of laws is something you cannot imagine…”

Having nearly grasped the law of devouring, Leylin had changed drastically. The immense increase in his stats reached the requirements of rank 7. At the very least, the Blazing Flame Monarch that Leylin had seen before definitely did not have such extreme numbers when it came to spiritual force, and perhaps had yet to even reach the ten thousands.

After all, she had merely comprehended a bit of the power of flames, and only understood the tip of the iceberg. How could that be comparable to Leylin, who now had a body of laws?

“Submit!” Leylin merely spat out this single word while he was encircled by the many rank 6 gluttonous beasts.

In that moment, the terrifying power of laws exploded from his body, causing the world to come to a standstill once again.

*Thud!* *Thud!* There were hints of struggle in the beasts’ eyes, but their bodies automatically knelt down.

Chapter 760: Back to the Magus World

With one word, the numerous rank 6 beings bowed their heads to him. The power of laws shockingly had such an effect!

“It shouldn’t be difficult to control these beasts given some time with just the law of gluttony. Pity…” Leylin gazed at the eyes of the large gluttonous beasts and shook his head.

“I can’t bring them back to the Magus World. Besides, I’m relying on the law of devouring which isn’t compatible with these gluttonous beasts. Most importantly, their power originates from the gluttonous power of Beelzebub. Now that the root of their power has been warped, I can’t fix them even if I try.”

“Perish! Innate law— Devour!” A terrifying, monstrous winged serpent that extended across the horizon appeared behind Leylin, and a horrifying black hole was formed in an instant.

Numerous gluttonous beasts wailed in anguish, but seemed to be suppressed by some kind of invisible force that rendered them immobile as they watched themselves disappearing into that black hole.

“No! I’m the second elder of the Stewart family, destined to break through the bloodline shackles and bring my family to glory. Why… Why did things turn out this way?” The enormous three-headed python discovered something was amiss when the black hole appeared, and he began to flee for his life. However, that wasn’t enough to escape the fate of being devoured. Along with howls of indignation, his voice slowly disappeared into the black hole.

The invisible pull spread across the plains, and the many gluttonous beasts were thrown into the black hole while howling in anguish. Their rank didn’t matter. Minutes later, all of the gluttonous beasts surrounding the holy city were completely gone.

“I feel a little full now,” Leylin touched his belly, speechless. After devouring so many gluttonous beasts, the bit of heat that he felt surging through his body had disappeared in an instant.

At this moment, the A.I. Chip’s prompt was transmitted.

[Beep! Host has taken in a small amount of essence, boosted by rank 6 innate skill Devour. Strength has risen by 0.001. Vitality has risen by 0.002.]

“After reaching semi rank 7, energy below that of laws is useless to me.” Leylin shook his head. He, who had now almost completely grasped the law of devouring, had a body of laws that was incomparable to what it had been before.

The essence of the gluttonous beasts of the Serpent Plains was just a tiny supplement for him.

“It’s time to leave.” Leylin’s eyes swept across the holy city. As he had intentionally spared the city before, the power of devouring had not taken in any resident of the holy city. Hence, all the snake beings within the holy city gazed at Leylin dumbly and took particular notice of that terrifying Targaryen serpent, practically losing all ability to speak.

“What’s going on? I only saw the holy mother appear, but after that, everything seemed to have gone stagnant. When did that thing appear?”

Belinda stared dumbly at the figure of the monstrous winged serpent, “Why… Why does this give me such a familiar feeling? Is this some hidden power of the holy mother?”

“Found you!” A gentle voice was heard by Belinda’s ear, and she then felt her body grow light, as if someone was lifting her, and her surroundings changed before her eyes in an instant.

When she regained her senses, she was already standing outside the holy city.

“Sister!” An elated voice could be heard. Sophia threw herself into Belinda’s arms, her tears falling without pause, and she evidently looked frightened.

“My precious Sophia!” Belinda patted Sophia’s back, and then glanced towards Aegnis, who looked despondent and down.

Of course, what attracted her attention the most was the the figure standing at the side and wearing black magic robes, who was just like some sort of god.

The black hair, pupils that were like the dark night and the face of this young stranger was like that of a god who had come down to this world… Everything about him was incomparably flawless, but Belinda felt a sense of familiarity with him.

“Belinda, Sophia and Aegnis, we meet again! Let me reintroduce myself. I am Leylin Farlier, and my name of Nick from before was just my alias,” Leylin gazed at the three uniquely different snake girls and laughed slightly, while saying things that caused their expressions to change drastically. Using the power of laws to search the city and bring the three of them here had taken just a second.

“You’re… Nick?” Belinda gaped, looking stunned. No matter how she tried, she was completely unable to match this man, who had gotten rid of countless gluttonous beasts with a wave of his hand, with the Nick she knew.

On top of that, Nick had had long silver hair, scarlet pupils and many wrinkles from aging. No matter how she looked at it, it was impossible for her to link the two of them.

No! If she were to disregard those features, his features were still rather similar! Belinda’s eyes narrowed, now finally knowing where that sense of familiarity was coming from.

“So should I call you brother Nick or brother Leylin from now on?” Sophia merely bit her fingernails, looking perplexed.

“That’s up to you, but I personally prefer being called Leylin!”

“Leylin Farlier, the wanted Magus! The person cursed by the holy mother!” Aegnis expressionlessly recited Leylin’s background. “Good job exploiting our Stewart Family. Where’s the holy mother?” While she still looked grim, her heart was sinking.

First was the betrayal of the second elder, which meant that the Stewart Family had not fulfilled its duties. It was because he had the protection of the Stewart Family that he had been able to cause so much damage to her.

After this disaster, would the Stewart Family have a chance of revitalising itself?

Not exterminating the whole Stewart Family should already be considered magnanimous on the Snake Dowager’s part.

“The Mighty Mother of All Snakes is obviously fine. She just left temporarily!” Leylin chuckled subtly. He then glanced towards Belinda, “So? Have you accepted this yet?”

“You’ve been… using me? You’ve already accomplished your aims, so why did you get me here?”

Belinda stood up, a dead look in her eyes.

“I can’t deny that.”

Leylin nodded, and then noticed Belinda’s body swaying.

“Then why?” Belinda’s eyes were full of complicated feelings.

“It’s obviously so that I can take you away!” Leylin laughed.

“Take us away?” Belinda never imagined there would be this sort of answer.

”Where are we going? Will it be fun?” Sophia’s eyes twinkled, her focus evidently quite different from the others’.

“That’s not happening. I need to stay here. My family needs me.” This was Aegnis’ reply.

“I’m afraid that’s not up to you,” Leylin said calmly. Belinda and Aegnis suddenly realised that they had lost all their strength. Whether their elemental affinity or bloodline force or even power as a Sacrificer, everything descended into stillness and could not be used at all.

“You can hate me, Belinda, but you must obey me and leave this world with me,” Leylin sounded serene, but there was an intent there that could not be resisted.

“My actions here, hm… how do I put it? I’ve completely offended the Snake Dowager. I’m obviously not afraid of her, but she might take her anger out on you guys. Hence, you’ll need to leave the Purgatory World…

“This reason is very applicable to Aegnis’ situation.”

Leylin stared at Aegnis, who now looked dull. If not for the fact that she had taken care of Belinda and her sister, Leylin wouldn’t even have cared whether she lived or died.

However, the Snake Dowager would absolutely take out her anger on the Stewart Family and they would be destroyed. This was a matter already set in stone, and if she were to stay behind, she was most likely doomed.

“Offending the Snake Dowager and having her anger taken out on us? O mighty dignitary! What have you done?!” Belinda was immediately stunned by these affairs, which were like that had only happened in legends.

“It’s nothing! I just made her bleed a little and also tore her godly status apart,” Leylin shrugged his shoulders, “Alright, enough idle talk. It’s time to go.”

“Hss…” The enormous monstrous winged snake hissed and struck at the air, opening up a huge black hole. Leylin flew into the air and, bringing the other three along, abruptly entered the spatial pathway.

*Whoosh!* Many fresh flowers bloomed to full flower on the grassland, turning the area into a sea of flowers. The wind whistled and brushed past, sending petals flying as beautiful music was heard, as if the Purgatory Will was sending Leylin off.

The snake beings in the holy city could only watch on cluelessly. The faith of some of them wavered, beginning to worship Leylin. This began the legend of a winged serpent dignitary, spreading in Purgatory World…

*PIla!*

A terrifying spatial storm was formed, and much lightning formed an arched door. Four figures traversed the lightning gate and descended to another place.

The sky was dark and gloomy and gave a repressed feeling. The air was full of negative energy and earth-type elemental particles.

“The localisation was rather successful! Though the astral plane coordinates long since stopped working, I’m not the same person I was before!” Leylin surveyed his surroundings, finding that this was close to the laboratory from which he had traversed to the Purgatory World, and he could not help but nod in satisfaction.

An existence of laws could wander around in the astral plane, and he’d long since known of the Magus World’s coordinates. There was no trouble in getting back. Powerful solidified soul force and the power of laws allowed Leylin to get a deeper understanding of the Magus World.

Like a mother whose child who had been traveling had returned, the Magus World received Leylin with open arms without the least bit of suppression.

“The Magus World’s Will…” Leylin closed his eyes, the figure of a Targaryen serpent emerging at his back, “So it’s already sunk into a slumber?”

“However…” Leylin glanced at the three whose auras had obviously become weaker, “Even deep asleep, it still subconsciously rejects existences from other worlds and even causes fear amongst rank 8 existences. How powerful could the World Will be at its peak condition?”

Chapter 765: The Power to Move Mountains

“Just looking at beautiful scenery is also a way of enjoying yourself!” Leylin’s eyes had a different look to them.

He had previously been afflicted with the Allsnake Curse, and had no choice but to struggle against the heavens. He had taken the risk to enter the Purgatory World, dancing on the edge of a blade with no extra time to do something as mundane as enjoying the scenery.

Now, however, after completely ridding himself of the curse on his bloodline,his body of laws, near rank 7, would last him over 100,000 years.

With this much more time, he finally had time to breathe, released from his tight schedule. This was why he had spent so much effort on dealing with this bilateral trade.

He had previously been someone who could not even take care of himself, so why would he bother with others? Now, with a lot more time and freedom, Leylin finally had the chance to consider the development of Ouroboros Clan, the Farlier Family and so on.

“Taking care of this land and its profits should be able to keep the Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan living well for thousands of years if managed well… and then there’s the tiny issue in the central continent…” Leylin stroked his chin.

He was planning to use around a decade to take care of matters in the central continent and perhaps the whole surface of the Magus World. Besides getting his own people to succeed in life, he wanted to build up his own power.

Whatever it was, based on the oral agreement with Ignox, he was going to have to take care of this land anyway. The subterranean existences would pay no heed to his actions.

‘In their eyes, the surface of the Magus World is not only incredibly small, but also produces few resources. It possesses no resources beneficial for those existences of laws. Amongst the Magi, there are only a few rank 6s, and it’s a remote and desolate place. They’re not losing out by tossing it to me. After all, Ignox was tasked with the first to fourth levels underground, and each level is comparable to the surface world…’

Of course, the reason Ignox had done so was because Leylin had yet to properly advance, and he wanted to ease his work.

‘That’s better for me anyway. I’ll definitely go to the depths of the core, but not yet. Furthermore, I can do a lot with the surface world when it’s completely under my control…’

……

Three days later, in front of the Thunderbird Holyland.

Numerous members of the Lyas family, under Eam and Arthur’s lead, gazed at the figure before them with respect.

Leylin had long since gotten used to this and continued to discuss matters with Aegnis. “How has the progress for building the organisation been?”

“It’s going alright,” Aegnis tucked her long hair behind her ear. She had changed into feminine attire which made the lines of her body more gentle, as if she was trying to show off her feminine charm.

“In terms of manpower, the Lyas family and Arthur Empire have already provided me with a lot authority and help. Of course, I hope to use my own people.”

Aegnis seemed very capable and experienced as she said,“ Tryxis, for instance, is the second-in-command of the subterranean organisation Shadow Toro. He recently eliminated the head and brought the whole organisation to us. His earth elemental spells aren’t half bad and he has some experience commanding organisations. He’s been a great help!”

“Oh?” Leylin’s truesoul force swept forth in an instant, and all the details of this Tryxis that Aegnis had pointed out appeared before his eyes.

“He recognized the power of our side so quickly, and his acts were so brazen… He has pretty good foresight…” It was a pity that this was all. No matter how smart he was, he barely entered Leylin and Aegnis’ sights. In the face of absolute crushing strength, scheming lost all effect.

“You can decide on that with Belinda. I’m giving you free reign. Now, let me completely remodel the ruins. The current place just isn’t suitable as a trading base.” Leylin floated into the air like a god. An awe-inspiring might like that of a divinity descended in that instant, causing many low-ranked Magi to faint.

A howling Targaryen appeared, with a pair of monstrous wings, single malevolent horn and pair of sharp claws growing from its belly. A unique spiritual force wave was transmitted to every Magus in the surroundings. “Hss… I am the king of devouring, the ruler of chaos and the void!”

“Devouring… the king of devouring? Is this the power that the lord wields?” King Arthur murmured to himself, taking the initiative to kneel. This was his aspiration, the end he desired on his path. With his lead, the Magi behind him all sank to their knees one by one.

Immediately after, they heard Leylin speak softly in mid-air, “Innate skill: Devour!”

*Crash!* It was as if a terrifying invisible mouth swept through the sky, large enough that once it passed the entirety of the ruins had disappeared. Whether it was the defensive spell patterns of the ruins or the seals and reinforcements added by the Lyas family over the years, they could not affect it at all.

There was no lightning, no flames. Nor was there a backlash from any of the mechanisms in the ruins. It was as if the place had never existed. A wide expanse had opened up in the ground. An aerial view would show that the ruins had gone missing, replaced by a terrifyingly deep pit that looked like something had eaten into it.

Many of the Magi were dazed, but some of the younger ones grew zealous as they cried out, “The master of devouring!” “The devouring ruler!”

“All the unnecessary facilities have been destroyed, only the sealed pathway remains.” A dark door brimming with light appeared slowly deep within the pit, seeming desolate.

“Let there be soil!” Leylin spoke faintly, and the earth howled. The ground trembled violently, and large amounts of earth squirmed upwards to fill the deep pit. The power of an existence that comprehended laws was divine, terrifying beyond belief.

“Moving mountains and suppressing seas with just a single thought! Is this the ability of a rank 7 Magus of laws?”

Leylin was very satisfied with his current control over laws. Through his comprehension and usage of laws, he even had the misconception that he was the world.

“Everything in the world is composed of and affected by laws. With my control and influence using my law of Devour, even if I have less than 0.01% control over of other laws, it is enough to unite the laws to form a fundamental change in everything…”

Leylin looked intoxicated by this.

Rank 1 to 3 Magi might be more powerful than regular humans. Those at and above rank 4, the Morning Stars, Radiant Moons and Breaking Dawns had all grasped the power to massacre and destroy countries. Those at rank 7 and above at the realm of laws lived and breathed with worlds, like the gods that overlooked all life from high ground.

The radiance of eternity was already beginning to appear before Leylin.

“Let everything that exists in this world continue to exist for all eternity!”

Leylni’s voice seemed to hold within holy light, scattering all over the beautiful surface of the earth.

*Rumble! A brand new construction with multiple buildings rose, encircling the spatial passage at the heart of it and creating a gigantic triumphal arch.

Numerous green stones flickered with dazzling lights on the construction.

“This is… Everlasting solidification spells, reinforcement runes, conscient runes.. The effect from this combination is enough for all the buildings to last without corrosion for above ten thousand years. That’s the effect of only one sentence from my lord…”

A white-haired Magus with thick presbyopic glasses twitched as if he had epilepsy, eyes even glimmering with tears of happiness, “This is the pinnacle of magic— to be able to directly leverage the power of the original laws?”

“All seals shall corrode, and only the passage between the two areas shall remain eternal!”

*Hualala!* The arched door of light immediately emitted elegant and beautiful luster. The layers on the seal crumbled one after the other, and the door of light unceasingly expanded until it merged with the whole triumphal arch, emitting shining rays of light.

“The spatial passage that has been reinforced with my laws should be able to be maintained for thousands of years even if it works in overdrive everyday.”

Blue rays flashed in Leylin’s eyes, giving him this information in an instant.

After grasping the power of laws, his thoughts were not lacking at all to the ultimate brain of his previous life, and perhaps even exceeded it.

Only the A.I. Chip, which had been with Leylin all this while and merged with his body had gained immense benefits, and could therefore surpass Leylin’s mind when it came to calculations.

The tremors of the ground continued, and numerous buildings kept rising from the ground. In the blink of an eye, a whole Magus City had been established.

“This area shall be the base of your organisation, and the name… Let’s call it ‘Alabaster City!’!”

Leylin smiled at Belinda as he spoke, and saw the glint in her eyes.

With Aegnis’ command, the many Magi before surged into the city, beginning more meticulous work and alterations, as well as any moving required.

Leylin was accompanied by Belinda and Aegnis and came to the heart of the spatial door.

“You’re not going back with me?”

Leylin glanced at Belinda. This pair had already accepted him long ago, and even Aegnis seemed to have an inclination to do so too. It was just a matter of time.

“No, I won’t go! Don’t you have a wife there?”

Belinda bit her lips stubbornly, “I want to stay here in the city you made for me to guard all that is yours!”

Leylin had already guessed Belinda’s thoughts. That matched with his wish anyway.

“As you wish! This place will belong to you. Even the organisation on the surface will have to heed your words after coming here.”

Leylin nodded while he stepped into the spatial door.

Chapter 767: The World and Beyond

“I’m sorry my beloved, I could not accompany you,” Freya’s eyes seemed to redden, covered in a layer of sparkling tears.

“No, you’ve raised Syre. For me, and our Farlier family, this is the greatest contribution,” Leylin stood up with the adorable little fellow.

As his son had inherited his Serpent Emperor bloodline, his appetite was enormous. Occasionally he was full of uncontrollable energy and emotional issues with his bloodline power arose. Naturally, for high-ranked Warlocks, these couldn’t be considered problems at all.

“…In that case, the bloodline shackles of Kemoyin Warlocks are all gone?”

Freya thought of the most crucial point.

“No, strictly speaking, only my bloodline shackles have disappeared. Your bloodline origins however, now originate from me instead,” Leylin spoke truthfully, “but with my help, it won’t be a problem for you to advance to rank 6. As for Syre, since he has my bloodline, there’s an even greater probability for him to advance.”

“What do you mean, an even greater probability?”

“Syre, come here!” Leylin smiled as he waved Syre over.

“Father!” The little boy ran to Leylin, with traces of fruit juice and grease still on his hands, “Hug!”

“Alright,” Leylin smiled as he hugged the boy to his chest.

“Syre, my blood, I give you my blessing. You will be blessed with incomparable glory, and the holy light will be at your side forever!” Leylin declared.

At that moment, the world seemed to come to a standstill. A tall phantom of a Targaryen winged snake appeared behind him.

Leylin assumed a solemn expression on his face, as if he was a God proclaiming an oracle.

It was a pity that all of the maidservants had long fallen into a dead faint, and only Freya was able to stubbornly remain clear-headed. However, the powerful phantom behind Leylin was also faintly trembling.

Syre was already fast asleep, but a small phantom of a Kemoyin Serpent Emperor appeared on his skin.

“Although I could do this after you’ve grown up, but it would be easier to advance the bloodline when you’re small…”

There was a tumultuous expression in Leylin’s eyes as he said, “My son, Syre, thou shalt inherit my endless and eternal strength, and become the Ouroboros Clan’s King!”

“From today onwards, thou art Ouroboros, the serpent of infinity, Ouroboros!”

With a hissing sound, the Targaryen winged snake behind Leylin opened its jaws widely and poured out a great deal of smoke, which engulfed the phantom of the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor completely.

The smoke finally transformed into a cocoon that had the phantom of the serpent emperor wrapped up within it. It seemed to be undergoing some mysterious metamorphosis.

Syre was still sound asleep, but his aura had clearly changed.

“This… This is…” As Freya saw this, she had completely lost her ability to speak.

“He must be very tired, do take him away and let him have a good rest. Take care to increase his milk by several times today and tomorrow,” Leylin smiled as he withdrew the phantom snake and his immense power, to the point where he appeared to be a normal Warlock. He had a gentle smile on his face, but the way he spoke made it clear that his orders were to be obeyed.

“Yes… Of course,” Freya absent-mindedly carried Syre away, and one could tell that she was mired in bewilderment and shock– the power that Leylin had shown was already beyond the mortal realm. Even the Blazing Flame Monarch was infinitely inferior compared to him.

After completing this, Leylin walked to the window alone. His gaze seemed to pass through the Eternal River pocket dimension to the starry sky outside.

“Daniel, my eldest son!” Leylin said in a low voice.

His soul force exploded with power that seemed to surpass the laws of the world, and penetrated directly into the Twilight Zone.

“This… What is this power?”

His young wife, Celine, had a look of horror on her face as she was awed by the powerful force.

With a loud crash, innumerable black particles began to converge into an enormous face. The intimidating aura flowed from its pupils gave off a suffocating feeling.

However Celine felt incomparably familiar with that face and said, “Ley…Leylin? You’re Leylin!”

“My son, Daniel!”

The enormous dark face continued to speak, and Daniel struggled violently out of Celine’s arms and ran towards the dark face.

“Thou will inherit my devouring and Dreamscape ability, and become the World Serpent, Jormungandr!”

Along with the face’s proclamation, laws of ‘Devour’ and dreamforce poured like a stream from it and engulfed Daniel completely, immediately changing him at the cellular level.

“I’ve returned, please take care of Daniel!”

At the end of the ceremony, Leylin’s voice came from the enormous dark face, and soon after disappeared without a trace.

However, the powerful feeling from earlier remained. Celine stroked her face, and was finally convinced that she wasn’t dreaming or was affected by some illusion.

“Daniel, my Daniel!” Celine flew to Daniel’s side, but after she realised he was only unconscious and not dead, she finally breathed a sigh of relief.

At this moment, she discovered that Daniel had slightly changed. The most noticeable change was the black rune that he was tightly grasping in his hand.

This black rune had a pure quality to it, as if it was the only one of its kind in this world. It had an inscription of a demonic Winged Devilsnake, which seemed to be connected to some unfathomably powerful being.

“This is Leylin’s aura, this is his rune!”

Celine stowed the black rune away with a look of astonishment on her face, and looking at the sleeping Daniel, she couldn’t help but to mutter to herself, “Leylin… What level has he reached now?”

……

“From today onwards, the infinite serpent Ouroboros and the World Serpent Jormungandr will be the two main bloodlines of my Farlier family,” Leylin leaned against the balcony, with a tumultuous expression within his eyes.

As Syre was the son of his first wife, Leylin envisaged him as inheriting his eternal and infinite power. However, this was only a seedling of a thought, and he would only be able to let Syre walk a future path to an even stronger bloodline if Leylin himself continued to constantly improve himself.

As for Daniel, his eldest son, his inherited abilities of Devour and dreamforce was already stabilised and mature, and would very quickly become his main strength in battle.

“Speaking of this, Syre’s bloodline still has far more potential for growth, and is full of unlimited possibilities. However, it is still far from perfect! And Daniel’s bloodline is the most violent, but the future has already been fixed for him,” Leylin stroked his chin, a smile blooming on his face.

“Their present and the future will be up to them!”

As an existence that was infinitely close to Rank 7, Leylin now had the ability to do what many high-ranking Magi thought was unimaginable, which was to make use of origin force.

To pass on his own bloodline, and even make a copy of his own abilities, for Leylin it wasn’t a particularly difficult thing.

Only, the paths these two bloodline branches would follow was just within Leylin’s imagination, and with the A.I. Chip’s assisted deductions, it still had some imperfect aspects.

In reality, the titles he had given earlier such as the the World Serpent and the Infinite Serpent were only given because they sounded nice, coupled with his momentary bad taste.

However, he had the confidence that after several hundred years had passed, these two mature bloodlines would absolutely dominate the entire central continent, and eclipse other bloodline warlocks.

Even when Leylin had arrived at the Rank 9 Eternal Realm, these two bloodlines of his would not be even a little bit inferior to those legends of old.

“Although I have already helped them to remodel and advance their bloodline, their bloodlines all originate from me, and for the time being their highest potential is only to rank 6. They can only continue to advance once I break through to a higher rank…”

Leylin carefully pondered this situation. He was thinking of establishing his clan, reproducing his bloodline, and investigating the probability of evolving his bloodline, and these were all tasks that the A.I. Chip was constantly researching as well.

Leylin very much looked forward to the surprise the bloodlines he had passed on would bring him, after going through nature’s survival of the fittest and natural selection.

……

The limitless azure sea, as far as the eye could see, with white waves sweeping across it.

Leylin and the others stood on the deck of an enormous sailboat, and their bodies moved up and down with the waves.

“So you’re saying that the work of transporting Kemoyin Warlocks to the south coast is still ongoing?”

Leylin supported himself on the railing and slightly furrowed his brows, “This speed is really far too slow. Within a month, the entire Ouroboros clan’s headquarters must be moved to this place, only then do we have enough people to develop the subterranean commerce!”

Although he had only complained a little, Emma and Gilbert broke out in a cold sweat behind him.

In the end, it was only due to Gilbert and Leylin’s earlier camaraderie as a master and disciple, that he could stand out and say, “The south coast has many dangerous areas, and some have even reached the extent of Rank 4 in danger. We can only use reinforced models of airships and ship holds, and dispatch a Morning Star force to escort them, and consequently the pace is slow…”

The dangers near the south coast weren’t considered much to Morning Star Magi, but for those Rank 3 Magi, it was as if it was a natural barrier to them.

“Mm, although your argument makes sense, you really have to increase the speed!”

“Of course we all want to seize the generous profits of subterranean commerce as quickly as possible, so it’s a pity…” Emma and Gilbert exchanged a glance, with a wry smile on their faces.

“On my map, this most dangerous area is the Dragon Whales territorial waters here?”

“Yes it is, my lord!” Emma involuntarily answered him.

“Very good, then perhaps I can help!” Leylin smiled lightly, but his expression suddenly turned icy, “Come out now!”

A ghastly sound with icy majesty could be heard along the surface of the sea, but it was the energy undulations that came from their periphery that made Gilbert and Emma’s expressions change drastically.

Chapter 768: Dragonwhale Successor

*Roar!*

A heavy noise sounded from the bottom of the ocean and that was followed by a terrifying shadow, constantly emitting strong life force undulations.

The pressure from its gigantuan body alone created a tsunami of magnitude 10, causing the ship that Leylin was on to waver violently.

“Float!” Gilbert commanded with a sharp voice.

*Phew! Phew!* Thick streams of air sounded with unbounded energy and propped the entire ship, resulting in it being suspended mid-air.

However, things were not so fortunate for the other marine tribes present. A mass of sharks, turtles and a mishmash of sea creatures were carried away in the waves of this catastrophe, many were even crushed to pulps of flesh, dyeing the surrounding waters red with blood.

The shadow grew exponentially, its size comparable to that of a continent. And in the blink of an eye, a huge mountain blade tore through the surface of the sea like a knife blade, revealing an enormous black back.

“T-This…is the Dragonwhale?!” Emma’s jaw dropped.

“The leader amongst them, more accurately. And it could be the totem of the marine tribe!” Leylin’s smile faded quickly. “Keep the noise down!”

The boundless sea calmed in tandem to Leylin’s order. Two eyes the size of planets roamed in the deep sea, with beams of light projecting out of them.

A phantom appeared, and it showed a middle-aged marine tribe man.

“Ulaz is here to meet my lord!”

“A rank 6 king of the Dragonwhales! His physical size is already equivalent to that of a small continent! Thank god only rank 4 Dragonwhale appeared instead of this one when we were previously moving…” Gilbert’s eyes narrowed and he immediately thought that he was hallucinating.

“What? He called Leylin ‘My lord’? Aren’t they of the same rank? Moreover, a Dragon-whale with such an impressive size

“Are you the one in charge of the Dragonwhale territorial waters, Ulaz?” Leylin readily asked.

“Yes my lord, as well as the neighbouring few islets and the continent’s marine tribe!” This soul phantom called Ulaz replied in a cute manner.

Even the lowest ranked Dragonwhale could create great storms and waves in the south coast before, which led to great losses, and even Leylin had heard of it back when he was a Rank 1 or Rank 2 Magi.

Now however, not even the strongest Dragonwhale King was trash worth mentioning in his eyes.

‘This form is abundant in bloodline force and if I devour it, the most it will increase my constitution by is 0.003!’ Leylin’s blue eyes flashed as he instantly got the answer, and the Dragonwhale King suddenly shivered underwater.

‘It’s too little, and I also still have other uses for it!’ Leylin inwardly shook his head and gave up on devouring the Dragonwhale.

“Ulaz, I have something for you to do,” a powerful force from Leylin, who possessed power over the creature’s life or death, naturally began to speak to it.

“My lord, please command me, your humble servant will not refuse under any circumstances!” For the same reason, after sensing Leylin’s unfathomable power and knowing its life was in Leylin’s hands, the Dragonwhale King answered with the utmost respect.

“Very good, I am the Ouroboros Clan’s elder, and should you see the flag of the Ouroboros Clan hung on any transportation, you are not allowed to attack them, and must even protect them, do you understand?”

“I will follow your command, almighty expert! I will also send my children as escorts for your ships!” Ulaz delightedly agreed.

“Very good,” Leylin nodded. After he showed his intent to try to catch him, the enormous Dragonwhale disappeared from the ocean surface, as if it was being chased away by some powerful magic.

‘For the south coast, the rank 6 Dragonwhale King is an undefeatable existence…” Leylin stroked his chin and said, “Fortunately, it didn’t pay much attention to the south coast in the past, or perhaps it had been dormant, otherwise the entire south coast could not endure its fury…”

Just the gathering of the Dragonwhale’s children could isolate the south coast from the outside world, and if the Dragonwhale King itself personally attacked them, looking at its form, it could have easily devastated the entire continent.

After all, although the south coast liked to toot its own horn as a continent, from the view of those Magi from the central continent, it was only a slightly larger island.

“Did you hear that? Move everyone as soon as possible! I trust that there won’t be any dangers from now on,” Leylin said to the two Kemoyin warlocks after following the Dragonwhale King’s departure with his eyes.

“U-Understood!” Gilbert wiped the cold sweat from his brow. Just seeing Ulnaz from earlier made him feel fearful in his heart.

And the person who could send the powerful Dragonwhale bending its knee, what rank had Leylin reached?

“Lord L-Leylin! Would it be possible for you to tell us your current rank?”

Jeffrey, who had been equally terrified, stood at the side. He was more powerful than Gilbert and the others, and was already a rank 5 Radiant Moon warlock. However, because of this, he could understand the Dragonwhale’s power even more.

At the same time, he began to perceive Leylin’s change.

In any case, even if it was the entire central continent’s strongest monarch, could not be on the same level as the rank 6 Dragonwhale King, and this gave Jeffrey an enormous shock.

“Me? I’m still a rank 6 warlock!”

Leylin smiled and hid nothing.

“How could this be?”

“However, I am only half a step away from rank 7,” the latter half of Leylin’s sentence sent the warlocks on the deck into a sluggish state.

“Seven… Rank 7! The rumoured god, with the existence of laws?” Jeffrey’s eyes widened and his mouth gaped wide open, as if he was an enormous toad. He foolishly looked at Leylin as he entered the hold of the ship.

“Duke Gilbert! Duchess Emma! Please could you confirm if I imagined that?”

After a moment of great bafflement, only then did Jeffrey try his best to readjust his expression back into place, and involuntarily ask.

“I’m afraid that you didn’t mishear, your royal highness Prince Jeffrey!”

Gilbert and Emma exchanged a glance with a wry smile on their faces and said, “However, we’re already quickly getting used to it. Lord Leylin has always been good at creating hopes and miracles!”

Now even Gilbert would not dare to consider himself as Leylin’s mentor anymore.

After all, he was an existence that was reaching rank 7!

Rank 7! What could it mean? In the ancient times, it would still be considered the position of a celebrated expert. The conqueror of many worlds, many native tribes could only tremble and weep…

And now, the Ouroboros clan had the strength of this rank?

Gilbert realised that he could only giggle at this thought, and Emma was also leaning towards it.

“Rank 7? Rank 7, ah… Bevis, Offa, your plans will all come to nothing!”

Jeffrey could only react to that after a long time, and suddenly sighed with a lonely expression on his face.

No matter who it was, once they had dealt with Leylin for some time they would feel as if they had been struck a blow. Jeffrey had previously felt this several times, but this time it was an even more powerful blow.

“However, with Leylin, the springtime of our bloodline warlocks has arrived!” After he had sighed, Jeffrey’s eyes were filled with hope.

Even if the central continent was currently filled with many Monarch ranked Magi, to a semi-rank 7 they were as insignificant as ants. With just one slap, swathes of them would die. Jeffrey could already see the scene where bloodline warlocks would dominate the central continent.

The enormous benefits that conquering the central continent would represent rendered their earlier schemes and all those things they had previously worked hard to defend seem ridiculous.

“Perhaps this was exactly what that lord wanted?”

Jeffrey looked in the direction of the ship’s hold and secrelty clenched his fist, an abnormal red flush appearing on his face.

……

Under Leylin’s operation, they had completed the long journey from the south coast to the central continent in the space of the few days.

When Gilbert and the others had made this journey before, they had needed a few months. If it wasn’t considered to have been too wasteful, Emma had even wanted to set up an astral gate in the south coast.

Passing through the astral gate and Morning Star realm’s hub and establishing a transportation spell formation that could cover the entire central continent was an important trump card to the bloodline warlocks.

However for the relocation of the entire organisation, operating the astral gate might use up a little of their resources, but the numerous times used would all add up to an enormous figure that would make even Gilbert and the others faint. Even their entire family fortune wouldn’t be able to afford it, and they could only use this long distance travel to carry out their move.

The astral gate’s transportation could only be used to transport several people or several important goods, and wasn’t suitable for the work of large-scale relocation.

However, after everything was settled, Leylin was already prepared to construct an astral gate on the south coast. Not just the south coast, even in the Twilight Zone and the subterranean world, he wouldn’t leave them out.

Although large-scale transportation wasn’t possible, but it would be very convenient for him to transport himself.

Within the Morning Star realm.

Alpha looked even more old and clumsy compared to before, as if his body had decayed. His eyes, however, still had an energy that was difficult to hide.

“Wade, do you think Jeffrey’s previous summon was real?” Offa rubbed his hands somewhat excitedly. He and Wade were both waiting at the transfer point, and even Bevis was also there, although his face was already incomparably gloomy.

“Jeffrey, as you both and I know, would not deceive us on this sort of thing! In addition, if that person has really risen to rank 6, we can confirm it once we meet face-to-face!”

Wayde said with a smile. Jeffrey’s messages were lagging behind a little, and once these two could truly acknowledge Leylin’s strength, perhaps they would be in for a great surprise.

Chapter 769: Turbulent Undercurrent

With a buzz, the Morning Star realm’s transportation area suddenly flickered with a brilliant light.

“They have arrived!” Offa and Wayde’s eyes lit up at the sight, but Bevis’ expression became rather probing and had an unyielding look to it.

Several figures wrapped in a gentle ray of light appeared. After the light had dispersed, it revealed the figure of Leylin, Jeffrey and the others.

“Sir Offa, Sir Wayde and Sir Bevis! It’s been a long time since we met,” Leylin walked in front of the rest and greeted them with a smile.

“Sir Leylin, you- have you broken through?” Offa twisted his hands together, and appeared very excited.

“Yes, I have already reached the realm of rank 6,” Leylin smiled, and behind his back, the essence of his sun-like truesoul appeared, its piercing golden flame sweeping across everyone with powerful energy undulations.

“As expected, this is the power of a Breaking Dawn rank!” Offa’s eyes were bright and filled with tears, “our organisation’s long-cherished wish has finally been realised, Sir Leylin, no, your majesty Leylin! You are the pride of our Bloodline Alliance!”

Offa respectfully bowed, along with Wayde and even a seemingly unwilling Bevis.

“Your highness? Have I been promoted to a new title?” Leylin seemed to find it funny as he raised his hand to support Offa and the others up from their bow.

With this hierarchy, as Leylin had now advanced to a rank 6 warlock and impressively become a Warlock Emperor, so he was now called ‘his highness.

‘What a funny way to give titles, so when Bevis also advances, wouldn’t the Bloodline Alliance have two highnesses?’

Leylin humorously thought of the aftermath of that scene.

“1557 years, it’s already fully been 1557 years! Our Bloodline Warlock Monarch has finally appeared, but never had I thought that it would be his majesty, Leylin!” Wayde said, which made Bevis’ expression darken.

He was still a rank 5 Warlock, and did not have the strength to act against Leylin. He could only respectfully express his allegiance. No matter how he had schemed before, in front of this absolute strength, it was an insubstantial as a spider’s web that could be brushed away without leaving a trace.

“However, I can also reach that rank. In a hundred more years, very quickly…”

At this moment, Leylin’s gaze had also gone past Offa and Wayde, and had arrived on Bevis.

“Sire Bevis!”

“Yes!” Bevis put in his greatest effort to make his smile slightly more natural, but he disgracefully failed at doing so. His twisted expression made everyone who looked upon it want to laugh.

“Your fog giant bloodline, when amplified by another set of giant’s remains, you still have 87 years left before you break through! Work hard, you still have 65.1% chance of advancing to rank 6,” Leylin said with a smile, and he looked as if he had completely seen through Bevis.

‘How did he know?’ Bevis raised his head with amazement. He had always considered the fog giant’s remains that he had obtained from Offa as his final hope and trump card, and never had he thought that Leylin would be able to tell.

‘The gap between him and me has grown so big?’ Seeing that Leylin had a greater understanding of his bloodline than he himself, and had even calculated the probability of advancement, dealt a devastating strike to Bevis’ confidence.

Until now, he realised that his actions before made him look like an absolute clown, and he looked extremely ridiculous.

“Lord Leylin!” After Leylin and the others had welcomed them into the headquarters, Offa and his group saw Leylin sit down. They still stood there ramrod-straight, with solemn and respectful expressions on their face.

“Mm! I’ve come to the central continent today to relocate the Ouroboros clan, and also take care of some other trifling matters. After that, I might permanently settle there,” Leylin said. This surface Magus world was all the same to Leylin, and no matter how concentrated the elemental particles were, it would not be of any use to advancing his strength now.

“Relocate? Settle?! Is it because of the subterranean commerce? I’ve heard about it, but please let me speak bluntly, your majesty. Although we Warlocks rely on bloodline power, the south coast’s weak elemental concentration will definitely still affect us…” Offa and the others had anxious expressions on their faces.

Their long-awaited rank 6 Bloodline Monarch had finally appeared, and they thought they could exact their revenge on the central continent, so how could they let Leylin go so easily? Would they really have to wait another hundred years for Bevis? Seeing Offa’s expression, Leylin immediately knew what they were thinking in their heart of hearts. However, he did not expose them.

“Be at ease, I know what you are all concerned about. Before I leave, I’ll settle this matter completely!” Leylin indifferently waved his hand, but Offa and his group were still a little dissatisfied. They seemed to want to say something else, but they were all stopped in their tracks by Jeffrey’s most severe glare.

After Leylin had left, Jeffrey was surrounded by Offa and the others.

“What’s the matter? Why did you stop us?” Offa asked very calmly. They had been comrades for a very long time, so he was very clear about how Jeffrey was as a person and knew that he definitely had his own considerations.

“The earlier situation shocked me a little too much, and the news from the distant continent was rather delayed, so I couldn’t tell you all about the latest situation…” Jeffrey said with a wry smile, “Lord Leylin is not an average rank 6 Monarch, he is the person that we must pin all our hopes on…”

……

Afterwards, the shocking news began to spread throughout the entire central continent.

The Bloodline Union’s Warlock king, Leylin Farlier, had already stepped across the threshold of Breaking Dawn, and entered the realm of rank 6!

After the Morning Star space had verified this news, they immediately invited other organisations to attend Leylin’s celebrations. Many powerful Magi organisations and even some Monarchs had one-by-one expressed their intention to come themselves and meet with Leylin.

In a short while, the entire Phosphorescence Swamp once again became the gathering point of the central continent, and it seemed like all the Magi were discussing this matter, and how it would affect the central continent.

……

Sky City, the Drifting Garden.

“What?” the parchment in Weyer’s hands dropped to the floor, “How is this possible? He’s already advanced to rank 6, and reached the same status as the Monarch of the Skies? How long has he taken?”

“The Monarch of the Skies has already accepted Leylin’s invitation, and will definitely personally attend. This news is very trustworthy. This is reality, you must get used to it and accept it, my child!” A middle-aged Magi that looked rather similar to Weyers helplessly said.

He knew, of course, how great the shock this news would pose to a genius like Weyers. His small achievements were nothing compared to Leylin. That terrifying fellow’ speed at advancing made all the central continent’s geniuses despair and crumble.

“Being born in the same century as him is your greatest misfortune but also your greatest fortune! I hope you can step out from his shadow,” the middle-aged man looked at Weyers with undisguised concern in his eyes.

“I want to go as well, I want to see exactly how far the gap is between me and him!” Weyers gnashed his teeth, with an obstinate expression all over his face.

“Ah, you…” the middle-aged man helplessly sighed.

……

The reconstruction of Düz City had happened, under the Blazing Flame Monarch’s direction, many slaves put out their utmost effort and had completely rebuilt from the original ruins in the shortest period of time. The sacred flame had been relit, to represent the Blazing Flame Monarch’s strength and might.

Inside the city, within a giant sphere of flames, the golden blaze’s boiling hot temperature had the power to melt the surrounding buildings.

This phenomenon continued for nearly a few hours, and afterwards a slender figure emerged from the flames.

The person was wrapped in a red cloak, and had a small crown of flame upon their head. It turned out to be Melinda, who was now the Blazing Flame Monarch.

“Over the years, after consuming so many precious materials and the power of Dreamscape Elven stones, finally I have mended my soul to 80% of its original self…”

The present Melinda had not only regrow a new arm, her aura had also reached the stage of rank 6.

“Leylin Farlier! You really have given me a huge shock!” Melinda’s expression was very complicated. She had previously been able to take revenge thanks to Leylin’s help. However, he had attacked at the most crucial point and made her suffer enormous losses. Only now had she been able to recover.

“He’s already broken through to rank 6? How interesting! Even bloodline shackles and the Snake Dowager couldn’t stop him?”

As an old monster who knew of many ancient secrets, Melinda naturally knew what it meant to break through the bloodline shackles– he had the strength to resist the originator of his bloodline!

“It looks as if I can’t take my revenge now, and I even need to try to mend our relations,” Melinda licked her lips with a rich smile on her face.

“Just as well! That freshly caught little fellow would be a rather good gift!”

With Melinda’s thoughts and a loud clap, a fire elf immediately appeared before her.

“Almighty master, please bestow your orders upon me!”

The elf knelt on the floor with a respectful and humble attitude.

“That freshly captured witch, I think she’s called Natasha, command the others to erase her attitude and make her compliant! Put her as one of our guards!”

“Your orders will be put into effect!” The elf spread it’s blazing wings on its back and flew out from the door.

“I really am looking forward to the ceremony!” Melinda laughed brightly, and the fire in the rear hall suddenly grew several times more intense, as if it wanted to scorch the entire sky.

In just a moment, the entire central continent was full of hidden undercurrents as everyone turned their gazes towards the Phosphorescence Swamp.

Chapter 775: Year 0

Time passed in the blink of an eye. The world continued to turn and change. For someone like Leylin, he often would not feel the passing of time once he wholeheartedly devoted his heart and soul to something. While he was at work, hundreds of years could slip by stealthily.

Of course, to beings of laws who had life spans that were easily ten thousands of years long, such a tiny amount of time was perhaps considered just a nap. But to average humans, this meant more than ten generations of cycles of life and death.

This was a relatively long period of time even for Magi. A few low-ranking Magi perhaps didn’t even possess such a long life expectancy. Only the almighty high-ranking beings would pay no attention to the passing of time like that.

For the average Magus in the south coast or even the subterranean world, the news of the outside world that left the deepest impression on them in this long period of time, was probably the sudden rise of the Ouroboros Clan to power.

The present-day Ouroboros Clan had long broken away from the embarrassing phase of having only two or three small fry. Instead, it had grown to become an influential power that spanned across the entire Magus World. Its formidable influence even extended to the subterranean world.

The Farlier family that led the Ouroboros Clan was even acclaimed as the “first bloodline family”!

The powerful bloodline that had been passed down generations overshadowed every other Warlock family in the central continent. Their extraordinary military capabilities were quickly revealed.

Among Leylin’s direct descendants, this sort of prowess was made even more obvious. Even the bloodline energy of collateral relatives with many generations between them was enough to make other Kemoyin families benefit greatly.

Freya’s and Maggie’s families were evidently the ones receiving such benefits. They followed the Farlier family closely, taking up the role of their subordinates. They had also greatly purified their own bloodlines through marriages and other methods, increasing their proportion of high-ranking Warlocks higher and higher until they seemed to emerge like an endless stream.

This new generation of Warlocks possessed extraordinary bloodline energy, and zealously believed in Leylin as their bloodline originator. They became the foundation of the Ouroboros Clan’s rule.

Leylin, who was gradually seen as a divine being, had already become a part of the legends. He did not appear in public for decades at a time, and was surrounded by an air of mystery.

Syre and the other Warlocks, the sons of his second generation, slowly took control over the authority in the Ouroboros Clan.

A team of Warlocks clothed with garments with the Ouroboros motif was travelling through the subterranean world unhurriedly.

Behind them were many captives and supplies that had obviously been plundered.

“Chief Lucca! The headcount has been checked. Nothing has been left behind. I can confirm that their clan has been completely destroyed!” An average-looking blond Warlock reported, with a worshipful look in his eyes.

“Very well! Imprison them in chains. Prepare to sell them as highly-ranked slaves!” Lucca said without the slightest hint of hesitation. The Warlocks under him received his order as per normal, and carried everything out methodically, as though they were already very accustomed to all this.

“The subterranean world! Such a gloomy sky is rather hard to get used to indeed. Perhaps after this mission has been accomplished, I should apply to rest on the surface for some time…”

Lucca gazed at the dark rocky sky, and couldn’t help but to sigh to himself.

As an elder of the Ouroboros Clan, he was already more than 500 years old, and had experienced all the major events from the initial attack to the glory that followed. His youthful appearance was already unable to conceal the continuous exhaustion of his body.

“Indeed… Recalling all of this, it truly seems as though I am in a dream.”

Lucca couldn’t help but murmur as he glanced at the numerous captives and the troop that was moving forth once again.

Everything all began from when the lord had entered the Ouroboros Clan. It was as though he was born to be a strong contender. The speed at which he was promoted was so fast that it practically exceeded the limits of Lucca’s imagination.

“These damn lowly beings. How dare they disobey the Ouroboros Clan’s orders! They are simply digging their own grave! Of course, it’s only with Chief Lucca that we could have easily destroyed them!”

The blonde team member came to his side and said, trying to curry favor with him.

“Me?! Haha… In the past, perhaps I was still worth noticing with the strength of a rank 3 Warlock, but now… Don’t make fun of your Uncle Lucca!”

Lucca gazed at this Warlock as a doting look flashed across his eyes.

“In comparison to the true bloodline nobilities, the blood serpent clans and the Maggie family, my tiny achievements don’t count for anything, much less when compared to the Farlier family. After all, they directly inherited the lord’s bloodline.”

Lucca’s voice became extremely respectful. A look of admiration also spread across the young Warlock’s face.

“A rank 6 bloodline! He didn’t even need to work especially hard to enter the realm of Morning Star, and even Radiant Moon …”

The young man’s face was full of envy and self-disappointment, “If only I could also…”

“Lukard! Stop those unrealistic fantasies of yours! Lord Leylin didn’t have an outstanding bloodline in his early days, yet he made it to his current level all the same.”

Lucca’s tone turned rather stern, “Now, what you need to do is to look after the order!”

“Yes Chief!” Seeing how Lucca spoke so harshly and with a serious expression, the young Warlock immediately saluted him and ran to the back of the troop.

“This chap is really…”

Lucca shook his head, with a helpless expression in his eyes.

The rise of the Farlier family and the families of their subordinates was definitely a huge blow to the original bloodline nobilities.

Of course, under the crushing suppression of absolute strength, these bloodline nobilities didn’t even dare to let out a fart. They accepted the Farlier’s family unconditional authority with complete sincerity.

Something else that had risen into popularity at the same time was the abnormal worshipping of the ‘Emperor bloodline’. Of course, having such a mentality was perfectly normal to Warlocks.

It was a pity that the Farlier family’s control over their bloodlines had always been very strict. There were few cases of the bloodline outflowing to other families.

To date, only a scarce number of the original bloodline nobilities managed to obtain that special privilege.

A great many of the older nobilities had already predicted that the rising Emperor bloodline would shuffle the cards on the table. They were willing to pay any price in order to obtain the new and powerful bloodline.

Of course, they didn’t entirely dare to actually plot to seize the bloodline. Currying favour with the Farlier family and even the other subordinate families at all costs was their fundamental policy.

At the same time, anyone who tried to illegally covet for the Farlier family’s bloodline was bound to face a bloody death in their hands..

“Sigh… Although Lukard’s bloodline is considered rich, it’s nothing compared to the Emperor bloodline. Besides, with our family’s status, having the bloodline spread to us would only happen far away in the indefinite future…”

The slight thought of those noble descendents who followed like flies behind the ladies of the Farlier family all day long made Lucca’s scalp prickle with pins and needles.

He hadn’t had the heart to tell his junior this cruel reality, afraid that he would become discouraged.

“Sigh… Hopefully Lady Luck will smile upon that silly boy, and let him be favoured by one of the young ladies of the Farlier family. Even if he’s marrying into her family, it’s still acceptable…”

Lucca couldn’t help but begin to let his imagination run wild. He then laughed involunarily.

“Forget it, I think it would be more realistic to think about my earnings that the captures this round will bring me…”

Those in power in the Farlier family certainly were informed about this contradictory situation. However, the proliferation of a bloodline was originally a highly serious matter, and it would take time.

Thus, the only thing they could do now was to constantly develop new ways to gain benefits and challenge that contradiction.

Although deep in his heart, Lucca was not satisfied with his family not obtaining the new bloodline, he was clearly attracted to the profits he was about to gain.

Once it was confirmed that his profits from this round was enough for him to accumulate a certain value of contribution points, he would be able to even exchange them for precious materials for his dash towards the crystal phase. Lucca’s face was wreathed in smiles.

“This is the advantage of having control over the transaction channel! Who would have thought that I, Lucca, would actually have the opportunity to advance to rank 3 crystal phase…”

The profits that the Ouroboros Clan gained from the bilateral trade were considerably high. The result of this was the plentiful resources for training and cultivation. This alleviated the contradiction to a certain extent.

“Take note, we’re about to reach the City of Alabaster!”

Lucca’s voice made the entire troop turn restless. Even he himself couldn’t help but look forward to it.

The channel of the City of Alabaster was of great importance, and was practically the lifeline of the entire trade industry. Thus, the level of security was at its highest, and it was also the most bustling part of the city.

Although the exchanges between the subterranean world and at the surface had penetrated their society, both parties have never found a channel more convenient and faster than this one. Therefore, it further highlighted the importance of the location of the City of Alabaster.

While the astral gate could resolve the problem of only being able to transport important supplies and people within a smaller distance range, it would definitely suffer losses if huge amounts of trading content was involved.

Until now, the entire subterranean world had already came to a common understanding: whoever seized control of the City of Alabaster would reap enormous profits.

Under the temptation of such great benefits, perhaps the other underground powers who originally conducted the trading processes and were infringed on had never given up on lusting after the City of Alabaster.

Although they absolutely did not dare to launch a direct attack, they carried out many other little tricks.

The City of Alabaster loathed such powers who were like rats in the dark gutters. The moment they were discovered, they were sentenced to the firmest form of repression and annihilation.

But as long as the Ouroboros Clan continued to exploit the subterranean world, one would imagine that such resistance would not be lacking.

This time, Lucca was precisely acting under orders to eliminate one of the smaller powers by force.

Those superior overlords and the profiteers were not in the least bit afraid of these insignificant little pests. Their stance was unusually unanimous, which was a resolute decision to destroy them!

In the face of such overwhelming strength, no matter how determined and solemn the defending party was, their final outcome was death.

Lucca glanced at the line of captives behind him, the corners of his mouth twisting into a look of utter disdain.

Chapter 776: Ouroboros

The fight for profits and the crushing repression that came with it was bloody and merciless. Lucca didn’t seem to sympathize with these captives even in the slightest bit.

Perhaps those Warlocks of the new generation would have their doubts. However, having experienced the turmoil in the central continent, the hostility of the Magus World and the glory afterwards, Lucca definitely wouldn’t entertain such a mentality.

“When we’ve arrived at the City of Alabaster and delivered our task, everyone can have a good rest!” Lucca yelled loudly, leading to his men joyously echoing his words. It was interjected by cries of fear from the captives. This scene was rather amusing.

“Also, everyone knows the rules, right? You don’t need me to say anything.”

Lucca then shot a fierce look across the people behind him. There was an exceptionally distinct hint of warning in his eyes.

The other Warlocks instantly turned sluggish. Lukard, on the other hand, forced a smile, “Please rest assured! Everyone absolutely will not show disrespect to the three madams of the City of Alabaster…”

“Very well!” Lucca was clear of the situation at hand. Although he knew that many of the Warlocks were reluctant to comply, his facial expression turned gentle.

While the City of Alabaster was under the control of Lord Leylin’s subordinates, it was obvious that freedom was maintained to a certain extent. Not only was there no mutual interference between the Ouroboros Clan and the the City of Alabaster, Lord Leylin also had his own staff that only took orders from the Lord himself. They had a firm control over the other end of the bilateral trade.

If not for the newly formed organization which didn’t have much manpower, Lucca and the rest wouldn’t be doing such missions like exterminating people.

Even so, before entering the subterranean world, these Warlocks had been ordered repeatedly that it was necessary for them to comply to the commands from the City of Alabaster. They were not allowed to violate them.

As for the fellows who daringly attempted to go against these instructions, their bones had already been turned to ashes. Only their soul was left behind in the Endless Prison in the City of Alabaster, full of remorse…

Of course, there seemed to be some secret rumor going around that this situation had an some unclear connection to Lord Leylin and those three madams.

Although he was already quite convinced of it deep in his heart, it was evident that Lucca would not publicly announce it even till his death.

The vast cityscape of the City of Alabaster gradually started to appear ahead of the troop. The everlasting radiance at the top of the structures was exceptionally gorgeous and dazzling, and had an extremely special feel to it.

“Rumor has it that the City of Alabaster was established in an instant when the Lord fully put his powerful Magus abilities to use. It received blessings from the Lord himself, and now has an everlasting quality.”

As he watched streams of people enter, as well as the envious and stunned expression on the face of the young lads in the troop, Lucca felt a sense of pride that couldn’t be put into words.

“No matter how many times I’ve seen it, it’s really so hard to believe!”

Lukard came to Lucca’s side, his eyes filled with admiration. The ability to move mountains and suppress the seas was something that he could only look up to. Just touching the boundary of that sort of strength in his remaining years was hardly even possible.

“The city of underground commerce: Alabaster!” Lucca’s voice had a rare hint of agitation in it. “When we’ve delivered our task, we’ll be able to go home!”

“Go home! Go home!” The many youngsters cheered together.

“Bah!” At this moment, the sound of a frivolous spit could be heard amongst the cheers, and was exceptionally ear-piercing.

“Hm?!” Lucca glanced over to see where the sound came from. It was from a young Magus with a distinct aura of someone highborn. Only noble Magi or had such a special feel to them.

“I remember you! You’re the first wife’s son of the family we destroyed this time. You’re rumoured to possess a noble bloodline, and you’re the most highly-ranked slave here!”

“You bunch of damned invaders! The mighty underground Magus Alliance will not let you off!” Although there were wounds on the young Magus’ face, and his body was bound by forbidden magic chains, he still raised his head stubbornly.

“The underground Magus Alliance? That disordered resistance organization?” Lucca felt like laughing, “I’m sorry, your wishes won’t come true…”

“Everything is witnessed by the almighty Mother of the Abyss,” The youngster was evidently very resolute. The look on his face made Lucca furrow his brows.

This sort of firm resolution was not because he was rooted to his beliefs, but stemmed from a confidence in some kind of trump card.

“Then… Can you tell me what makes you so confident in that?” Lucca asked inquisitively.

In such a circumstance, he was simply unable to see any possibility in the tables turning.

This fellow was about to sold as a slave, and would just be adopted as a boy toy at best by some highly-ranked Magus who took a fancy to his appearance and bloodline. However, Lucca didn’t mind chatting with him for a while more.

“You’ll see!”

The young man shot a fierce look at Lucca before looking away.

“You damned swine. Who do you think you are now? What position are you in to actually try to rebel against the reign of the Ouroboros Clan?!” Lukard shouted harshly, itching to lash him with the whip in his hand.

“Forget it, Lukard.” Lucca grabbed Lukard’s hand, and his voice turned gentle, which was a rare sight. He felt that he was still capable of showing mercy and compassion when dealing with this loser.

“Hmph! When we arrive at the slave market, I’ll be sure to ‘take good care’ of you. You can spend the rest of your life rolling around in mud and becoming a lowly experimental subject and filthy animal…” Lukard gave the slave a menacing scare, making his face turn rather pale. His fist was clenched so tightly that his finger joints had turned white, yet he did not lower his head and continued to hold it high.

“This is the capital of commerce: the City of Alabaster! Remember to show your identification credentials and observe order, or you’ll meet with expulsion or even be arrested!”

A few of the Magi from the City of Alabaster were on patrol around the city gate. They shouted this with the help of sound amplification spells, allowing their voices to travel far.

The many merchants and Magi roaming about seemed to be very familiar with this. They lined themselves up in a composed manner, and everything appeared neat and orderly.

“Ahem! I have some contribution points from exterminating the enemy powers, as well as these highly-ranked slaves. How much are these worth altogether?”

At this point, even the other Warlocks in the team couldn’t help but beam with joy after calculating their profits.

However, strange distortions suddenly appeared in the sky in the distance. An enormous black stormcloud suddenly moved quickly across, and it had many strange skeleton runes at its centre.

“Let go of Vick!”

The angry bellow of an aged person could be clearly heard from the dark clouds, causing the area around the city gate to become chaotic. Lucca’s legs also started to turn wobbly, even though his strength was at rank 3.

“This… This feeling… Rank 5 ! No! A being that’s rank 6 or above! Wasn’t he just from a small family? Why would they be involved with this power?”

At this moment, the young slave had gotten a pleasant surprise, and was full of smiles.

“ Lord of the subsidiary clan! I’m here!” A crimson radiance emerged from the young man’s body, which was evidently some sort of indication of his location.

“A subsidiary clan? Is this a conspiracy? Or a coincidence?” Lucca’s thoughts were a mess.

King Arthur certainly wasn’t the only Breaking Dawn contender in the first layer of the subterranean world. However, the majority of the other monsters lived in seclusion, and spent their days cooped up in their laboratories. The City of Alabaster obviously wouldn’t offend them just for such insignificant benefits. Thus, both sides appeared to show restraint.

But now, a monster was clearly being dragged into the situation.

“How daring of you! You actually had the nerve to attack my affiliated clan!” Anger could clearly be felt radiating from within the black cloud.

The overbearing pressure of a solidified truesoul made all the Magi and Warlocks crouch on the ground. Only the slaves were left standing, their faces glowing with happiness.

“Haha… Haha… You lowly bloodline bastards. How dare you offend the noble young master, Vick! I will execute every single one of you! No! Before execution, I’ll let you enjoy all the torturous punishments the subterranean world has to offer!” The young man laughed maniacally.

“We’re done for! Unless Lord Leylin or King Arthur happens to be here, even the chief of the Lyas family cannot match up to a rank 6 being…”

Lucca’s pupils shone with desperation as he watched the white arm bone reach out from the dark cloud.

“We cannot tolerate anyone violating the interests of our bloodline Warlocks!”

At this very moment, a booming voice suddenly sounded from within the City of Alabaster.

The voice was accompanied by a wave of terrifying bloodline strength. A scarlet radiance washed across the entire sky, as though it was inexhaustible and everlasting, pushing the dark cloud to a side.

“What bloodline is this? It definitely isn’t the Giant Kemoyin Serpent!” A furious voice boomed from within the cloud, and there was even a hint of fear in it.

“It is I, Ouroboros! The limitless and everlasting snake: Ouroboros!” Lucca then saw the frighteningly enormous phantom of a giant snake burst out from the heart of the City of Alabaster, with a body that seemed to extend across the entire horizon.

Whether it was the gigantic body of the snake or the bizarre scales on it, it had a completely different appearance from a Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Yet, it made Lucca feel like bowing in worship.

“Is this… Is this the legendary Emperor bloodline?”

Even as a veteran Warlock of the Ouroboros Clan, it was his first time witnessing the Emperor bloodline explode firsthand.

But the familiar feeling from the bloodline and the orders originating from within his genes made Lucca bow down right away, his eyes involuntarily brimming with tears.

Having inherited Leylin’s bloodline directly, the Emperor bloodline was also conferred the ability to grant these Kemoyin descendants life or death.

It was only now, after coming face to face with the might of the Emperor bloodline, did Lucca thoroughly understand the actions of the other bloodline clans.

Such an astounding bloodline was indeed worth sacrificing everything for.

Chapter 777: Manderhawke Plate

“How is that possible? How could the City of Alabaster have a rank 6 Magus?” A voice of denial sounded from within the dark crowd. The owner of the voice clearly did not expect this, as he thought he had already performed a detailed background check on the City of Alabaster before he dramatically knocked down their door.

However, reality slapped him in the face.

“Nothing is impossible! Watch out you old bastard, the one and only consequence for those who offend the interests of the bloodline Warlocks is death!” The monstrous Ouroboros roared with an outburst of terrifying energy. It seemed still as eternity, yet was filled with infinite kinetic energy.

*Rumble!* The earth’s crust shook violently, roaring. Even space itself was warped and the elements were pushed away. The only thing that came out unscathed was the City of Alabaster, which was under the protection of the Ouroboros.

*Pss!* The dark cloud split open, exposing an elderly man in black robes.

“Impossible! How could a rank 6 acquire this power?” The elderly’s heart was full of regret. If he was given another chance, he would never choose to be Ouroboros Clan’s enemy. Sadly, he would not have the chance to do so.

“Go and repent in the astral plane!” The monstrous serpent swallowed the elder mercilessly, and a terrifying quake shot out. It took over ten minutes for the earth to settle completely.

The phantom of a mountainous infinite serpent shrank, and with a flash of light merged into the body of a teenager with black hair and eyes. These features were proof that he was a pureblood of the Ouroboros Clan.

“Master!” Lucca and Lukard greeted him respectively.

“Mm” He nodded and disappeared into the air.

“Captain, could that be…” Lukard asked Lucca with disbelief.

“If I’m not wrong, that master should be be the the son of the Monarch of Blood’s first wife— Master Syre! He’s actually achieved rank 6 at a few hundred years of age! The bloodline of the Master… Sigh…” Lucca looked at Lukard worriedly, and he could seen a tinge of loneliness from Lukard’s eyes.

“Legend says the pure bloodline of Master Leylin comes with two forms——the first is infinity, and the second is the world! So, that Master had inherited the bloodline power of infinity?” Lukard felt a sense of desolation. Both he and Syre were about the same age, but Leylin’s son’s achievements seemed out of his league.

Lucca had no choice but to shout for his attention. “Let’s stop thinking about that, hurry up and escort all the captives in.”

“No worries, Cap. No matter what bloodline they’ve inherited it’s good for the clan!” Lukard bowed to him with full respect, and soon started to manage the crowd.

Many of the captives were chased inside, while the arrogant teenage captive was totally dumbfounded, stuck in place. Needless to say, the fight caused a sensation. However, Syre just flew straight back into the heart of the city.

“Aunt Aegnis!” A noblewoman with elegant hair stood in the living room, the perfect image of a nobility.

“Congratulations, little Syre!” Aegnis’ eyes were full of surprise as she exclaimed, “You even entered the realm of Breaking Dawn directly. Leylin’s bloodline really is extraordinary… ”

“This is nothing to be proud of. After all, my brothers and sisters are just as powerful.” Syre smiled humbly.

“Yes, your siblings…” Aegnis had a benevolent smile on her face.

“I’ve still got lots of things to work on. Daniel advanced far before I did!”

“His path is already fixed, all he needs to do is to stick with the path and keep on upgrading himself. If I were to compare, your effort definitely deserves much more appreciation… ” Aegnis knew very well the differences between Leylin’s two bloodlines, but either once was terrifying beyond her imagination.

“Anyway, Belinda and Sophia are rather caught up in something, would you like to see them?”

Syre rejected her suggestion. “No need. Nobody will dare to take any action for at least some time now that that Magus’ plot is ruined. I want to return to the surface and visit Father.”

“Hmm… It’s being a long time since I last met that fellow!” Aegnis sounded dissatisfied as she talked about Leylin, and Syre could only smile wryly in response to the past affairs between his elders.

……

Within a laboratory in some unknown dimensional void, Leylin opened his eyes. They seemed to flash with black lightning.

*Buzz! Buzz!* Leylin’s body shook, and a layer of stone came loose and fell from the surface of his clothes.

[Beep! The analysis of the World of Gods’ apparatus has been completed! Time spent: 67 years and 13 months. ]

The A.I.Chip’s voice faithfully reminded him.

‘It’s been over 60 years… Together with removing memories and the preparations for the experiments, nearly 300 years have passed…’ Leylin’ s handsome face remained just the same as before, as though the power of time was completely lost on his body, ‘However, the wait was extremely worthwhile. I managed to gather the required data.’

Leylin was deep in thought. When he swallowed Beelzebub the power of laws he’d gained had caused great agitation and chaos to his own memories. This was especially true because Beelzebub was an old freak who’d lived for an unknown length of time. His memories contained all sorts of information, including many secrets about Gods. Leylin did not want to put it to waste, hence he’d had the A.I. Chip record every single thing. It was why it took so long for him to wake up.

“However, all my efforts were worth it, I can finally start something practical!” Leylin came to a astral gate with an excited expression on his face.

This specific astral gate was incomparably enormous. On top of that, there were many strange runes on it that included Leylin’s personal comprehensions of the power of laws.

“Gods!” An ancient yet dazzling light shot from Leylin’s hand, merging into the huge stone gate.

*Buzz! Buzz!* The entire gat shook violently, and there were even some strange energy undulations in the laboratory. With his powerful soul force, Leylin connected to the entire astral plane in a moment.

The vast sea of stars which were as old as history washed over Leylin’s own soul force. This feeling was rather different than his previous experiences, if not for his near rank 7 soul force the destructive power of the astral plane would have completely erased him.

The splendid nebulae seemed to ebb and flow continuously, distorting numerous rings of stars. It was like Leylin’s body was a huge black hole, engulfing everything around him.

“This kind of extreme long-distance projection serves to be a great challenge for the soul force of a Magus!” Leylin remained calm, his soul force seemingly indestructible. He sat and watched the galaxies flow away before him. Finally, after what felt like a century, his expression changed as he almost saw the end of the astral river.

“Such a special feeling…” A simple premonition had Leylin sighing with exclamation, “The Magus World and World of Gods are like oceans at opposite ends of a galaxy. No wonder those ancient Magi were still attached to this universe.”

In spite of his vast database, Leylin was still awed by the marvelous scenery in front of him after the indescribable sensation faded. There was a dense crystalline wall in front of him, shimmering like a well-constructed beehive. In the astral river, it looked magnificent and infinite.

Within the crystal wall was a radiant light, the light of the Gods!

“Ugh…” Leylin’s body trembled, and a phantom Targaryen appeared immediately, its slit eyes filled with desire and familiarity.

“The World of Gods! The world origin force of such a powerful foreign world would be so great… Not to mention the law of devouring originates from here…” Leylin appeared to be rather calm despite every single cell in his body longing for it. Deep in his heart, he maintained his cold determination.

“This crystal wall system… “ Leylin’s soul force encircled around the huge crystal wall, feeling the immeasurable depths of its power. “The culmination of the worlds origin force, and there’s also the conscients of Gods there…”

Leylin’s expression turned more solemn the more he sensed, “It stubbornly rejects everything from outside, and has blocked all connections from the outside world. It’s as solid as steel, and just as unyielding…”

With a simple probe Leylin understood clearly that even the creator of this system couldn’t destroy it, of that he was pretty sure. “It’s impossible to break through such a system, the only way is to use Beelzebub’s method to smuggle myself in…”

“Beelzebub only needed to leave the World of Gods, and he was a native himself. It’ll be much more difficult for me. It’s only expected that I had to spend 300 years of simulation to find a safe method of passing through…

“Manderhawke plate!” Layers of virtual light gathered in Leylin’s palm, forming a circular disc.

On the disc were peculiar patterns, especially the huge chipped edge, and it looked like it was bitten off by some unknown creature.

In the memories of Beelzebub, this was the key to secretly pass through the crystal wall system!

“The main material plane in the World of Gods also had strong isolating power, it’s hard even for the Gods to transfer their powers. It was the same for Beelzebub who was located at the ninth of hell…”

Leylin recalled this bit of information that the A.I. Chip had organised.

Chapter 778: Exploring the World of Gods

The path of the gods, known as the path of faith, was the foundation of the laws of the World of Gods. Whether it was gods, demons or even devils, their desire for believers and souls was frightening.

The competition on the main material plane had been fierce from the very beginning. Compared to the gods who had resources and money to spare, a devil like Beelzebub was already on the losing end and had no choice but to wrack his brain for ideas. His reputation in the main world was awful as a result.

However, this all changed one day.

Beelzebub obtained a fantastic divine device— The Manderhawke plate! He had named it himself, since he had never seen any description of this device in history, although its effects were extremely powerful.

This Manderhawke plate had the miraculous effect of reducing the suppressive effects of a world boundary.

In other words, if Beelzebub wanted to transmit his godly power to the main material plane and would normally be taxed 90% of his power, the Manderhawke plate would reduce the amount he needed to pay to 10% or even fewer.

This consumption was much cheaper and convenient for him as compared to the gods of that realm.

Because of this advantage, Beelzebub had been able to develop and flourish in the main world, gathering large amounts of the power of faith and souls, establishing his status in hell in one fell swoop.

Of course, the gods were no fools. After a period of investigation, they had banded together and complete purged of the organisation that worshipped him.

Evidently, Beelzebub who resisted the many gods alone had no choice but to get lost. Not only did all the resources he had amassed in the main material plane disappear, with only a few followers slipping past the net and on their last legs, he wasn’t doing well in hell either, where he was suppressed by the other hell sovereign kings.

Thankfully, the secret of the Manderhawke Plate had not been leaked, or else there was no way he could settle this matter so easily.

Even after all this, Beelzebub was already paranoid and did not dare take any more action in the main material plane.

He, who had the Manderhawke Plate, set his sights on areas outside the World of Gods.

In the limitless astral plane, there were many intellectual beings. The power of faith they could generate was a huge temptation for him, and it was even better because no gods or other enemies could notice this!

After a period of experiments, Beelzebub succeeded.

Of course, after that, he had been unlucky enough to meet Leylin. His main body was probably grievously injured and now in a deep sleep, and he could even die if he was unlucky. After all, hell was not a peaceful place.

“The power to extinguish the barriers between worlds…” The glowing disc arrived at the periphery of the crystal wall, where numerous runes were flickering. It seemed to attract some existence within the wall, which made the area surrounding the wall soften. This made Leylin wonder if this situation would spread to the rest of the wall.

“No! This isn’t from a flaw in the laws. This was a way out left behind from the very beginning, set up during the design process…” With Leylin’s foresight, he immediately saw how extraordinary the Manderhawke plate was.

“Based on Beelzebub’s thoughts, the Manderhawke plate could very well be an imitation of the most powerful deity device in the World of Gods, the Clay Plate of Destiny. This is very possible. Perhaps this plate might even be a part of the Clay Plate of Destiny…” Leylin’s eyes burned with fervour.

What he had in his hands was obviously not the real Manderhawke plate, or else he would long have been able to enter the World of Gods. Why would he have needed to go through all this trouble?

The shining plate in Leylin’s hands was merely a specific device made by the A.I. Chip from Beelzebub’s memories, as well as the precise calculations down with knowledge on the equipment of the World of Gods.

With data from experiments on the real thing, as well as long periods of observing and doing research to imitate it, Leylin had great confidence in this imitation.

Things were as expected. Under the rays of the fake Manderhawke Plate, the region of the crystal wall here was already beginning to melt, revealing a large passageway.

“It was this easy?”

Leylin furrowed his brows, but still separated a thread of a soul seed, which disappeared into the pathway.

“Get lost!” The moment the soul seed touched the crystal wall, a terrifying voice sounded, bringing with it a powerful isolating conscient.

*Pu!* The seed was immediately annihilated, and even the Manderhawke Plate was floating unsteadily.

“Has the World Will of the World of Gods awoken? No, this is just its subconscious mind! This extent is just…”

Instantly, Leylin knew what had happened. This was an instinctive reaction of the crystal wall, which repelled souls like Leylin who tried to enter. His different type of soul force was immediately discovered, without leaving any room for doubt.

“You’re the one who should scram! You’re just a sleeping subconscious will. Scram!” Two streaks of black lightning shot out from Leylin’s eyes, his black hair flying while he looked to have turned into an ancient demon.

“Hss…” The tremendous body of a Targaryen emerged behind Leylin, its energy undulations and rank 7 will resisting the crystal wall.

*Buzz Buzz!* At this moment, the Manderhawke Plate in Leylin’s hands flashed and completely enveloped the entire area, not allowing any information to be transmitted.

Near rank 7 power was something that even the wills of small worlds could only somewhat resist. While the World of Gods was incomparably powerful, it was still slumbering, and there was only a small region resisting. It had not activated its full force and the Manderhawke Plate had even removed a portion of its sensing abilities, so therefore it was at its weakest.

*Pak!* In that moment, a surge of powerful emotions disappeared, revealing a small space.

“Now’s the time!” Leylin’s eyes flashed, and numerous soul seeds separated and disappeared into the crystal wall.

*Boom!* Practically the very moment the soul seeds disappeared into the pathway, the entire Manderhawke Plate crumbled into powder. Leylin was sent flying backwards, numerous terrifying wounds already appearing on his body as he turned pale.

Fresh blood spurted everywhere, but it returned to Leylin’s body at an even faster rate, as if his body had become a huge magnet. The terrifying injuries disappeared in an instant, though Leylin’s face was still obviously pale.

“Just the backlash from a small portion of the crystal wall reduced me to this state, despite the protection of the Manderhawke Plate…” Leylin’s eyes were filled with admiration. He had not attacked the wall forcefully before, or else he would have met the counterattack of the crystal wall and fury of the gods, which would have turned him into ashes in an instant.

This sort of powerful ability not only failed to make Leylin afraid, but it left him longing to best it.

However, Leylin’s sighs of admiration disappeared in an instant. He was now putting effort into maintaining the connection with his soul, and the terrifying consumption continued.

Unlike separated truesouls, one couldn’t sever the support to a soul seed if they wished to maintain it. Even for an existence like Leylin, the consumption from behind the barrier in the World of Gods was astonishing even though things had happened only for a short moment.

The A.I. Chip was now quickly recording. The process of traversing through the crystal wall was not smooth, and soon information on the soul seeds being annihilated was transmitted.

[Soul seed #1 extinguished.]

[Soul seed #2 extinguished. Estimated time that host can maintain support: 31h 24min 12s.]

However, this lessened the consumption on his end, allowing Leylin to go on for longer.

*Swish!* An orange meteor streaked through the night skies, descending in a dark forest.

“This is… the World of Gods?” Leylin’s soul seed scanned the surroundings. It was a dark forest, and his blaming flames had already caused the area arounding him to be charred, creating an empty area there.

“An enormous malicious intent, as well as these laws!” Leylin’s soul seed did all it could to gather data, “The terrifying World Will of the World of Gods might only be suppressing me unconsciously, but that’s enough to suppress the range of the soul force’s scanning to within 10 metres… On top of that, these limitations on otherworldly power…”

Leylin could clearly sense that this was an exceptionally strict world, with extremely powerful limitations on otherworldly strength. Even if Morning Star Magi came here, they would not possess powerful strength, and it was impossible for them to do what they could in the Magus World.

‘The energy particles are very stable here and easy to manipulate… The exemplaries of this world must find it hard to break through individually. The norm should be to work in groups, ten adventurers in a group would be a good arrangement… Even if my main body comes, I’d probably be suppressed by one to two ranks and only be able to exhibit strength of Morning Star or Radiant Moon… Under such stringent conditions, how terrifying would the gods who have been able to break through be?’

At this point, Leylin suddenly found that he had underestimated the gods.

Their strength far exceeded his expectations, especially since he was being suppressed by such a large degree.

“Ovanna, look! Is that a meteor? It landed in the forest!”

In a little village by the forest, a little boy with some freckles on his nose glanced at the sky, suddenly speaking to the pig-tailed girl beside him, “I’ve made a decision. I’m going to look for it!”

“Tiff, have you gone mad? The priest has already said that a meteor is a bad omen!” Ovanna glanced her friend in worry.

“Priest…” Ovanna’s eyes showed her fear. “That’s true! Then I’m not going!”

The meteor from before had evidently brought a large change to the village. Many adults gathered, looking worried, and all began to pray nearby a little altar in the village.

Ovanna and Tiff quickly separated, but what the young girl did not notice was that after parting ways, Tiff ran outside the village, an excited look in his eyes.

Chapter 780: Encirclement and Repentance

“The oracle said this place has been polluted by a foreign force. A purge is necessary!” At the middle of the group of knights was an old man wearing the attire of a bishop, looking devout and pious. He seemed extremely stern.

“Lord Bishop, we have completely surrounded the area!” A knight reported respectfully after urging his horse over. He was chiseled, his features as sharp as a knife.

“Good! Divine corps, be prepared to coordinate with each other. Don’t let even a single heretic escape!” The bishop waved his hand. Numerous youthful and resolute priests dressed in white ceremonial clothing followed behind him, followed by the groups of knights in an orderly manner.

A serious crisis immediately enveloped the little town, but the residents did not notice at all.

“Hm? An exemplary polluted by the power of other laws…” Though his detection abilities were largely limited, Leylin still sensed the people surrounding the village. It was a pity that there was nothing he could do. In his current state, he needed Tiff’s help just to get out of the forest. There was no way to break through this besiegement.

“The surveillance by the gods is extremely strict!” Leylin exclaimed in admiration. He’d noticed the altar when he’d first entered the village, as well as the laws it emitted.

Of course, there were some differences between the laws here and those of beings from other worlds. Perhaps a more appropriate name for it would be divine force.

With the protection of divine force, the whole village was akin to a domain. Though the effects were extremely weak compared to a real domain, they had similar characteristics.

“A foreign being like me would be discovered the moment I enter the domain!”

Leylin sighed, “Unless I find an area where the truly faithless gather or evade places with altars or shrines, there’s nowhere for me to hide when I’m in this form… It’s a pity that it’s impossible…”

In Beezlebub’s memories, practically all intellectual beings of the World of Gods had faith in various gods.

Here, being faithless was very frightening. Even those followers of another religion or those who had faith in the devils were treated better than the faithless.

It was rumoured that after death, the souls of the faithless were not accepted by any gods, and could only howl and wail as they were crucified while alive.

“Faith in the gods spreads like numerous nodes throughout the World of Gods. Each follower’s soul will be branded by the gods!”

Here, massacres were obviously not forbidden. However, all research done on souls were seen as a blasphemy to the gods, and those discovered doing so would be burnt at the stake.

It was fine to kill the followers of the gods, but if he tried to influence their souls in the slightest degree, the gods would notice in an instant.

The fury of having one’s child touched by someone else was definitely enough to induce fury from the gods.

“The souls of priests, deity officials, devout followers and sacred warriors must definitely not be touched, or else their god will be provoked and surely won’t take this lying down!”

This was the most important lesson Leylin had learnt from Beezlebub’s memories.

“In other words, in the World of Gods, it’s impossible to massacre and devour souls in order to quickly regain strength. If I do that, there’d be something like a tracker on me, and I’d be discovered by the gods no matter where I go. Of course, in a foreign world, my soul strength isn’t much. I won’t be able to escape…”

After determining the situation, Leylin strangely felt relaxed.

He was only a soul seed at this point, and it being exterminated would not really affect the main body much. He could make use of this opportunity to gather more data.

“Come at me, sacrificers to the gods!”

A streak of dark red flashed from the broken sword, with a bloodthirsty radiance.

……

The sounds of the neighing of horses, high-pitched roars, the blood-curdling screams and profound pleas for help.

Tiff used the back of his hand which was cleaner and rubbed his eyes, and then yawned.

He, who had been awakened by the sounds, saw the fire outside his window. The trotting of horses, the slamming of doors and shouts lingered by his ear like the mumbles of a devil.

“What’s going on? Is this a nightmare?” Tiff’s mind was in a state of confusion, unable to react to what was going on.

“What did you come out for? Get back in there!” After Tiff left the room, he was immediately pushed roughly back in.

On his father’s face was a grimness and solemness that Tiff had never witnessed before.

But before he could obediently return to his room, a tall, handsome steed rammed into his garden.

Mounting the horse was a knight wearing steel armour. The luxurious armour made out of steel rendered Tiff speechless, for this usually belonged to lords who were knights or some family heirloom belonging to nobility, such as barons.

Even the baron who was closest to this area might not have goods of such quality.

Tiff’s eyes were full of fear and envy. Meanwhile, he also noticed a crest on the armour— this was the crest of the Spring Water Goddess!”

“It’s the holy knights of the Spring Water Goddess! What are they doing here?”

It had to be said that these holy knights used to be Tiff’s idols, but what they were doing now was just destroying his dreams.

“Esteemed lord, may I know…”

Tiff’s father gathered his courage and approached the knight. Before he could finish his sentence, however, he was ruthlessly sent flying and crashed to the ground.

“I’m only saying this once. All residents are to gather at the altar. Everyone!”

The knight burst through Tiff’s front door, and what followed was the sound of trunks and boxes being rummaged through. Tiff’s mother, brothers and sisters were chased out.

Following his father and the rest of his family, Tiff left through the front door and headed to the heart of the village to gather.

It was only at this point that Tiff noticed, stunned, that the other villagers had been expelled from their homes and, like flowed like a stream to converge at the center of the village.

“What– What’s going on?” Tiff still had no idea of what exactly was happening. All he knew was that his mother had a tight hold on his hand, to the point that it was painful.

In front of him was his father, whose expression was dark and full of uneasiness.

Even when the famine had happened for the past few years, and when the tax officers had come to the village, Tiff had not seen such an expression on his father’s face before.

The many villagers gathered like herded sheep. The knights raised their torches and surrounded them, shining brightly in the night sky.

Around the knights were also many priests.

Their clothes were even more extravagant than the priest he had seen previously in the village. To make it simple, all of them must be amazing people.

“Cough cough… cough cough…” The solemn atmosphere as well as the arrival of the deity officials and knights caused Tiff to begin to feel fear, though he had no reason why.

“Lord bishop, all the villagers have gathered. This is the village chief.”

A knight with golden patterns on his armour tossed an old man who was trembling hard before the bishop.

“Lord bishop, our Kahn Village has always been piously worshipping the Spring Water Goddess and never dared go against her!”

From Tiff’s perspective, this village chief who was usually very capable was like a baby here, weeping and sniffing in front of the old bishop.

“The god has taught us to treat every follower with love!”

The old bishop kindly helped the village chief up and even bent to his knees to help brush off the soil, immediately giving rise to feelings of gratitude from the chief.

“The reason I’m here is because I was instructed by the god to purge this area of foreign forces.”

After the chief calmed down, the bishop expressed his purpose in coming here.

For some reason, Tiff saw his father’s body swaying and almost crumpling to the ground. Even his mother was beginning to sob quietly, and the surrounding villagers looked as if the world was ending.

It was only a long time later that Tiff knew that the gods were very brutal when it came to dealing with foreign forces. Even the commoners in the area that were affected had terrible, miserable conclusions to their lives.

Of course, he was a mere child now. All he knew was that after the bishop who seemed very influential spoke, the many villagers, including the chief himself, went limp and fell to the ground, unable to even plead.

“Oh mighty Spring Water Goddess, your humble servants piously offer sacrifices to you. Please open your godly eyes and differentiate the foreign force here!”

In front of the altar in the little village, the bishop devoutly prayed. Immediately after, milky-white rays of light surged from the altar, bringing with it a holy, clean luster.

“Come here one by one so we can separate you. The god will not misidentify anyone.”

The old bishop announced. Immediately after, those knights began to grab hold of the villages, pressing them down under the altar and forcing them to kneel and repent.

The villagers were forced to go through with this ceremony under the altar one after another, and the rays of light on the altar stayed white.

“Next!” The old bishop looked ruthless, as if nothing in the world was worth him frowning or hesitating over. The holy knights were like demons, only knowing to complete their tasks robotically.

Finally, it was Tiff’s family’s turn.

First was his father and sister, and then Tiff.

Tiff knelt on the cool ground, feeling very uncomfortable.

“Quick, repent!” A tremendous force could be felt on his back, and he had no choice but to bend down.

“Mighty Spring Water Goddess, Bynx, you are the god of all spring waters, and also the stars in the sky, the one who loves us like a mother. I confess to you…”

Chapter 781: Eruption

Tiff was muddle-headed as he prayed, but he’d already performed this ceremony of repentance in the past. Even if he stammered over his words, there were generally no mistakes.

“It can’t be!” “We’ve found it!”

However, Tiff found that the aura in his surroundings had changed afterwards. The gazes gathered on him were like those of wolves, causing every hair on his body to stand on end in his nervousness.

“What’s going on?” Tiff raised his head, stunned. He immediately saw that the milky white lights from the altar had turned a demonic dark red.

“Foreign force!” Tiff felt his neck being grasped, and his entire body was yanked into the air.

The old bishop in front of him now looked incomparably sinister. He could faintly see his father wailing before he was struck to the ground. Now even the villagers isolated his family members, keeping away from them like they had the plague.

“No! Once more, please try it once more! My Tiff definitely would not blaspheme against the goddess!” The cries lingered in Tiff’s ears, but the grasp on his neck was becoming increasingly tight, to the point that he was feeling suffocated.

At this moment, the palm released its hold on him, and long-awaited fresh air poured into his windpipe. Tears and mucus flowed out of him. “Say it, Heretic! How did you go against the teachings of the goddess?”

Thee bishop’s brows furrowed slightly at the sight of this heretic.

This heretic’s strength was much too weak and was incomparable to the powerful blasphemers from before. Such a small threat would not have warranted the goddess descending and commanding them to act.

“Truth spell!” A dot of golden light flew from the bishop’s hands, disappearing into Tiff’s forehead.

Following which, Tiff found his mouth beginning to move involuntarily, answering all of the bishop’s questions.

Tiff’s life had been very normal to the point that it was boring. When he was asked about the exploration earlier in the day, the bishop’s breathing evidently became rougher.

“Quick, surround the kitchen at the back of this home!”

A tremendous force flew out, and Tiff felt like his body was floating high up in the clouds before falling into a gigantic iron hoop, making his whole body ache everywhere.

With the escort of many soldiers, Tiff and his family members arrived in front of their house.

Immediately after, waves of knights rushed forward as if meeting with some great enemy, finding a mottled iron sword.

“Lord bishop!” The leading knight respectfully offered up the sword with both hands.

The powerful, sinister strength from the iron sword caused the bishop to frown, “A demonic item, or a temptation from the devils? Even appraisal techniques are useless on it.”

Though he had no idea what the characteristics of this item was, the bishop had already decided what would be his current target.

“If I purify this item, the favour and care I get from the goddess should be able to raise my ranking as a priest by a whole grade, right?”

The bishop’s eyes showed how bewitched he was by this notion before he repented piously, “Oh mighty Spring Water Goddess, please forgive your servant for his greed…”

For some reason, there were no strange changes to the iron sword that Leylin’s soul seed was residing in. It docilely allowed the bishop to add all sorts of seals to it, and with numerous knights escorting it, they arrived at the altar in the village.

“This child’s soul has already been polluted by the power of the foreign force…”

The bishop stood before the altar, stating his final judgment on Tiff.

“Burn him to death!” “Burn him to death!” “Burn him to death!” Before Tiff could react, the many villagers began to howl maliciously.

Such a zealous atmosphere and the large difference from what Tiff was used to seeing caused him to break out in tears.

Even his family were bound by the infuriated villagers on wooden crosses that had been made on the spot.

Tiff had a very bad of feeling of what was going to happen.

“No! Please forgive them. I… I did nothing! I only brought an iron sword back. I’m willing to repent for that!”

Tiff wailed and pleaded for the last time, “For the goddess’ sake, you can punish me, but please let my family off!”

“The family of the heretic must also be purified!”

What answered him was the bishop’s grave expression.

Immediately after, amidst large amounts of flames and the cries of children, Tiff fainted in his fear.

“Mighty goddess, your servant piously invites you to descend…”

After burning Tiff’s family at the stake, the bishop began to pray in front of the altar devoutly with his other sacrifices.

As the chief offender, Tiff and that iron sword contaminated by evil needed to be personally dealt with by the goddess herself.

“Hm… is this the path of faith?”

The soul seed in the iron sword was watching all that the bishop was doing, “Using religious ceremonies to spread fanatic behaviour, while gathering the extreme emotions and soul force emanated from the followers…”

Leylin calmly analysed.

In his current state, he basically could not resist at all. Hence, he placed all his effort on gathering intel.

Through this period of observation, the details on the surface of the World of Gods were shown in front of him, clearer than Beelzebub’s memories.

“First is the surroundings. Otherworldly power is limited to a very harsh degree. The regular beings here, with even the most common peasant, has a body that surpasses that of regular people in the Magus World by a huge degree, and even by several times. And then, we have the priests and knights here…”

Leylin could clearly sense the strength of another existence’s laws from the priests.

Though this path was very similar to Purgatory World’s parth of offerings, there were still differences.

The chief difference was that the usage of the power of faith was very wide-ranging. Just the slight disturbance he had caused had allowed Leylin to see so many of these so-called priests.

The number of people here were obviously gathered only from the surrounding regions.

If power was to be poured into all of the priests there were, the many dignitaries of Purgatory World would go bankrupt, and yet it was a simple matter for the gods here.

Furthermore, there were differences when compared with the trade of equivalent exchange of the path of offerings. The Sacrificers here all thought themselves to be the servants of the gods and believed they had very low statuses.

This situation aroused Leylin’s interest, urging him to find out more.

“Furthermore… as there are too many, the gods can’t focus on every single one of their followers, unless they are invited to do so or if there are blasphemous souls…”

Leylin watched the bishop that began to pray, the feeling of an existence of laws descending beginning to tingle in the area.

“I need to do something!”

He made his decision, and then placed his focus on Tiff.

Leylin, whose body was now but a broken sword, had no way to resist. He needed some sort of medium.

Come to think of it, this guy was rather suitable.

Blood and fire! And then there were the malicious smiles from the villagers, knights and priest… This was what Tiff saw in his dreams.

The heavy feeling of being suppressed was like a huge mountain, destroying this child’s soul.

In this situation, manipulating Tiff was just too easy for Leylin.

“Hey kid, do you want to take revenge?”

Many flames shot out all of a sudden, converging into a huge face that stared at Tiff.

“Of course! No matter what you are, whether a demon or devil, it’s fine even if you want my soul. Please give me the strength to take revenge!”

Tiff began to weep in his dreams as he knelt.

“How astute. I like it!” The flaming human face smiled evilly, turning into a gigantic blazing winged serpent that disappeared into Tiff’s body.

“Remember. My godly name is Kukulkan— the feathered serpent Kukulkan! Your soul, flesh and everything shall, from hereon, belong to me!”

A voice sounded in Tiff’s mind, and immediately after, he felt as if his body was lit with flames, and felt like it was burning.

“What’s going on?” “This kid’s body is burning!”

The clamour around him caused Tiff to open his eyes once more, but the charred crosses not too far away only resulted in tears of disappointment.

The boiling hot feeling did not dissipate as Tiff stared at his palm. This was no longer like a human. Strangely enough, there were scales with flames around, looking like a palm of vengeance that had come straight from hell!

“So… it wasn’t a dream!” Tiff mumbled.

At this moment, the bishop and knights were startled by Tiff’s appearance. From their point of view, he had suddenly been enveloped by a layer of fire, turning into some demonic thing that had come from hell.

“Kill him!” Holy radiance flickered from the bodies of a few knights as they brandished their large swords and charged towards him.

“Ah…” Tiff yelled, and the seals on the broken sword that Leylin had attached himself to crumbled, and then fell into his hands.

“Die!” The broken sword slashed and created a few mysterious red streaks. Immediately after, the knights’ bodies fissured, with blood and innards flying everywhere alongside the horrified cries of the villagers.

As if there was a limitless amount of strength being poured into from the hilt of the broken sword, Tiff was like a death god as he reaped the lives of the surrounding knights.

“His life rays have gotten more powerful. He’s at least comparable to a level 15 officer!”

“Goddess Bynx, how is this possible?”

“Goddess, please bless us!” The many knights and deity officials yelled in fury.

However, Tiff cared nothing at all for things like this. His mind had already been filled with the thirst for revenge.

One after another, the enemies were destroyed under his bloody red field of vision, which then focused on the bishop.

“Mm! Let’s end this with a final experiment. Innate ability: Devour!”

With Leylin’s will, Tiff’s arm grabbed onto the bishop’s shoulders.

Following which, his flesh began to melt at a visible rate.

Chapter 782: A Call from Dreamscape

“The goddess… will not let you off!” The bishop said as he put up his final struggle. His face was filled with the fanatic expression of someone who had died for a good cause.

Leylin simply did not give a hoot about all of this. “Well! The transformation efficiency of his flesh is not bad. His divine force is also rather decent. Next up… the soul, the most important part!”

However, when the broken sword came into contact with the bishop’s soul, the situation changed drastically!

“You… You actually have the cheek to profane my soul?” The excruciating pain from somewhere deep within his soul made the bishop come to his senses. A mix of despair and resolution surfaced on his face, “Almighty goddess! Your devotee sincerely offers his own life, and longs for your arrival! Divine art— Deity’s Descent!”

The powerful counter-attack made Tiff take many steps back in succession. The summoning ceremony that had been interrupted resumed, now moving very quickly. After all, the bishop had been working himself before but now the goddess only needed to take the initiative to descend.

“Indeed… The soul of a devotee is a forbidden zone.” Leylin gave a forced laugh, and immediately sent a command to Tiff’s brain, telling him to go far away and leave the iron sword with the soul seed behind.

‘My power has almost been used up. Leaving now is useless, so I might as well contribute whatever strength I have left!’ The broken sword suddenly turned scarlet. Molten iron started to dissolve and finally formed the outline of a humongous devil.

The badly damaged demonic wings, gigantic compound eyes, the devilish hand which had six fingers on it, and even the law of gluttony it grasped was all identical to the Sovereign King of Gluttony.

“After all, I also control Beelzebub’s power of gluttony. Passing off as him will be far too easy…”

Leylin took control over the body of devil and looked over at the bishop in front of him — just that he was now lifeless. Yet, his body floated eerily in midair.

A powerful conscient was being implanted in the bishop’s body, filling him with some sort of divine sensation.

Soon after, Leylin saw a pair of golden pupils.

“Now!”

Leylin did not dare to actually meet the other party face-to-face, or his flaws would definitely be seen. At the very moment when the Spring Water Goddess descended, he suddenly manipulated the body of the devil to explode spontaneously!

*Boom boom!!* The scorching flames, along with the power of laws, completely wiped this tiny village from existence.

Even the residents in the neighbouring towns could see the orange sky in the distance.

In the entire Kahn Village, not a single soul survived except for Tiff.

This incident was determined to be caused by the invasion of a devil. Through facilitation by the Spring Water Goddess Church, a new round of exercises took place across the entire central continent to root out heresies.

Of course, all of this didn’t have any relation to Leylin.

*Crash!* The huge door of the astral gate disintegrated inch by inch. Leylin sat on the ground, his face as white as a sheet.

Weakness spread across every part of his body. Ever since he had transformed into a laws being, such a feeling was already very rare.

“The World of Gods is indeed incomparably powerful. A mere force that wouldn’t even be able to support the soul for a day almost led to excessive depletion, and endangered my origin!” Leylin smiled bitterly.

“Moreover, this experiment has proven that any other force is extremely conspicuous in the World of Gods. It simply cannot be concealed, and the consumption is way too high, which is disproportionate to the benefits…”

There was a profound look in Leylin’s eyes.

‘The suppression and hostility in the World of Gods is something that even I am incapable of resisting against in my current state. In that case, it seems that the best method at present would be to walk the old path.’

After this experiment, Leylin had already made up his mind.

In the World of Gods, it was necessary to adopt a brand new format, which would be different from his former expeditions in the other worlds.

“I’ll make my moves through an independently acting body, and he cannot receive any kind of power from the host body. Also, it’s necessary for him to grow entirely based on the laws of the World of Gods.”

Leylin stroked his chin.

“When he matures to a certain level, at least rank 7, then we can coordinate and work together to break through the crystal wall shackles.”

“If we’re going to do this, the Truesoul Splitting Technique that Melinda provided previously still needs to be improved on. Additionally, the method to maintain control over the body must be experimented as soon as possible.”

A multitude of ideas emerged from Leylin’s mind, and was arranged according to the level of importance.

Only when all of this was complete and the experimental data fully recorded did Leylin then step into the outside world.

“Yes!” Leylin shut his eyes and immediately knew of Syre’s breakthrough using the sensing abilities of his bloodline origin.

“He’s already advanced to rank 6? The limitless and everlasting power of Ouroboros seems to be highly compatible with Syre!”

Although his pace was slower than the eldest son Daniel, Leylin was extremely satisfied.

Both of his children that branched out from his bloodline had grown healthily, and even had a strong grip on the other Warlock families in the Magus World.

It was a pity that such lightning-speed advancements were only possible before these two bloodlines reached rank 6. When they attain the comprehension of laws, they would definitely meet with a bottleneck of greater difficulty.

Leylin knew this as clear as day.

“However, Daniel and Syre haven’t made any achievements in the comprehension of laws, and are currently only equivalent to newly promoted rank 6 Magi. But with the additive effect of the bloodlines, their true combat abilities shouldn’t be inferior to Magi like the Flame Monarch. I’ll be able to execute my plan with ease.”

Under the protection of the two rank 6 Warlocks Daniel and Syre, the Ouroboros Clan no longer feared clashing against others in most ordinary situations.

The remaining beings of laws naturally wouldn’t provoke them as well, out of respect for Leylin.

After all, even the current Ouroboros Clan was just like a child’s plaything in their eyes.

With such assurances, Leylin could finally let go of the Ouroboros Clan completely and concentrate on his own matters.

“A.I. Chip, show my current statistics.” Leylin commanded.

[Leylin Farlier, rank 6 bloodline Warlock: Targaryen (rank 6). Strength: 185.64. Agility: 133.21. Vitality: 263.11. Spirit: 469.77. State of soul: peak of Breaking Dawn. Comprehension of laws: 99% engulfed. Host body has already been saturated with the original power of the Magus World, and is unable to be raised further.]

The A.I. Chip gathered and displayed Leylin’s latest data.

“Indeed! The original power of the Magus World is now ineffective to me. Unless… I advance once more?”

Leylin’s gaze seemed to shine brightly.

Within the past 300 years or so, he had three opportunities to enter the underground world to absorb the original power of the world and the comprehension of laws. It was a pity that no matter how astonishing his combat abilities were, which were even level to average law beings, he had no way of changing the fact that he was still at rank 6.

In comparison to the real laws beings, his current capacity was like a small cup, which had already been filled to the brim with the original power of the world.

If he wanted to continue absorbing the original power of the world, the only path he could take would be to advance to rank 7.

“In fact, the rank 7 realm has already been completely laid out in front of me. I just need to get rid of Beelzebub and wrest control of the last bit of his power of laws!”

Leylin’s eyes seemed to be ablaze with excitement.

The repeated absorptions of origin power and comprehension of laws made him gain a greater understanding of the Magus path. It even allowed him to plan which direction to take in the future to a certain extent.

All of this had to be realised in the World of the Gods.

“Hmm?! Syre is requesting to communicate with me. Is it about the secret snake den? Forget it! I’ll let him take full responsibility for it, he doesn’t have to report to me.”

Leylin then spent the next few moments casually dealing with the work that he had accumulated.

The secret snake den was in actual fact a pocket dimension that Leylin had constructed himself. It mimicked the same method that the Snake Dowager had used for the Serpentes Plains, and many different highly-skilled snake species were bred there.

Among them, it was only natural that the Kemoyin Serpent descendants were the most common. The bloodlines of the Alabaster Devilsnake and the Three-Headed Python, as well as a small amount of the Targaryen bloodlines also circulated among the snakes.

Through gradually reproducing over a long period of time, the secret snake den had turned into a paradise for highly-skilled snake species. A few variations had also appeared in some specimens.

Of course, this was still a far cry from the standard that Leylin expected.

However, that didn’t matter. With his current life expectancy, he absolutely had the patience to continue waiting.

“Although the probability of success of such experiments in variation is almost insignificant, it’s still a glimmer of hope! My financial ability and physical resources are also sufficient for this experiment to carry on without taking the cost of production into account.”

Leylin supported his chin with his left hand, and suddenly lifted his eyebrows.

“Is this feeling a calling from the Dreamscape?”

The familiar sense of a bloodline caused a strange smile to creep onto the corners of Leylin’s lips.

After receiving the bloodline of the Alabaster Devilsnake, his understanding of Dreamscape was already so deep that he had even obtained the ability to travel there directly.

His advancement to the halfway point of rank 7 as well as his comprehension of laws strengthened this ability significantly.

It could be said that the current Dreamscape was no longer some kind of backyard garden to Leylin, but a homeground that he was extremely familiar with.

Just moments ago, Leylin had sensed a call from Dreamscape, and the source was actually the Snake Dowager!

Ever since suffering a major loss at Leylin’s hands when he had been promoted, the Snake Dowager hadn’t appeared, making Leylin feel rather regretful.

He had looked forward to fighting her in the Magus World. Judging by the powerful and oppressing strength there, the Snake Dowager definitely wouldn’t be able return home. Evidently, she wasn’t a fool and didn’t let Leylin fulfill his wish.

Leylin had also been tactful enough to hole himself up inside the Magus World and didn’t give any Purgatory Exemplaries a chance, thus they could only fume with rage between gritted teeth.

“The Dreamscape? How interesting!”

Chapter 783: Negotiation

In the infinite astral plane, the Magus World and the World of Gods were like the two ends of an hourglass. They were both extremely formidable, yet there were numerous smaller worlds in between them.

Among these worlds were large-scale worlds such as the Purgatory World, Icy World and the Shadow World. Although they couldn’t be compared to the big two, these worlds were still plentiful in origin force.

Dreamscape, however, was even more marvelous. It didn’t have a fixed form yet it spanned across many worlds, as though it was everywhere at once.

At its peak, dreamforce was comparable to the energy of the Magus World. However, this strange yet terrifying world was now at its lowest point because of how weak dreamforce was right now.

This characteristic of Dreamscape was evidently exploited by numerous beings. They used it as a bridge for communication and interaction. This was especially so for the Snake Dowager, who had mastered dreamforce.

“Since it’s an invitation, I’ll go!” Leylin smiled and suddenly disappeared from his laboratory. He was confident in dreamforce himself, and although he couldn’t defeat the Snake Dowager in his current state, he was strong enough to buy himself the time to escape Dreamscape.

With such a premise, it was naturally impossible for the Snake Dowager having come to attack him. She likely wanted to make peace.

After all, no matter how unwilling the Snake Dowager was, Leylin had already broken free of his bloodline shackles and had even advanced to become the primogenitor of a new bloodline. This was an undeniable fact!

The Snake Dowager had the ability to live for countless years, and she had even successfully survived the final ancient war. It was impossible that she was still unable to accept this reality.

A scarlet flame flickered as a huge door appeared on the plain, and Leylin’s figure emerged from the door frame.

“Is this… still Dreamscape?”

Leylin raised his eyes and gazed into the distance. What he saw was all withered trees and dried up streams and lakes. The entire world seemed to be an arid wasteland, and there wasn’t even a trace of life.

Although he long knew that the entirety of Dreamscape had also entered a dreary phase in the wake of the value of dreamforce dropping, such a situation surprised Leylin.

“By the looks of it, I’m afraid that perhaps the entire Dreamscape has fallen in the hands of death…”

Leylin frowned slightly. He recalled the time when he was still at rank 5, and all the aboriginals he had come across in Dreamscape.

“I wonder what happened to little Gillian and their community? I’m afraid that things probably didn’t end well for them…”

The Dreamscape aboriginals that Leylin had met previously were from the most lowly community in Dreamscape. Even though he had imparted his teachings to them previously, it probably only gave them a little more power to defend themselves.

In the face of the Master that was natural disaster, this tiny bit of power was like an ant, the difference being that it was just slightly bigger.

The deterioration of dreamforce was something that even those lords that could cause calamities had to defend against. Judging by Gillian’s community’s capabilities, it was likely that they were unable to survive.

“However, seeing how Dreamscape can be so strange and beyond belief, it’s not that Gillian’s community didn’t have any hope of surviving at all, just that such a possibility is so small that it’s practically negligible enough to be disregarded.”

Leylin shook his head and didn’t think further.

“The degradation of the world… exemplifies the fundamental truth of the astral plane. Even if I am a being of laws, I cannot escape from my final destiny, which is to perish… Forefather of Targaryen… What do you think?”

The surrounding land turned into nothingness, and the entire wasteland seemed to have transformed into a boundless sky in an instant.

A ball of snakes appeared like a star, and the heads of numerous giant snakes hissed angrily, revealing the Snake Dowager’s charming face.

“It’s precisely why it’s able to excite me and vow to pursue eternity and to transcend worldliness, and I will abide by this even till death! Oh Snake Dowager, if you’re of this level, you don’t have to put up an act in front of me.”

Leylin laughed gently and took a step forward with his boot.

*Snap! Snap!* Jet black cracks started to appear in the starry sky, and made horrifyingly loud sounds.

Shortly after, many of smaller cracks started to extend like a spiderweb. Numerous spatial storms rippled across the surface, and the entire sky shattered under Leylin’s feet. The surrounding environment reverted into the original Dreamscape.

The Snake Dowager looked on as Leylin trampled the sky into smithereens. Her beautiful eyes shone with a profound radiance, and it was a good while before she spoke slowly, “Leylin! Your current strength is worthy enough for me to meet you head on!” Her voice had an inexplicable charm to it.

Of course, the Snake Dowager was expressing her natural bloodline abilities, which had long lost its effect on Leylin.

“The premise of a relationship is to have equal strength.” Leylin had already understood this principle earlier, thus his facial expression did not change. He then asked unhurriedly, “I don’t think you invited me here to discuss this issue, right?”

“Yes…” The Snake Dowager’s voice was melodious.

“To have a being like you among my descendants is my luck, and also my misfortune. But since the bloodline origin has already been taken from me, it will be of no use to be entangled with you.”

“So it seems that you have a method to resolve this?” Leylin was evidently ridiculing her, but the Snake Dowager didn’t seem to feel it.

“As long as you assist me in seizing the Shadow World, I can write off all the previous incidents in one stroke, and even help you to become the other origin of the Ten Thousand Snakes. Together, we can share the power of the Shadow World.”

The Snake Dowager bit her lip, as though she was making a huge sacrifice. Such a lovely and pitiful posture would make any male creature go crazy.

Leylin, however, was not enchanted by her graceful bearing. Instead, he was astonished at how fearless the Snake Dowager was.

“Seize the Shadow World? Mighty Snake Dowager, you have such an enormous appetite!” Leylin drew in a deep breath, and at the same time also recalled an intelligence report regarding the Snake Dowager.

“But that’s right! You initially made use of shadow force to cultivate your own laws and form paths of laws, hence you would covet the Shadow World more than anyone else. You tried to capture the entire Shadow World in the ancient times, but unfortunately, you failed…”

The path taken by rank 8 beings was to exploit some kind of medium, continuously refine their own laws, and form a path that was exclusive to them only.

If one was able to achieve this, they would reach the peak of rank 8! They would be able to spy on beings in the rank 9 realm, such as the Mother Core, for instance.

The Snake Dowager’s previous attempt failed, thus she had no choice but to migrate out of the Shadow World along with her descendants, and arrived at the Purgatory World.

But the origin of the Shadow World was crucial for the Snake Dowager to achieve the peak of rank 8, therefore she couldn’t give it up.

Consequently, it was highly normal for her to launch an offensive once more. What Leylin didn’t see coming was that her actually approaching him for assistance.

“Aid you in seizing the Shadow World? I’m afraid I’m impotent!”

Leylin was understood the level of the Shadow World thoroughly. It was a powerful world, much like the Purgatory World, and possessed numerous law beings.

In other words, if he was on the same camp as the Snake Dowager, he would have to take on many other law beings one on one. Leylin even strongly suspected that there was an extreme being similar to the Mother Core within the Shadow World, otherwise the Snake Dowager’s plans wouldn’t have been thwarted.

In such a situation, wouldn’t it be suicide to form an alliance with the Snake Dowager?

“In reality, there aren’t as many law beings in the Shadow World as you think! Besides, you inherited my bloodline. The same additive effect applies to your strength in the Shadow World as well. The assistance that the Shadow origin will provide you with will definitely go beyond what you imagined…”

The Snake Dowager evidently knew Leylin’s considerations. For beings like them who had reached this level, most of her crafty conspiracies had already lost their effect. The only effective way was to tempt him directly with benefits.

“Does the Snake Dowager actually have so much confidence in seizing control over the Shadow World?” Leylin couldn’t help but ask this question directly upon seeing her self-confidence.

“I almost succeeded the previous time! All I lacked was an assistant of the same origin.”

The Snake Dowager shot Leylin a profound look, yet it made his scalp go slightly numb.

“An assistant of the same origin? Makes sense. We are, in fact, beings of the same bloodline origin. Even our powers can work in harmony and complement each other! If she really missed by only a hair previously, then coupled with my powers, perhaps…”

Leylin’s pupils twinkled as he quickly analyzed the situation.

Of course, no matter how the Snake Dowager made it sound like a deluge of heavenly flowers, he wouldn’t fall for her trap.

Just a vague and insubstantial agreement that she would write off all their previous grudges in one stroke, coupled with a promise that they would share the profits together, and she wanted him to sacrifice his life for someone else? What kind of joke was this?

What was more dangerous was that he was still a semi-rank 7. If they were in the Magus World, even if the Snake Dowager came down personally, he was confident of making sure that she would land herself in serious trouble. But if they were to fight for the controlling rights of the Shadow World, it was inevitable that he would have to make the trip using his actual self and descend within the Shadow World.

Since it was a foreign world, and also the Snake Dowager’s home ground, Leylin wasn’t foolish enough to deliver himself up straight into her mouth for free.

In all likelihood, the Snake Dowager might gobble him up straight away even if she couldn’t capture the Shadow World, to properly make up for it.

“My apologies, I’m still incompetent when it comes to matters like these.”

After much consideration, Leylin immediately rejected her without hesitation.

The moment the words left his lips, he could feel the surrounding space come to a standstill. The Snake Dowager’s beautiful pupils nearly became as narrow as a straight line, as a horrifying sensation dissipated from the ball of snakes.

Leylin, however, was not fearful. The gigantic Targaryen phantom appeared behind him and started hissing at the Snake Dowager in anger.

Large amounts of bloodline energy seemed to begin to grow restless, and was about to fly out from the Snake Dowager’s body.

Having already extricated himself from her control over his bloodline, not only was Leylin no longer under the Snake Dowager’s control at all, but his body even had an odd restraining ability towards her.

No matter how mystical this force was, it still didn’t have any effect in the face of such a tremendous difference in terms of strength.

But there was absolutely no problem for Leylin to break away from the Dreamscape during this short amount of time.

And the Snake Dowager could only grudgingly choose to reach a compromise upon seeing this.

Chapter 788: Alternate World Reincarnation

“Injuries to the truesoul are the most terrifying. Even existences of laws will sink into a deep sleep in order to heal them…” Leylin laughed wryly, “This is a result of splitting a small part of my truesoul. If it’s anything like what Beezlebub did, it’s very possible that my main body would just die…”

The phantom Targaryen behind Leylin’s back withered and slowly disappeared. A bit of faint red light flew out from between his brows and disappeared into his hand, flashing like a firefly. This was the smaller truesoul that Leylin had split. The experiment had to begin immediately, lest it dissipate from prolonged exposure to the external world.

“Astral gate, open!” Leylin huffed in a low voice, and a procedure identical to before was executed. His soul force waded through the long astral river until it arrived at the tremendous crystal wall surrounding the World of Gods.

“Manderhawke’s Plate!” The stone plate in Leylin’s hands came to the crystal wall, emitting a light that caused a portion to seem to be on the verge of melting.

At the moment a channel opened through the crystal wall, Leylin’s eyes brightened and immense rank 7 spell undulations were emitted from his body. “Rank 7 spell— Alternate World Reincarnation!”

Time seemed to stop in that instant. That bit of truesoul in Leylin’s hands was enveloped in the brilliance of the Alternate World Reincarnation spell as it disappeared into the World of Gods.

Everything happened quickly. Once it was done, the Manderhawke Plate exploded into powder, and the crystal wall from before closed itself quickly with no trace of a flaw.

“It’s all up to the truesoul now…” The huge astral gate gradually collapsed, and Leylin could only smile wryly.

With his serious injuries, he could only slumber in his laboratory, recuperating with time as he controlled his clone in the World of Gods.

“These injuries are enough for me to sleep for a few hundred years. If I don’t get any benefits from the World of Gods, it would be such a huge loss…” With this thought, Leylin’s body disappeared into the ground under the laboratory.

With the slumber of his main body, all of his attention was focused on that clone.

The brainwashing and refining from a world origin was a very terrifying process.

Leylin’s truesoul could sense that ever since he entered the World of Gods, terrifying energy whirlpools had formed next to him, tirelessly washing away all traces of the power he used to possess.

Evidently, this was an effect of the rank 7 spell, Alternate World Reincarnation. It allowed Leylin to reach the core of the World of Gods and be altered by the origin itself.

Once this modification was over, he could perhaps wash off all traces of being from another world and truly become a native of the World of Gods.

This alteration happened extremely quickly. The luster of the Manderhawke Plate had diminished by a huge degree after opening just the external layer of the crystal wall, and after opening up the World of Gods, it had been directly destroyed with no traces of it left at all.

Next was the power of the rank 7 spell, the reincarnation spell that allowed Leylin to arrive in this world. Its luster gradually dissipated.

Just like stripping off a greatcoat, once the rays of light of the reincarnation spell dissipated, Leylin’s truesoul was fully bared in the immense darkness.

Vastness! Terror! Boundlessness!

This was Leylin’s truesoul’s first thoughts. Compared to this enormous world, his little truesoul was nothing and couldn’t even be compared to an ant, and it could only tremble in the corner.

The and powerful source immediately invaded into Leylin’s truesoul.

The truesoul, which had already been shrunk and condensed to a large degree, surprisingly gradually became slower under the alteration of the world force.

“Even soul force has been forcefully removed…” Leylin’s truesoul watched this process, able to only laugh.

The truesoul was constantly altered, to the point that Leylin’s own conscience was gradually becoming fuzzy.

Gradually, the changes from the world force went on to the deepest layer of his truesoul, where his memories and his most important elements of self were.

The tremendous soul force ruthlessly invaded it with no intentions of stopping.

“Could it be that… I’m going to be defeated just like this? With such a laughable method?”

Leylin’s truesoul was on the verge of death, and only this little thought appeared tenaciously, as if making its last struggle.

*Bzzt bzzt!* At this moment, a bright silver white light shone from Leylin’s truesoul memories.

Under the influence of the white rays of light, the world force hesitated for that slight moment, and then let go of Leylin’s memories, altering other areas.

“Could… could this be the power of the Alternate World Reincarnation spell? So it still has a bit of energy left, stored in my memories? Or… it’s something else?”

Leylin’s truesoul was perplexed, but having been diminished to the limit quickly sank into a deep sleep.

Time seemed to stop at this moment, but at the same time, a long time seemed to have passed.

“Where… is this?” Leylin, who regained his consciousness, sized up his surroundings, stunned.

Perhaps ‘sizing up’ wasn’t the right term for it, because he no longer had a body, and naturally had no eyes or organs like that.

What he was now doing was using his senses to explore the area like feelers.

Darkness… It was darkness all around with no light at all. Leylin, who was now conscious, measured up his surroundings and felt helpless.

“Even my truesoul has vanished. I’m just a body that’s a mixture of memories and a fragmented soul now?”

Leylin’s conscient was suddenly enlightened. At this moment, there seemed to be a black hole in the air that sucked his conscient in.

Leylin’s conscient found itself getting dizzy as it sunk into a deep sleep…

“How long have I slept for?”

When his conscient re-awakened, the surroundings had changed once again.

While it was darkness all around, orange-red light could be seen. He could even hear some low hums in his confusion.

Thankfully, while his conscient was weak, Leylin could tell that his conscient was no longer without a source but had something maintaining his life.

“In this state, what I need is to do what I can to reduce consumption of energy and allow the conscient to rest in order to amass more energy….”

Leylin’s conscient sank into sleep once more. However, before going back into a slumber, Leylin gave himself a prompt.

The terrifying calculation abilities of his main body now became the most precise stopwatch.

Once it reached 17280 000 in his mind, Leylin reawakened.

“Mm, 17280 000 seconds, which is two hundred days have passed?”

Awake, the conscient was elated to find that it had gotten stronger. There was the obvious feeling of energy being transmitted, as if there was a warm rush unceasingly pouring towards his stomach.

“Stomach? Mm!!!” An electrostatic force swept across him, and immediately after, Leylin felt his right leg twitch.

“This…” His conscient abruptly became clear as he then went through a more detailed probe.

Thanks to this slumber, the area that he could explore expanded, gradually forming the image of a baby hugging his head. The veins and even bones could be seen.

“I have a body now! So what happened was that I’ve always been in a pregnant woman’s stomach as an embryo!”

Leylin abruptly understood.

“So it seems like the Alternate World Reincarnation spell formation succeeded!”

However, Leylin soon found himself at a loss, “Do I have to start off as a baby? This is simply too shameful!”

However, with Leylin’s thick skin, this embarrassment only had him turn red for a moment, before he began to consider this situation as if nothing had happened.

“A baby is far too weak. With my current state, my parents should be regular human natives of the World of Gods. It’s a pity that in this situation, I have no way to protect myself. I can only leave everything up to fate…”

All the previous energy he possessed had been washed off and removed from him. Even the soul energy that Magi were the most proud of had completely disappeared. Besides a bit of awareness, he was no different from other unborn children and naturally had no way to protect himself.

In addition, just thinking for this moment left Leylin feeling dizzy.

“This isn’t good! A baby’s brain has yet to fully mature. In this state, I should try my best to withhold my thoughts. It’s better to sleep.”

Leylin understood everything.

Conscients cannot exist without a body. This was even more so in the World of Gods, where laws were even more stern. Leylin now had lost all his solidified soul energy. His conscient and spiritual force could only rely on this developing body of a fetus and he naturally could not overdo it. If the woman were to have a miscarriage because of this, Leylin would be doomed.

Leylin, who understood this well, could only sink into a deep slumber while hoping this pregnant woman would be safe.

“Ugh…” At this moment, in a port city in the World of Gods.

A noble young lady clutched at her swelling stomach, brows tightly furrowed.

“What is it, darling!”

A young man immediately came over to help her along, looking anxious.

“It’s the child. He kicked me…” The woman looked gentle, brimming in the radiance of motherly love.

“What a cheeky fellow!”

The young lad bent down, pressing his ear tightly to the swollen stomach, to which the lady protested coquettishly.

Chapter 792: Fighting Spirit

“The accurate usage of formalities and the mastery of titles and honorifics at different levels is a complicated subject,” Anthony wiped the small blackboard behind him, “Before we begin the course, I would like to introduce a respected deity to you.”

Anthony fished out a badge from his chest pocket. On it was a sacred logo in the shape of a book which had a dim luster.

“Can you recognise this?” Anthony asked softly.

“I recognise it! This is the emblem of the almighty God of Knowledge, Oguma!” Leylin nodded earnestly.

The smile on Anthony’s face spread even wider, “That’s right! All of us scholars believe strongly in the almighty God of Knowledge, Oguma, who is also the origin of all knowledge.”

He shot a profound glance at Leylin, “It is also the religion that the Faulen family believes in. Do you pray frequently?”

“I’ve seen my parents do it!” Leylin replied. After all, you couldn’t expect much of a child.

“Very well. Now, follow my actions.” Anthony’s expression grew sincere, pure, and holy, “Almighty God of Knowledge, you are the origin of all knowledge, the controller of truth…”

Leylin was secretly rolling his eyes vigorously, but he could only follow Anthony and pray, “Your glory will be scattered upon the entire world, driving out barbarism and ignorance, and bringing about the golden age of civilisation…”

A young voice continuously reverberated in the small drawing room. Jonas and Sarah, who were hiding outside the door, had smiles plastered on their faces.

‘So apart from giving me language lessons, this teacher is also here to give me lessons on the divine…’ Leylin was secretly gloomy, but didn’t express the slightest bit of impatience on his face. Instead, he was conscientious and focused, at which Anthony couldn’t help but nod approvingly to himself.

In actual fact, Leylin knew that there was totally no way for him to avoid this. After all, the influence that the deities had on this world was honestly too deep. If he wanted to continue living under his false identity, he had to transform into a believer.

A person without faith in the World of Gods would be considered a freak, and would have absolutely no room for survival.

Fortunately, the deities only had great influence on and branded the souls of their own devout followers and fanatics. They didn’t pay much attention to the general believers who had only been slightly influenced by the glory of the gods.

What was even more ingenious was that unless one assumed the position of a priest, it was practically impossible to tell the extent of faith that one had. Anyway, all he had to do was just pray at fixed times and occasionally make donations at the church. Leylin felt that he could totally act out such superficial deeds very well.

Based on what Leylin knew, the God of Knowledge, Oguma was a deity that many noble families and scholars believed in. It could be said that he was rather someone all cultured people believed in.

Of these two specific types of people, one set cared only for their interest while the other laid special emphasis on practical laws. They definitely weren’t as religious as they claimed to be. Leylin wouldn’t stand out if he mixed with them, thus this deity could be said to be the best option.

‘There’s only one other option in the Faulen family’s territory… The God of Sufferance Erma…’ Leylin shuddered.

Erma was a deity brimming with devotion and sacrificial spirit. Most of her teachings advised her believers to exercise patience and compliance, making her a deity that many rulers liked to introduce into their territory.

Naturally, the same applied with Baron Jonas. These two churches were the only ones currently in his fief, resulting in a scenario where the upper class prayed to the God of Knowledge and the farmers and sailors prayed to Erma.

Although the Baron also wished to introduce the church of the Goddess of Wealth Waukin into his territory, he hadn’t been successful.

The island’s trading industry wasn’t very prosperous yet, and was even boycotted by the combined resistance of both the current churches. The wealthy pastors who knew how to earn money more than they knew how to preach naturally wouldn’t be attracted to this place.

‘Excellent!’ Upon seeing a white cloud of holy light floating up from the religious emblem and draping itself over Leylin, every single wrinkle on Anthony’s face was smoothened out with a smile, “The almighty God of Knowledge has received your prayers. In the future, you may follow your parents to the Knowledge Shrine and Church to participate in scripture-related activities and donations.”

“That would be my honor!” Leylin replied methodically as he secretly rejoiced, ‘Sure enough, my soul is now wholly native to the World of Gods, and I haven’t aroused even the slightest amount of suspicion from Anthony. As long as I maintain this level of faith in future, and do not attract his attention, there definitely won’t be any problem.’

Of course, Leylin also knew that he had no path as a priest. After all, priesthood demanded great faith. Not only were priests expected to understand the entirety of their deities’ doctrines and follow them, even their souls belonged to the deities themselves.

If his own soul was laid bare under the gaze of the deities, Leylin wasn’t certain if he’d be able to conceal the truth.

‘However, with my attitude, I’m afraid that I wouldn’t be able to achieve even the lowest level of a priest…’ Leylin grew speechless at these own thoughts of his.

“Alright, let’s begin today’s lesson. I’ll just mention that the remuneration I get from your father is three golden coins every time the hourglass runs out!” Anthony started to write on the blackboard. He wrote in cursive, which appeared highly complicated and beautiful.

“Three gold coins?” Leylin deeply exhaled. Even a young child like him knew that the purchasing power of gold coins in the World of Gods was extremely high.

“Knowledge is priceless…” Anthony nodded satisfactorily at Leylin’s show of poor manners, then began the morning’s lesson.

This level of teaching was simply considered nothing in Leylin’s eyes. He had even specially lowered his speed of learning by a great deal in order to conceal how exceptional he truly was.

Even so, the abilities that he displayed had earned exceedingly high praise from Anthony. He strongly commended Leylin in front of the Baron and his wife, and even predicted that he would become a mighty scholar one day, which made Lady Sarah’s eyes twinkle with delight. The Baron lifted Leylin up and tossed him around in the air many times.

After enjoying a sumptuous lunch under the maids’ care, Leylin followed the Baron to a small field behind the manor.

This was the place where farmers usually lay their grains under the scorching sun. It was very spacious and empty, a wooden frame upright at the side holding hammers, daggers, pikes, knight spears, and other kinds of weapons.

A warrior dressed in leather armor was already waiting in the centre of the field.

“Leylin, this is the chief imperial bodyguard of our family. You may call him Uncle Jacob!” The Baron introduced him to Leylin.

Leylin could distinctly sense a menacing aura from him, one that could only be cultivated by traversing mountains of corpses and oceans of blood. He also felt his formidable strength; Jacob clearly possessed some sort of extraordinary ability, and was a Professional.

“Uncle Jacob!” Leylin immediately shouted sweetly.

“Your Uncle Jacob has always been in charge of the patrol team at the harbor. I specially transferred him here to take responsibility and teach you martial arts. He is your instructor from today, understood?” The Baron’s voice grew stern.

“Teacher Jacob,” Leylin secretly rolled his eyes as he greeted him seriously once more.

“Jacob, I’ll hand Leylin over to you!” Jonas hit Jacob’s shoulder

“Rest assured, Sir, I will definitely teach the young master all that I know!” Jacob straightened his chest.

After the Baron left, only Leylin and Jacob were left on the small field. “Before we start on the warrior training, I have a question for you, young master. Do you know what a Professional is?”

Jacob had a very boorish face. Having had a long-term job that required him to oppress others, he was brimming with a deadly aura. Even if he tried hard to make himself look gentle when he smiled, his looks would intimidate many imps, so much that they would cry.

“I’ve heard about it before…” Leylin scratched his head.

“A so-called Professional is someone who possesses formidable strength. Even in other countries, they receive preferential treatment, especially so for Professionals who are rank 5 and above.” The muscles in Jacob’s right hand bulged, as though trying to make him more persuasive. They were covered in a misty brilliance.

“Look carefully! This is an ability that only rank 5 warriors and above possess. Fighting Spirit!” With a loud bellow, Jacob smashed his fist onto the ground.

*Rumble!* Smoke and dust scattered throughout the air, as though a small-scale earthquake had occurred in the field. When the smoke and dust dispersed, a huge sunken pit could be seen next to Jacob.

“Wow…” Leylin’s jaw dropped open, and he appeared to be extremely shocked. He reacted in about the same way as other children would, but he was actually secretly estimating Jacob’s capabilities.

‘Such destructive power… It’s almost the same as knights who’ve activated life energy. There’s no doubt about it; the harsher restrictions on extraordinary powers in the World of God means that Jacob’s true strength should be even greater than this. He should be close to a rank 1 Magus in strength…’ Leylin made secret calculations as the A.I. Chip immediately revealed Jacob’s stats.

[Jacob, Warrior. Rank: Rank 5 or above (insufficient information). Estimated stats, Strength: 3, Agility: 2, Vitality: 3, Spirit: 1.5. Evaluation: Dangerous!]

Leylin sighed in silence. At the same time, he had also roughly gauged Jacob’s strength. ‘This body is too weak. Even the A.I. Chip’s scanning abilities are limited.’

“I’m only a warrior, thus I can only show you the strength of a warrior, young master.” Jacob said regretfully, “There are many different types of Professionals, who possess strange yet mysterious abilities.”

It was clear that Jacob was faithfully fulfilling his duty and using his formidable strength to lure the young master into walking on the path of strength.

“Then… what is your rank as a warrior, Uncle Jacob? Can you tell me?” At this point, Leylin fully put his advantage as a young child to use, and constantly tried to acquire information.

“Me? I’m just a mere rank 6 warrior!” Jacob laughed, seemingly embarrassed.

Chapter 793: Ernest

“A rank 6 warrior? How about my father? What rank is he? Is he rank 15?” Leylin appeared very innocent and vulnerable. After all, in the hearts of children, parents were unequalled.

“Rank 15?! Cough cough…” Jacob almost choked on his saliva, “Esteemed young master, Professionals above rank 5 are already valued by nobility. Those beyond rank 15 are treated with excessive respect even among the highest strata of society. There are very few of them on the continent…”

“Is that so?” Leylin stroked his chin. He’d heard about this ranking while he had still been a soul seed, and it seemed like after borrowing a medium to use, the strength of his soul seed was not half bad.

Of course, no matter how powerful he was, he was still a foreigner. Nothing could be hidden from the glory of the gods, and he would easily have been destroyed.

“Uncle Jacob, what happens after rank 15? Are there more powerful beings?” Leylin was like a little guy filled with curiosity.

“After rank 15… ah…” Jacob’s eyes were dim, “Then there are only the Legends! Legendary beings can make whole kingdoms retreat, and are the most powerful forces of the continent…”

“Legends?” Leylin’s eyes flashed.

“Alright! Let’s start training today. First is long-distance running!” At this moment, Jacob realised that Leylin’s questions had pushed him off topic. He turned grim.

“Fine, fine…” Leylin began to run around cheekily like a little cheetah full of energy, his smooth motions causing Jacob’s eyes to brighten.

……

Deep in the night, in the baron’s study room.

Jonas sat behind the work desk, arms crossed as he looked deep in thought. “You’re saying Leylin’s body has good potential, and if he were to go through warrior training, he he has high prospects?”

Jacob stood before Jonas, speaking sternly. “Yes, my lord! The energy in young master Leylin’s body flows very smoothly. On top of that, with a great body from birth, I’m certain that the young master will gather fighting energy and break through to become a rank 5 warrior in ten years if he perseveres with warrior training!”

“Alright. You may leave,” Jonas waved his arms tiredly. Only after Jacob bowed and left could he laugh wryly. “Outstanding literary talent and an outstanding physique! Leylin, you truly are a gem gifted to me by the gods!”

Jonas grabbed at his hair in frustration. Every parent hoped their child would be a genius, but when Leylin was outstanding in both of these respects, Jonas grew distressed as to how best to nurture the boy.

“It’s obviously necessary to continue the cultural lessons, but what about the warrior training?” Jonas knew Jacob’s strength well, and if Leylin truly had talent, it would be a waste for him to be training under Jacob.

On top of that, warriors had low status in the World of Gods given how common they were. While they could grow extremely powerful at the higher, more profound realms, one would unavoidably be treated like cannon fodder in the beginning. Jonas was hesitant about it.

“What are you worrying about?” At this moment, a gentle voice was heard from outside the study room, and Jonas’ eyes brightened.

“Ernest! Welcome!” Jonas stood up while beaming sunnily, watching a figure walk out from the shadows.

The figure had a head of long, soft, silver hair. His eyes were filled with wisdom, and while he looked young he had a great aura. He wore a yielding gown similar to those of scholars, and had a mysterious golden decorative motif on his chest. Powerful magical force twined around his body, giving him a very menacing aura. Evidently, Ernest was a powerful magician.

This was a magician! The spellcasters of the World of Gods grasped powerful abilities in magic, and were existences that could control the natural elements around them. More importantly, every spellcasters was extremely well-learned. Their breadth of knowledge was above that of many famed scholars.

Of course, due to the great amount of resources and time that had to be poured into magic, magic was a Profession of nobles. Regular commoners definitely couldn’t pay the expenses required to study and conduct experiments.

“We meet again, Jonas!” Ernest smiled gently, giving his friend an enthusiastic hug.

“I’m sorry I couldn’t get here in time when your child was born. Experiments that probe the abyss are too complex and time consuming…” Ernest looked sorry.

“Treat this Ring of Light as my belated gift!” He passed a glimmering silver ring to Jonas, “Though the light spell in this can only be used thrice, it’s not bad for a child’s toy…”

“Thank you very much, on behalf of Leylin as well!” Jonas took the ring carefully, moved by the present. With his knowledge, he knew that even a temporarily enchanted item like this could easily fetch ten gold coins.

Magical items were that expensive! Often times, they could not even be sold due to their exorbitant prices.

With the Faulen family’s background, they would at most befriend a few useless magic scholars, and it was impossible to make connections with powerful spellcasters like Ernest.

Meeting him was a pure coincidence. After finding out his true identity, Jonas had spent much effort to build up a great friendship with him.

After they sat down, Ernest continued his query, “Jonas… What’s worrying you?”

“Well…” Watching the powerful spellcaster, Jonas had to conceal the glimmer in his eyes. He laughed wryly, “You know Leylin is already five, right? His talent is worrying me. I’m worried he’ll lack the guidance he needs, which will cause him to walk the wrong path and not be able to show his outstanding talent…”

Jonas mentioned Leylin’s display in detail. It had to be said that even while he was hiding a lot of information, Leylin’s was definitely a talent amongst the natives here.

As Jonas continued, Ernest’s eyes brightened, “Tomorrow! Let me see the child tomorrow. If he really has talent, I can consider taking him in as my student!”

“Thank you so much!” Jones stood up, elated.

“It’s nothing!” Ernest smiled slightly. He had already noticed Jonas’ objective, but he didn’t particularly mind. He had gotten a huge sponsorship from Jonas before, and taking a child in as a student wasn’t much in return. Of course, the child needed to have talent in magic, even if it was at a low level.

The next day, Leylin was informed that all of his classes were postponed, and that he was going to meet someone important.

“Leylin, my child!” Jonas stood before Leylin, looking extremely serious.

“I will bring you to see a powerful magician later. Even in the entire continent, he is a very terrific person, so you must be respectful. Is that understood?”

“Yes, father!” Little Leylin nodded vigorously, looking forward to this. ‘A magician? A spellcaster in this world? I can finally walk the path of the elements again…’

Leylin was more than aware about whether he had talent in casting spells. In addition, he didn’t have plans on choosing a different profession having restarted his life. He was a Magus, and it was much easier for him to reach the peak of the path of magic.

Of course, he had not considered becoming a Warlock once more. He had gone through a great number of trouble to break his bloodline shackles in the past, and wanted nothing to do with it again. Hence, becoming a magician was currently Leylin’s best choice.

“I hope you’ll become a powerful magician. If that happens, our Faulen family…” Jonas’ tone held hope and anticipation as he rubbed Leylin’s head, bringing him to the drawing room. In there was a magician with long silver hair, gazing over him with eyes as intense as lightning. Goosebumps arose on Leylin’s skin.

“Ah!” A low hum could be heard from his lips.

“Come! Leylin, this is your uncle Ernest!” While perplexed by Ernest’s expression, Jonas immediately hinted at Leylin to greet him.

“Good morning, Uncle Ernest!” Leylin bowed respectfully, his bright eyes full of curiosity.

“Good child, come here.” Ernest’s eyes were filled with excitement. Even Jonas could tell that he was holding his emotions back.

“Hold this!” Another silver ring appeared in his hands. Unlike the previous one, this looked like an exquisite work of art, and had a glistening gem embedded at its crest. Jonas could tell at first glance that this was a magic item with a permanent spell inside. Compared to the one from before that could only be used thrice before it was rendered useless, it was at least ten times the value.

“Thank you, uncle!” Leylin respectfully took the ring, while he held it with contempt in his mind.

‘A magic artifact that can be used only when my spiritual force has reached a certain level? What a primitive method of sensing…’

The moment he held the ring, the energy pathway and structure within was laid bare before Leylin’s eyes. ‘I’ll take this chance to show off my ability then!’

Chapter 795: 8 Years

“In that case, master, if a wizard can only store magic one day before using it the next, then isn’t it necessary to determine which spells to use on the day before? And once the spell slots have been used up…” Leylin raised his hand and asked.

“Yes! All wizards need to prepare all the magic they will use a day prior. It’s important to know which spells to prepare, and as for the issue of spell slots being used up…”

Ernest looked very stern. “Remember this well, Leylin! Once a wizard uses up all his spells and has no scrolls or magic artifacts on his body, he is no different from an ordinary person. Hence, you can never let yourself get into that situation. This is very important! I’ve seen many who used up all their spells and were unlucky enough to be gnawed down the core, without a scrap of flesh left on their bones!”

“I understand!” Leylin sat back down speechlessly.

‘Based on what he said, wizards actually use their spiritual force as a currency to buy the authority to use magic from the Weave. While this method makes the requirements to become a wizard less stringent, this is basically a nightmare for those who are talented enough to build spell models by themselves…

‘So in general, wizards are impotent and diminished versions of Magi?’ Leylin felt disconcerted. ‘So while it allows those without enough aptitude to use magic, this Weave is inflexible and confines true talent in magic!’

Leylin’s eyes flashed, ‘Perhaps this is the goal of the gods, to prevent the rise of a wizard who is too powerful. Could this be an effect from the final battle with the Magi? In that case, I should look up the history of this Weave Goddess. If my guess is correct, she must be a new god that only gained popularity after the ancient final war!’

Despite knowing this, Leylin obviously would not stick out his neck and try to change things. His goal was to remain low-profile as he grew up, and he absolutely would not do something like challenging the gods.

Before having the confidence to break through the power of laws, he had no choice but to explore the path of wizards.

“Next… I’ll teach you a meditation technique, and then you can start making contact with the Weave…” Ernest continued to teach from the lectern, unaware that this pupil that looked studious on the outside was exploring many new ideas.

‘Meditation here isn’t too different from Magi’s meditation techniques, but the effects are slightly weaker. Of course, coupled with the laws of the World of Gods, there are many areas I can learn from. As for the Weave…’ Leylin’s spirit began to extend outwards.

Using the method that Ernest had taught him, his spirit seemed to touch upon a powerful existence. It was a network of invisible energy shaped like a spiderweb, and it enveloped the entire World of Gods with its powerful energy.

Even the surface density of the energy pathways left Leylin’s scalp prickling.

‘Are those nodes spell slots? I never thought that just the surface layer of the Weave would be enough for me to feel stunned like this,’ Leylin watched the Weave, his eyes full of admiration as he grew more convinced in his guesses.

‘So powerful… It must have been created as a joint effort by the gods. Mystra should be one of the most powerful of peak rank 8s, which is why she was selected to manage it.’ Leylin knew very little about the gods. All he knew was that there were a few stages to the most powerful of them, second to the World Will that was the Supreme God. Unlike in the Magus World, there were greater gods, the middle gods, and the lesser gods.

Mystra was definitely among the most successful of the greater gods, having tremendous divine force. Even if Leylin’s main body were to fight her it was unlikely that he’d hold the upper hand.

“I’ve already given you the meditation method. Next up is to continue practising the use of your spiritual force and making contact with the Weave. Other students might need up to three months, but you’ll be able to do it in a month!” Ernest spoke frankly.

All of a sudden, a strange undulation spread, causing his expression to change.

“Weave! You’ve made contact with the Weave!” Ernest charged forward, grabbing Leylin’s slender arm. His eyes went read, “Leylin, is it really your first time touching upon magic?”

“Of course, master! I’ve rarely even left the manor since birth!” Leylin’s eyes gleamed as he answered innocently.

“Then tell me! Are you the illegitimate child of the Weave Goddess?” Ernest asked extremely seriously…

……

Come fall, there were scenes of a great harvest everywhere. Grain and flour filled warehouses, and many farmers looked gleeful at the sight.

This harvest was enough for them to pay their taxes, and would even leave enough food for them to live through the winter and plant seeds at the beginning of spring. At this thought, they could not help but begin to pray, singing praises in the favour of the gods, as well as the benevolence and generosity of the lord.

With the profits from having a port and with many residents moving from the continent to the island, the Faulen family’s taxes were set very low, which could be considered a very benevolent act from them.

Haystacks were piled up high in the training grounds of the manor, forming forts in varying shape. Two figures were now clashing on the ground.

“Pay attention to your centre of gravity, I’m coming!” Along with the warning, a blonde teen in white training clothes brandished a metal sword like a viper, twisting his body in an arc in mid-air, spinning around to arrive next to his opponent and thrusted his sword forward at an unexpected angle.

Leylin’s opponent seemed middle aged. His face had marks of age on it, his hands were full of calluses, and he now looked as if he was battling his greatest enemy.

“Hah! It’s this way!” He called in a low voice, holding the heavy sword in his hand horizontal.

*Clang!* The two swords produced a dull sound as they collided with tremendous force.

“Crap!” The man’s expression changed and he slipped. Having lost his centre of gravity, his entire body was thrown off balance.

*Boom!* He felt a tremendous force slam into him, but the force turned gentle when it hit his chest, and he seemed to be sent flying away rather delicately, as if he was light as a feather.

When the middle-aged man opened his eyes once more, the blonde teen’s metal sword was already at his chest, “You’ve lost, Jacob.”

“Yes, young master Leylin, I’ve lost!” Jacob laughed helplessly.

“Your earlier parry was not agile enough, and you lacked instinct in your movements!” In front of him was obviously Leylin. However, Leylin was now guiding Jacob in detail as if he was the teacher instead. Jacob listened obediently, watching him in admiration.

After sending Jacob away, Leylin picked up a white towel and wiped off the sweat on his face before walking into the bathroom. The steady rise of the cloudy steam made the room look a little hazy.

Coming before a precious mercury mirror, he judged his appearance. He had curling golden hair, blue eyes, and a handsome face which inherited his parents’ excellent features. While the fine hair near his lips betrayed his true age, it did nothing to conceal the mature charm he possessed.

‘It’s been ten years since I’ve started training to become a wizard!’ Leylin sighed. Hr followed it up with an order, ‘A.I. Chip, show me my current stats!’

[Leylin Farlier. Age: 13. Race: Human. Rank 5 Wizard. Strength: 1.5, Agility : 1, Vitality: 1.3, Spirit: 5. Condition: Healthy. Innate skills: Sturdy, Erudite. Spell Slots: Rank 2 slots (1), rank 1 slots (2), rank 0 slots (3)]

After fumbling around for many years, Leylin had developed more functions for the A.I. Chip, and even the stats were now more detailed. He turned his attention to the description of his innate skills.

[Innate Skill. Sturdy: Host has persevered through warrior training, and possesses a sturdy physique. (Strength +0.5, Vitality +0.3)]

[Erudite: Plentiful experiences and great knowledge has allowed the host’s willpower and spirit to expand and become more resilient. (Spirit +1)]

‘The stats that the A.I. Chip shows includes the bonus from my innate skills…’ Leylin looked rather solemn, “In other words, besides the strengthening of my spiritual force from birth, my body is practically comparable to a regular adult?”

After the passing of so many years, Leylin found that due to the limitations by the world’s laws, it was extremely difficult for humans to raise their strength.

There seemed to be some kind of bottleneck when raising any of his stats, and once they reached an average of one his progress had stalled. Only his spiritual force, which was related to him being a wizard, was still somewhat increasing, but it too seemed to have reached a bottleneck.

‘When it comes to my body’s stats, Jacob still surpasses me in many ways. The reason I could defeat him was technique… Is this some added bonus from being a warrior?’ Leylin stroked his chin, sinking into deep thought.

While the increase of his strength would be shocking to his peers, this did not satisfy him.

“Perhaps I should find an opportunity and go on a trip outside!” Leylin inwardly made a decision as he bathed in the warm water. He naturally had ideas about how to increase his strength, but he obviously could not implement them at home. Travelling abroad now seemed to be a rather good idea.

Chapter 796: Anthony

‘A.I. Chip, how’s the progress on the analysis of the Weave?’ Leylin inwardly asked, closing his eyes.

[Beep! Analysis prioritises concealment of the host. Current progress: Rank 0 Weave 87.69%, Rank 1 Weave 37.61%, Rank 2 Weave 2.33%!]

The A.I. Chip quickly replied.

This was one of the many reasons why Leylin was advancing so slowly as a wizard, and he was very interested in the existence of the Weave. If he was able to completely analyse the Weave without being discovered by Mystra, it would make it extremely convenient for him to cast spells.

Even with such a huge project on his hands, Leylin was still able to reach rank 5 as a wizard. This display was already enough for Ernest to rave and exclaim that he was a genius, even a monster.

Wizards in the World of Gods were ranked according to their level of contact with the Weave. Those below rank 3 could only make contact with its surface, memorising and using rank 0 spells. They would acquire a deeper understanding of it upon reaching rank 3, gaining the ability to use rank 1 spells.

Leylin was now a rank 5 wizard, able to make contact with the second layer to use rank 2 spells. He was doing rather well for himself. On top of that, being a wizard in itself gave him great status. If he was lucky, he could even be conferred a lordship as he was in a large noble family, and it was highly likely that he’d gain his own land with meritorious deeds, passing it down the generations.

This was the dream of commoners. It was a pity though; at this level everything was like the dirt on the ground to Leylin, filling him with disdain as he trod on it.

‘Ranks 1 to 5 are considered normal in the central continent, and those from rank 6 to 10 are considered elites. From 1- to 15 are experts and those above are true powerhouses who enjoy great reputation in the continent. Even if they aren’t considered Legends, they are the apex of power, and those who appear most often. Legends could care less about worldly matters, placing their ambition and hopes on obtaining divinity, perhaps igniting their godfire and obtaining a place as a deity…’

This was Leylin’s current understanding of the power hierarchy in the World of Gods, obtained from the intel he had acquired as well as his own conjectures. Gods were set on a pedestal here, living in their divine eternal lands while their churches and priests raised followers for them.

The prime material plane prevented all powerful forces from entering, and even if a god were to make a material body and descend they would only have the strength of a peak Legend at most. Of course, they held another title; they were called Saints. Even if their real bodies descended they would still have the same name.

Hence, there were many situation in the prime material plane where high-ranked Legends besieged Saints and caused their fall. Sometimes they even managed to rob them of their divine force. Those gods would basically not let their real bodies descend and could only do that with their clones.

‘Legends are the most powerful in the prime material plane. If I can become one quickly, I’ll have enough power to protect myself. Besides, I need to do that to gain divine force.’ Leylin stroked his chin. As he had gotten enough nutrients growing up, he was already rather tall for a 13-year-old, as could be seen in the mirror. Besides his face being immature, he was practically a little adult.

‘Is the reason for the bottleneck in my stats that I’ve yet to fully develop?’ Leylin pondered over his situation, ‘Based on this progress, it’ll probably take centuries of training to reach the rank of Legend. That’s too long, and I haven’t even considered what comes after…’

Leylin conjectured that the Legends of the World of Gods were quite similar to Morning Star Magi. They possessed abilities that surpassed imagination, and while one used legendary magic the other used Arcane Arts. In addition, they both met the bare requirements for entering the ancient war campaign, and after advancing, they would undergo a massive transformation.

‘Compared to the rankings of Magi, the division of ranks in the World of Gods are greater in number. In addition, those high-ranked Legends have abilities comparable to rank 5 Radiant Moon Magi…’ Even in the prime material plane, there were many powerful beings amongst the natives of this world. While there were high-ranked Legends, there were still many children of gods, divine beings, and even demigods.

Based on Leylin’s thoughts, their abilities would not lose out to rank 6 Breaking Dawn Monarchs, or even a near rank 7 like him.

“The World of Gods is filled with danger,” Leylin sighed. Not only were there churches and followers all over the continent, the gods had eyes everywhere in their children and family. The moment abnormalities were discovered, and he attracted the attention of the gods… Leylin instantly felt his scalp prickle in fear.

‘Perhaps… Adventuring is not a good option. There are many ways to increase the lifespan of wizards. I can use time to train… Besides, my main body can afford to wait for me!’ Leylin changed his mind.

Without external dangers, he didn’t mind spending more time if that would ensure his safety.

“Young Master Leylin, your afternoon classes are starting! Don’t make Master Anthony wait too long!” A gentle voice was heard from outside, and Leylin was pulled back to reality.

“Alright!” Leylin found a towel and wiped at the droplets of water on his body, and then headed to a room outside.

There were two maids with pretty faces and blushes on their cheeks. They went forward, using their tender little hands to straighten the creases on his clothes.

In a feudal family, the family head and young master’s personal maids were very important. They not only had to serve their masters in their daily lives, but also take care of their master’s bodily needs. If nothing went wrong, this role was usually taken on by the daughter of the housekeeper.

The Faulen Family obviously could not do away with this custom. Leylin’s two personal maids were the daughters of the main housekeeper Leon. It was obvious that they had already prepared themselves mentally and were even slightly excited, but Leylin had no plans to do anything.

‘I’m only thirteen. Although young masters might have become experienced in that area at this age, they can’t be compared to me…’ Leylin knew how to control himself.

“Claire, Clara! Has Master Anthony arrived?” Leylin watched these two sisters, and only when the flush spread down to their pale necks did he ask them teasingly.

“Ye- yes, young master!” Claire blushed as she answered, feeling slightly relieved yet also disappointed.

“I can’t let my teacher wait for too long…” Leylin smiled as he left, not forgetting to tease them for a while.

“But this’ll only go on for these two years…” Smelling that sophisticated aroma, Leylin mumbled to himself.

……

Rays of sunlight shone in through the window, brightening up the hall.

“Mentor Anthony!” Leylin respectfully bowed. While he’d already learnt all the knowledge that the scholar knew, Leylin did not act too rudely since manners were compulsory for nobles.

“Leylin, you did well!” Anthony was already an old man, his kind voice low and his eyes shining. It was obvious that he truly liked this student.

“I’ve already taught you everything in terms of etiquette and speech in the continent. Today, we shall delve into its history…” Anthony produced a thick yellow tome that looked like a dictionary and placed it on the desk.

History was a rare subject even among nobles, only a few scholars focused on it. However, Leylin differed from the rest; he was extremely interested in this subject.

“History is confusing and tasteless. Many nobles hate it. Can you tell me why you chose this?” Anthony caressed the cover of the volume, looking rather nostalgic.

“It’s because knowing history makes one wise. It’s like a mirror that allows us to know ourselves better. No matter how foolish or absurd a situation, it’s already occurred in the past. We need to prevent such things from repeating.”

“A novel idea… cough cough… that makes sense… cough cough…” Anthony’s face was flushed, but he suddenly began to cough, his body bending into a stooping position.

“If you can see that, you’re definitely my student… Of course, you have Ernest as your master and might not think much of this, but I hope you’ll take this!” Anthony’s hands trembled as he produced a white silken bundle and unwrapped it layer by layer, revealing the emblem within.

“This is the proof of my glory as a scholar, presented to me in the king’s capital by the God of Knowledge. It is now yours… Cough cough…” Anthony’s hands trembled as he placed the emblem in Leylin’s hands, “I believe you will not tarnish its glory!”

“I swear on it!” Sensing that this old man’s life force was already fading, Leylin answered seriously.

While he already had a wizard for a mentor, Leylin had not abandoned his studies of culture, and Anthony taught him very seriously. It could be said that in these 8 years, the old man had already spent a lot of effort on him.

‘What a great teacher!’ Leylin judged inside, but had no plans of helping him. On one hand, he wanted to avoid revealing himself, and on the other, the concepts in the World of Gods were different. In the eyes of believers, death was merely another beginning. With the guidance of a priest, their souls would rise with glory to the land of the gods, where they could live an eternal life.

Chapter 798: Wither

A pungent herbal odour wafted through a dimly lit room, mixing with the strong smell of incense. The two scents mixed to leave one light-headed.

An old scholar lay on a bed with an exquisite brocade silk quilt draped over him, on the last leg of his life. The atmosphere was heavy, and light sniffs sounded out on occasion before they were suppressed.

Leylin was clad in black ceremonial attire as he stood amongst the guests, expressionless as he watched the old man on the bed. There was no sign of the inexperience on his face from before, and instead he seemed more mature, like a handsome young man.

It was obviously Anthony on the bed. This scholar was a normal human after all, and his life force had been diminishing for a long time. Being able to hold on to till date was already something that greatly surprised Leylin.

On top of his role as a student about to send his master off, Leylin had a more important matter to attend to.

At this moment, Anthony’s body twitched and his throat moved. There was a slight flush on his face, and it was obvious that death was near.

“Priest! Get the priest!” His wife shrieked, and the children around her burst into tears.

The crowd split into two, revealing the sorrowful face on Bishop Tapris. “The gods will watch over you from the divine realm.”

“Thank you! Thank you, Lord Bishop!” Anthony’s wife wept. As a bishop of the god of knowledge, Tapris evidently had a high status on Faulen Island, and being able to have him attend meant Anthony was given face. While Leylin suspected this had to do with his powerful family, it was still a good thing, no?

Tapris waved his arms, showering him in holy light and stabilising Anthony’s condition. Afterwards, the scholar began his last prayer. It might instead be called a narration of his memories. “My life… began at the island of Sicily….”

“Leylin, my student, I hope to see the day you succeed. Even in the divine realm, I’ll be rooting for you!”

“I understand, master!” Leylin quickly hastened forward, the A.I. Chip’s detective abilities being raised to the maximum.

Tapris was moved by Anthony’s mention of Leylin, something he’d done even after reciting his will. It showed how well Anthony thought of his student; his own investment hadn’t been wasted.

“I… I see the glamour of the gods…” Anthony struggled for the last time, raising his palm. The light in his eyes dimmed, and his arms powerlessly fell to the side of the bed.

“Nooo…” “Anthony…” “My dearest Anthony…” Many cries began to sound in the room.

Tapris’ face grew even more pious as he began Anthony’s eulogy, “He was a learned scholar and a good samaritan, one who was willing to help others. As a follower of the god of knowledge, Anthony Blunton used his entire life to pass on the teachings of the gods. The gates to the divine realm shall open for him in death…”

‘It’s here!’ A trace of emotion flickered in Leylin’s eyes. Through his powerful senses, he saw huge, shining golden gates. The gates opened to a bright holy light, within which Anthony’s soul rose from his body on its own. After taking another peek at the world of the living, he threw himself inside…

‘The divine realm, situated in a plane above the prime material plane…’ Leylin sighed inside.

‘Normal followers’ souls must first enter the soil and, after being evaluated by the God of Death, advance into the divine realms of the various gods. However, Anthony’s soul bypassed that procedure. Is this a privilege from the bishop?’ Leylin wondered.

After the souls of followers reached the divine realms, they would in theory become petitioners, henceforth breaking away from mortality. As long as the god and their divine realm were not destroyed, they would basically exist together with the god.

To a certain extent, this was a sort immortality, but they could not be bothered by external forces.

‘It’s rumoured that high-ranked petitioners can undergo a transition in terms of their souls, becoming something like a holy spirit… Every such one is a precious asset of the god, but their numbers are…’ Based on Leylin’s thoughts, these holy spirits were souls that could not die nor be extinguished, very similar to materialised souls.

This meant that, in theory, every holy spirit was comparable to the truesoul of a Breaking Dawn Magus.

‘While the formation of holy spirits relies entirely on external forces, there is the benefit of living a stress-free immortal life while depending on the gods. Over time, the defences of the gods’ divine realms must have grown extremely terrifying…’

With a limitless number of believers, holy spirits, and the power of being the authority in that realm, gods were basically invincible in their own divine realms. Even the more powerful deities couldn’t easily dispose of the weaker ones if they were in their own realms, and they would have to pay a terrible price.

As for those Magi who had accidentally intruded into a divine realm… the result was obvious.

‘Evidently, master Anthony’s soul has a ways to go to meet the requirements to become a holy spirit. The mighty god of knowledge, Oghma, would obviously not make an exception for him… But with the bishop paving the path for him, he’d probably be in a better situation than many petitioners.’

After the divine lights retracted and the guiding force disappeared, Leylin’s tense body relaxed. Bishop Tapris approached him then as well, having completed the ceremony, “Leylin!”

“Lord Bishop!” Leylin bowed to him respectfully. After all, he was a follower of the god of knowledge even if in name.

“Anthony was a pious follower. He will definitely be treated well in His kingdom, there’s no need to worry…” Tapris consoled him, and seemed to have more to say.

Leylin and Tapris left the room, heading to a garden. Those people around had voluntarily left this area to them. “If I don’t remember wrong, you’ve already held your coming of age ceremony. You’re now a true man!” Bishop Tapris shifted the topic to Leylin.

“Yes, it was conducted last month…” Leylin answered modestly. Based on the customs of this world, boys would be considered adults once they hit 15, and could marry and have children.

“I was by your side when you were born… At that time, you were a little guy, still in your infancy. You’ve gotten so big in the blink of an eye…” Bishop Tapris laughed gently, as if reminiscing. As a rank 10 priest, the years did not leave marks on his face. In reality, he was much older than Anthony.

“But… I rarely see you attending celebrations at the church. Baron Jonas might be busy with work, but Lady Sarah is a very devout follower…” Tapris’ voice showed a hint of disapproval.

“My apologies, lord bishop! I often conduct experiments with master Ernest and I must lose track of time…” Leylin quickly apologised.

A look of helplessness appeared on Bishop Tapris’ face. Wizards in general had the least piety in them. Many of them were just general followers, and he’d long since expected this. In reality, while the entire Faulen family might be followers of the god of knowledge, they had never completely lost themselves in the teachings of the god.

In many areas on the continent, the worldly authority that nobles had were perpetually in conflict with gods’ authority. Even Baron Jonas had brought in a new god, Ilmater the Crying God, while the church of knowledge already existed. He planned to build a church of wealth, allowing other gods to spread faith in them amongst the followers.

This was the instinct of a noble, but Tapris obviously couldn’t accept it. His plan was to pull in the next generation head of the Faulen Family.

It was a pity that wizard Leylin was just like his father. While he never forgot to donate and make sacrifices to the church, he rarely took part in zealous religious ceremonies. On top of that, he was a wizard and had help from his mentor… Tapris’ expression grew darker.

“My apologies for my rude actions, Bishop Tapris! Please allow me to donate ten gold coins to the church to repent for my sins. On top of that, please inform me the next time there are celebrations and gatherings!” When it came to matters of faith, Leylin had long since planned to treat them with less importance. However, since Tapris had brought it up, he had no choice but to do this.

Anyway, he already had plans to go to the church’s celebrations every once in a while, pretending to be a follower.

“Good! There will be a holy baptism seven days later. It is a day in remembrance of the god of knowledge’s feat in reforming the demon, Angmar. The church will hold a grand celebration, so I hope to see you there…”

“It would be my honour to. I’ll definitely go!” Since this was a personal invite from Tapris, Leylin agreed straightforwardly.

“Good!” Tapris nodded, and was then asked away by someone who had been waiting for him beside them. Besides Anthony’s funeral, there were many matters he had to attend to.

After the Lord Bishop left, Leylin remained in the garden, watching the white rose behind the wooden railing while deep in thought. ‘He wants me to go there personally? What is that supposed to be? A warning?’

In reality, with his status as a noble the power of the church was not as immense as one would expect it to be. If Tapris dared overstep his boundaries, he would definitely be jointly resisted by the entirety of the nobility in the Dambrath Kingdom.

Chapter 800: Request and Preparation

Isabel stood in the drawing room, and she still had the long golden hair and blue eyes that Leylin was familiar with. However, her pretty face was stern and icy, and her sharp gaze held an aura of danger.

She wore tight-fitting soft leather armour and had a black scabbard for a longsword at her waist, her slender legs forming a beautiful arc. Leylin sensed an iciness and despair in her temperament, as well as the flames of revenge hidden deep within. There was also evil.

“Long time no see, cousin Leylin! I’m so glad you’re still doing well!” Isabel drawled in a hoarse voice. Her icy gaze seemed to melt a little while watching Leylin, becoming more welcoming.

“Aunt, I’ll be off now!” Isabel bade Sarah farewell, while the rims of Sara’s eyes turned red.

“What happened?” After Isabel left, Leylin’s expression turned dark.

“Ahh… my pitiful little sister…” Madam Sarah began to weep, and Leylin could only stay by her side.

Through the inarticulate descriptions from his mother, Leylin somewhat guessed the situation. Cousin Isabel’s family had been struck by a disaster months ago. Her family had been massacred in cold blood, and there were traces of demons and devils left behind at the scene, which meant it might have something to do with an evil deity’s ceremony.

Practically no one survived other than Isabel, and that was because she’d been at the church of the Goddess of Agriculture.

While Isabel’s father was not a true noble, he did have a temporary status as a baron. While this status would only last for his life, these actions immediately resulted in anger from the church and royalty, and the town hall even announced that they would find the murderer.

There was another issue. Her family had always been a liaison between the Faulen Family and the Dambrath Kingdom on the continent. The consequences of this act was that the Faulen Family would lose all means of contact and news from the continent. Needless to say, there were also many troublesome matters which needed settling. Whatever it was, having a devil involved made things complicated. Leylin’s father in this world had already set sail after he had gotten this information, planning to go to the continent and solve the problems.

“You have to console your cousin Isabel properly. She only has us left, and I heard that she even had to deal with an attempted assassination just recently! Oh, my poor child…” Madam Sarah wept, while Leylin nodded seriously.

Cousin Isabel just now obviously lacked the temperament that a priest should have. Evidently, the revenge she wanted to exact, or perhaps the series of shocks she had endured after the incident had caused her to walk the path of blood and vengeance. Who knew, she might even be involved in some ceremony or sacrifice to the gods.

“Hm? This timing… does it mean Bishop Tapris already knows about this?” Leylin came to a sudden realisation. With the communication between churches, it was very possible that he had received the news before Leylin had, which made his recent invitation very interesting.

“A storm is coming…” Leylin walked out of the drawing room. As he watched the overcast skies, his expression became as gloomy as the weather.

‘Something seems off…’ Leylin touched his chin, ‘Her family can almost be seen a branch of our Faulen family in the Dambrath Kingdom. This act against them seems to be aimed at us…’

‘Are the up-and-coming Faulen lands now being coveted by the nobles? Or is this an effect from us eliminating a few pirate crews sometime ago?’ A multitude of possibilities arose in front of Leylin. When he regained his senses, he was already standing in front of Ernest’s room.

“Is it Leylin? I still have important experiments to finish…” Ernest’s annoyed voice could be heard from within the room.

“I’m sorry, master, but I feel like we need to have a serious talk,” Leylin’s smile had no effect on him.

“Fine, but only for half an hour!” The door was pulled open, revealing Ernest’s haggard face. His hair was messy, and there were dark circles under his eyes.

One could see filthy clothes and all sorts of junk everywhere upon entering the room. There was practically no place that was clean save for the laboratory.

Leylin flung a grey shirt that had been tossed onto the sofa away and sat down. Ernest seemed to think of something at this point and wiped his face, watching his prodigious student.

“Leylin! You seem to be have met with some trouble… does it have to do with the church of knowledge you mentioned in the morning? It shouldn’t trouble you this much; is it something else?” Ernest was rather concerned when it came to this student of his, someone who had a bright future ahead of him.

“Yes. It’s a huge problem…” Leylin laughed bitterly and began to narrate the situation.

“So you want me to act and maintain the safety of the manor?” Ernest’s brows fluttered, as if he had seen through Leylin’s plans. It had to be said that this was perhaps the best choice.

“No, no! I actually want to ask master…” Leylin shook his head instead and requested something else, causing Ernest to watch his student in wide-eyed shock.

A moment later, a gigantic flying bird soared from the manor, with was a figure seated atop it.

“My student really knows how to order his teacher about…” This figure was evidently Ernest, though he was now hastening his journey and cursing along the way.

“The strength of Father’s guards and a rank 9 magician should be enough to take care of the dangers and challenges…” Leylin muttered as he stood by the window, watching the bird shrink into a tiny black dot as it flew away.

If he was the one who had orchestrated the elimination of Isabel’s family, causing Baron Faulen to lose his connection to the mainland, it would only be the first step. Next he would create traps and hinder the baron who was heading towards the continent,

The Faulen family was a noble family that was new and still developing. Once Baron Jonas died, there would only be a widowed mother and an orphaned son left behind. He didn’t have any support either, and was the easiest to deal with.

Hence, protecting the baron and his men was the key in this situation. And the only high-ranked power the Faulen Family could rely on right now was the rank 9 wizard Ernest.

“The meagre benefits of our island and port are far from being sufficient for those great nobles. The power that the other party holds shouldn’t be too powerful. Hopefully, with master Ernest’s strength coupled with that of the family, we should be able to successfully take care of this matter…” Leylin’s eyes flashed.

Of course, while he focused mostly on Baron Jonas, it wasn’t as if he prepared nothing for the Faulen Family. Initially, he had planned to get Ernest to handle everything. In the worst case scenario, Leylin and his mother themselves would be safe. Perhaps this was something Baron Jonas realised as well, which would be the reason he hadn’t invited that old friend of his on the journey. However, Leylin had spoiled his plans.

“With master Ernest, there’s no need to worry about the baron, but the defences of the manor are diminished by a great degree…” Leylin sighed, “I’ll have to make up for it myself…”

Leylin had always been training his abilities as a wizard on the sly, but he’d never had the chance to use them in real battles. Of course, with his experience prior to this reincarnation, this wasn’t a huge issue. He rather anticipated practicing on a few dumb bandits and the like.

“Alright, now to see what master left for me…” Leylin returned to his room and fiddled with a few artifacts on the table. Ernest was no fool, and he’d obviously made preparations for his student’s safety by leaving behind a few protective artifacts.

“Hm, let me see…” Leylin’s eyes were filled with curiosity as he tidied up the artifacts on the table. Ernest had only left three artifacts behind. There was a black ring and two unknown scrolls with some magic patterns on them, emitting a mysterious luster.

“Appraisal!” Leylin tapped on them, and several streaks of white light burst out, returning with information about them.

“A magic ring with a protective shield that displaces attacks, as well as two rank 4 spell scrolls. Mm… One’s a Stone Skin spell while the other is an offensive Blizzard spell…”

Given the types of the spells, Ernest had evidently made them himself. They were the best quality artifacts he could make given his rank, and on top of that there was the additional costs from the high rate of failure.

Leylin put on the ring and played around with the scrolls in his hands. In many cases, rank 4 magic scrolls could even turn the tides of battle from defeat to victory, and Leylin was very aware of what they were worth. Though many of the materials to make the scrolls had been supplied by the Faulen Family, Leylin still felt his heart warm.

“These things give me some more security… I might need to modify the plan…” Leylin muttered to himself as he returned to his room, sending the sisters away.

“A.I. Chip, show me my current stats!” Leylin commanded.

[Leylin Farlier. Age: 15. Race: Human, Rank 6 Wizard. Strength: 1.6. Agility: 1. Vitality: 1.5. Spirit: 6. Condition: Healthy. Innate Talents: Sturdy, Erudite. Spell Slots: Rank 2 Spell slot (2), Rank 1 Spell slot (3), Rank 0 Spell slot (???)]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned.

Chapter 802: Celebration

Lively streams of people filled the bustling pier. The air was filled with the smell of sea and rum.

As the horse carriage entered the port, Leylin watched the busy scene outside through a little window within. Sailors, farmers, soldiers, adventurers, and all sorts of people entered his sights. They were quickly classified, marking those who had decent strength and harboured malicious intent.

As he had been immersed in the study of magic, Leylin rarely came out from the manor, much less came to this area. ‘It seems like the Faulen Family has managed this place extremely well; it even surpasses my expectations. It’s understandable that someone might covet this place.’

Leylin glanced towards the group next to the crossroad. A wandering bard was now performing there, and he could not help but exclaim in his surprise. “Hm? There are even bards wandering around!”

Bards in the World of Gods weren’t just street performers. They were usually spies that were primarily responsible for probing for intel, or they made a living out of selling information. Most importantly, they were usually very powerful.

With how much the Faulen Pier was flourishing, quite a few bards had come forth to perform or on vacation.

“Jacob, what’s the name of that bard? How long has he been here for?” Leylin enquired.

“That one? I heard that he’s called Xuno and comes from the faraway Northern Lands. His poems are always very pleasant to listen to and there are always interesting stories. The baron was even thinking about inviting him to perform in the manor some time ago…” Jacob answered quickly.

The commoners here quickly gave way and presented their greetings to the authority that managed the island and port. Sitting in the middle of the horse carriage, Leylin was however unperturbed by everyone’s reverence and instead furrowed his brows, “There are far too many people here, and yet the frequency at which the patrol appears is too low…

“Jacob, how much strength does our family have?”

Jacob froze for a moment, surprised by Leylin’s question. “Are you referring to the patrol, young master?”

However, for someone like him who had once been the commander of this place, Jacob knew the situation with the patrol very well. “We have two groups here that come up to a hundred people total. They’re all great little guys with good strength.”

“Great little guys? Good strength? That means there aren’t any with exemplary strength, and they are only able to suppress those sailors and thieves?” Leylin grew speechless, “Out of this hundred, how many have professions? How much armour do we have? And long-range weapons such as crossbows?”

In the World of Gods, where exemplary powers were suppressed to the utmost, armour and weapons were a huge factor when it came to strength. Troops with great equipment and training would find no trouble dealing with those with professions below rank 5. If there were enough of them, even those at rank 10 and below did not dare go head to head with soldiers.

Of course, after rank 10, numbers would not be enough to make up for the lack of quality.

“Professions? Armour? Crossbow?” Jacob’s surprised voice sounded in front of him.

“What? We don’t have them?” Leylin sighed.

“Professions? The leaders of those two groups are retired military officials that the baron recruited. They’re low ranked warriors who haven’t even been certified to rank 5. As for armour, those who are vice leaders and above all have one set, and there are a total of twelve. And crossbows… Our patrol doesn’t have equipment like that, though there seem to be a few stored in the manor…” Jacob looked a little flustered as he spoke.

“Too little, it’s much too little! This is too weak…” Leylin seemed to be complaining.

“Young Master, why do you say so?” A look of surprise appeared on Jacob’s face, “A Baron has over a hundred elite troops. Even in the kingdom, that power is equivalent to what a viscount can have… In order to bear the costs of this group, the baron throws in a large amount of his earnings…”

“Baron… this…” Leylin had a sudden realisation. The Faulen Island was a newly developed territory with no population. It was difficult to even get farmers to plow the lands here, not even considering recruiting troops.

If not for the Faulen Island being on an isolated piece of land, having to deal with numerous vicious pirates, Baron Jonas would long since have halved the number of troops here. In order to recruit enough people, there was no way but to hire them by offering large amounts of money, and he probably had to take care of their food and their families.

While the barons in the Dambrath Kingdom could have many troops, they never had so many unless it was wartime due to the great costs.

If not for the benefits from the trade, the Faulen Family would long since have gone bankrupt due to the army.

“The rise of a noble family is truly difficult…” Leylin sighed inside. The father of this body had gone through hundreds of battles, and with difficulty obtained this uninhabited island as his territory. With his hard work over half his life, Baron Jonas finally made this area a little popular, yet now his work was immediately coveted.

“If all of the hundred were to have equipment…” Leylin calculated it. Creating armour was extremely expensive in the World of Gods, and a complete set could even be a knight’s treasure passed on through generations. The value was equal to even a small manor. If modified by magicians or blessed by priests, the armour’s price would be even more terrifying and perhaps comparable to a city!

“It’s not practical to change the armour of the patrol, but I can think of something when it comes to their weapons. At the very least, they can’t use rusted metal…” Leylin sighed and clutched at his forehead.

He was no longer in his original body, where he was exceedingly wealthy. In the World of Gods, he spent only a few gold coins every month, and most of it was spent on spell materials.

‘There are ways for low-ranked magicians to earn money, but that’s mostly labour from copying spells or brewing low-ranked potions. There’s not enough time… Sigh, in the World of Gods, the small nobles don’t do that well. Only the churches are truly wealthy. The paladins of the church of the Goddess of Singing Waters all had a full set of metal armour, and some even had been blessed with divine spells…’

Leylin could not help but think back to what he had seen before as a soul seed. The wealth of the churches of the gods were renowned in the continent, especially that of the Goddess of Wealth. It was said that their headquarters had been built with gold and silver, and even the ground was paved with gold bricks. Leylin, who was going insane over his poverty, had even decided to steal everything once he made his mark on this world.

“Then… Can I use them?” Suppressing the immoral thoughts he had, Leylin asked Jacob who was outside.

“Of course! As the next-in-line of the Faulen Family, the young master’s wish is our command!” Jacob answered resolutely, “Do you need me to send down the signal?”

“No, there’s no need to for now. I want to go to the church of knowledge, and it shouldn’t be too dangerous. Tell them…” Leylin spoke apathetically.

He added some more words on the inside, ‘You’re useless against priests or holy warriors. On top of that, few would be willing to fight against the church and god they believe in.’

After Leylin was done with his instructions, the carriage once more sank into silence. He did not continue speaking and only judged the terrain and buildings outside curiously.

As the carriage reached a spacious area, Jacob’s voice was heard, “Young Master, we’ve reached the Knowledge Shrine!”

Leylin looked outside the window. The streets were clean and tidy, and the passersby were very cultured. Whether it was farmers or soldiers walking past, all would control their footsteps such that they were softer, appearing prudent and reverent. Put next to the bustle and chaos at the port, the two were practically worlds apart.

A lofty and majestic church emitted dazzling light through the carriage. The churches of the gods were always constructed splendidly, being beautiful and solemn,

“O god of knowledge…” Many voices could be heard saying their prayers.

As this was a day of celebration, many followers of the god of knowledge had congregated here. The spacious floor was crowded with people.

In order to worship the god of knowledge, Jonas had dedicated the best section of land on the port and did not accept even a copper coin. In the eyes of the priests however, this was a given.

“Seems like the ‘cultured people’ of the port are here!” Leylin sighed as he rubbed his face, changing his expression to a sunny one.

“Young Master Leylin!”

“Welcome, welcome!” “My, look who’s here!”

Many familiar faces crowded around. They included his uncles and aunts, and he had no choice but to smile and greet them one by one.

With Anthony as his mentor, Leylin had no faults when it came to his manners. What he showed off was his most perfect image as the next-in-line of a noble family, and everyone sang his praises.

The price, however, was that after the many greetings Leylin found his facial muscles had begun to stiffen, and much time had passed.

‘I know this is troublesome, but it’s necessary. Nobles…’ Leylin sighed as he entered the large shrine and threw a small bag of gold coins into the donation box. The pot-bellied priests beamed in reply.

Leylin looked around. The ornamentation of Oghma’s church wasn’t half bad. There were bookshelves and statues all around, and it was filled with a scholarly atmosphere…

Chapter 803: Marquis Louis

After finishing his prayers in the main hall of the church, a few maids finally led the way to bishop Tapris.

Tapris was very frank the moment he started speaking, “My child, you seem to have run into some trouble!”

“Yes, respected Bishop. I urgently need teaching and guidance from the god of knowledge.” Leylin secretly grew a lot more relaxed just due to Tapris’ attitude. He was indeed like what Leylin had suspected, and only intended to take this opportunity to knock his family’s confidence. He didn’t have any plans to actually replace the Faulens.

If this was the case, foregoing a few benefits in exchange for his help was not a difficult issue for him to discuss.

Judging by his behaviour, Bishop Tapris must have also been nodding secretly to himself. As heir to the Faulen family, Leylin’s promises would have to be fulfilled even by Baron Jonas, and this was one made in a church with a deity as their witness.

‘It seems like Baron Jonas has an outstanding successor!’ Tapris thought slowly to himself, then looked at Leylin, “Dear little Leylin, have you heard of Viscount Tim?”

“Viscount Tim?” Leylin’s voice was filled with doubt. Under Anthony’s guidance, he certainly understood the upper class nobles of the Dambrath Kingdom, yet he hadn’t seemed to have heard of any deeds performed by this viscount.

“Oh, look at me, getting ahead of myself! Viscount Tim was just crowned a few months ago, so it’s perfectly normal for you not to have heard of him before. His father, on the other hand, is a distinguished person you must have heard of before. Marquis Louis!”

Tapris watched Leylin’s expression expectantly.

“Marquis Louis? The king’s brother!” Leylin exhaled lightly. Although he knew that things wouldn’t be simple this time, he didn’t think that the nobles involved would have a direct connection to royalty.

The nobility was never a tight knit community. The power struggle between the regional and central nobles had never ceased for even a moment, and although there was a possibility of them uniting as one in the face of divine authority, an instinctive battle for benefit would begin once the moment the pressure from the outside world was reduced.

Within the kingdom, the regional nobles and the kingdom’s central nobles were the two factions that put up the fiercest fights.

“That’s right. Viscount Tim is already of age. Although he’s the second son, Marquis Louis adores him very much, and even wishes to obtain a piece of feudal property for him…” Tapris held his tongue, and left the rest to Leylin’s imagination.

“So that’s how it is!” Leylin nodded seriously. Although the king and his people ruled over the entire Dambrath Kingdom, they couldn’t possibly own all the territory. Moreover, after the division of property across the generations and the emergence of other noble families, the amount of territorial land that the king now governed directly was already quite small.

To date, all the territories in the kingdom had been divided until there was practically nothing left. Even if one was a prince or princess, if they were not particularly favoured by the king, they would not even receive any hereditary titles. The highest ranked titles they could receive was that of an Count Palantine, or a Marquis, and they would only possess a few manors.

Non-hereditary title of high rank

As a brother to the king of this generation, Marquis Louis was still able to fish up a decent amount of benefits. The Baltic archipelago was his fief, and the total area of the whole stretch of islands far exceeded that of the Faulens. He even owned several decent deepwater ports.

To put it bluntly, even the Faulens had to rely on a tremendous volume of trade in the Baltic Archipelago and play second fiddle in order to toil for money.

However, Louis still had to consider his first son. It would be very foolish of him to divide his territory, and hence he had set his sights somewhere else. Perhaps he had now turned his gaze towards the Faulen’s territory

Stripping another noble family of their inherited territory for no reason would definitely send huge waves rippling through the circle of nobility. But if this family was extinguished with no successor and Marquis Louis had Tim carry on their family name, then things would be a lot easier. His influence as a marquis would also minimise the consequences of this incident.

“Many thanks for being straightforward, respected bishop. From now on, the church of knowledge will be fully accepted by the Faulen territory. Additionally, we will portion out another plot of territorial land in the eastern part of the island to offer as tribute to the church,” Leylin rose and gave his thanks.

Although this was only an intelligence report, he felt like the possibility of it being true was extremely high.

Firstly, the territory under the Faulen family actually did thin out Marquis Louis’ profits. Even though it was only by a little, it was enough to upset him. Secondly, the Faulens were a newly rising noble family, and they didn’t have complicated relationships with other nobles that would have been difficult to deal with. There were only minimal consequences associated with making his move on them.

‘Could it be that this is also a contest between the regional and central parties?’ Leylin had experienced much more trickery than this, and had depth in his foresight.

‘The Faulen Family started out with military service, and were the king’s imperial bodyguards from the beginning. Thus, they could be regarded as part of the central party. But ever since they obtained their feudal property and arrived here, the family was actually already inclined towards the regional party. That was also how my father the baron handled it. However, what was awkward was that the people of the Faulen island had very little contact with the people from the mainland, as it was a lonely island situated far away. Hence, they haven’t been accepted by the regional nobles yet… Which is the reason why this family is now in an awkward situation in which we cannot rely on either side…’

After thinking thoroughly about this, Leylin was suddenly struck by a huge realisation, ‘No wonder. If I saw this situation, even I wouldn’t be able to resist taking action. There are plenty of advantages, yet the risks are very minor. Perhaps Viscount Tim is also pitifully begging for this opportunity…’

In fact, Leylin’s second guess was much closer to the truth than his first guess, but there were a few minor differences.

Although his opponent was just a viscount and seemed relatively less capable, he was backed by the marquis and was even the king’s nephew. If one took their eyes off him for even a second, he would easily trigger chaos.

However, it was fortunate that he was just a favoured second son. Even Marquis Louis wouldn’t spend much energy on him, much less alert the king. As long as he didn’t kill his opponent, there probably wouldn’t be much of a counterattack.

After all, when it came to issues like schemes to seize the territory of smaller families, because most of the bigger nobles did it on the sly, these rumours were restricted only to their thoughts, and could not be spoken of in polite company.

Tapris personally sent Leylin out of the shrine. Just as Leylin was about to board his carriage, Tapris muttered softly in a deep voice next to his ear, “It seems that a surge of pirates have escaped to the vicinity recently. I hope you’ll take care! May the god of knowledge bless you.”

“Got it!” There was a glint in Leylin’s eyes, and he gave Tapris a profound look before boarding the carriage.

The body of the carriage kept rising and falling as the wheels rolled on. Leylin sat in the carriage with his eyes shut, yet his thoughts kept moving.

‘That cunning Bishop Tapris. Is he preparing to lay his bet on both parties?’ As a matter of fact, Leylin really did want to get assistance from the church this time. If he could personally exert pressure on the marquis with the power of the church of knowledge, the marquis would surely give up on making such moves.

But this was evidently impossible. Even Bishop Tapris did not own some labour headquarters for him to exert his authority. If they dispatched warriors and priests from the shrine, they would be deemed to be in favour of the Faulen family. Tapris had also clearly rejected doing so.

Now it seemed that although Tapris had only given a bit of the intel, he had managed to immediately gain a heap of profits. Even if Baron Jonas was here, he wouldn’t dare to go back on his word. If Viscount Tim succeeded, he wouldn’t forget to rope in Tapris as well. If placing his bets on both parties would guarantee him profits, why wouldn’t he?

Of course, it wasn’t that there was no other way to obtain assistance from the church, but that would require dedicating all his territory to them. However, both sides would suffer and be destroyed indiscriminately if he used this method. Additionally, they would be boycotted by all the nobles from the mainland, and be seen as traitors by the nobles!

After weighing the matter, Leylin reached the conclusion that things hadn’t escalated to such a nasty stage, and he didn’t have the courage to abandon his social class. There was no doubt that he would use ‘that’ method.

“Pirates?” The look in Leylin’s pupils seemed distant. Since the other party was also a noble family that controlled overseas trade and had numerous harbours, they evidently had a formidable maritime force.

Even the pirates nearby might be secretly under their control. It was highly possible for them to send out a group of men to cause a commotion in the Faulen Island and use this to create pressure, or even attack the manor directly and silence the Faulens. They did it once long ago anyway.

“Relying on the hundred man patrol to get rid of this wave of pirates is rather challenging…” Leylin stroked his chin. He had never underestimated his opponent’s strength. With a marquis backing him, that viscount could easily dispatch tens of professionals.

“Someone above rank 15 is absolutely impossible, but there might be one who is above rank 10, and a few elite professionals above rank 5… It won’t be easy to defeat them…” Leylin quickly evaluated his opponent’s strength, just at the most basic level.

Of course, the Faulens didn’t only have the harbour patrol, but the real masters were definitely travelling with Baron Jonas. Only the the wizard Ernest had stayed behind to take care of things, but this source of help had also been dispatched by Leylin himself.

“The other party will obviously focus their main strength on the baron. The force they have sent over here should only be a small portion of their main force. It’s not like we can’t fight them with everything we have!” Leylin had a distant look in his eyes.

In fact, he had also considered cowering and hiding in some corner of the mainland, avoiding the situation at hand. He would then slowly accumulate skills and become a great wizard, maybe even a strong Legend. But putting aside the affection from the baron and his wife, even if he could heartlessly abandon everything he had, he was unable to give up on the benefits that the Faulen Family brought him.

A sea of resources was needed for a wizard to advance. Be it expensive materials for him to perform sorcery, or all kinds of magic books and such, a great amount of gold coins was required to purchase them. Without an influential power to gather wealth for him, Leylin would simply be incapable of meeting his needs alone.

Chapter 804: Assassin

A great wizard could not rise without the support of an extremely influential power. It was a pipe dream to achieve such success alone. Were he to try to build up his power and wealth through underhanded means, he would obviously provoke many people.

In comparison, the Faulens had only met with a small inconvenience. Even if Leylin broke away from the family, he would still run into the same problem when trying to make a name for himself.

It was needless to say that his identity as a nobleman was rather decent. At least it allowed Leylin to travel unimpeded in any place where human civilization gathered. He couldn’t bear to give that up.

With the speed at which his strength was improving, the Faulens would one day be unable to meet his demands, thus he had to expand the interests of the family.

If he ate more, others would have less to eat. Leylin had long predicted that the Baltic archipelago and the numerous natural ports owned by Louis’ family would become stumbling blocks in his family’s rise in society.

Even without this incident, the Faulens would one day become enemies with Marquis Louis. After growing aware of this, Leylin’s gaze turned as cold as ice. ‘If that’s the case, I’ll move those blocks away!’

“Compared to the rich and imposing maquis, the Faulen Family is simply not prepared as of now. Even if we emerge victorious in this incident, we are destined to keep a low profile. It would be best… Huh?”

Leylin’s eyes suddenly widened, ‘This energy undulation… A.I. Chip!’

[Beep! Task established, initializing scan… Suspicious person discovered in the vicinity! Gathering of high energy detected! Person is determined to be in possession of powerful explosives.]

The carriage seemed to have turned translucent in the A.I. Chip’s display, revealing the streets and people in the form of numerous lines. A few passersby were sneakily drawing closer to it, and they were marked out by the A.I. Chip.

“Are they assassins? Jacob…” Jacob was currently rushing the carriage along, but hearing Leylin’s voice stunned him for a moment.

“Don’t stop! Don’t show any signs of suspicion or panic. Let’s change direction!” Leylin’s command was transmitted to Jacob, yet it seemed like no else heard it.

Jacob stopped for a moment. He had already viewed voice transmission as an ability unique to a wizard. Being experienced, he immediately knew what the young master had discovered.

*Crack!* The crisp sound of the horsewhip sounded. The carriage, which had been going forth, suddenly made a sharp turn, and entered another junction.

“They’re still following us? Hah… Did they vow not to give up until they achieved their goal?” Leylin could see the route that the assassins were taking through the A.I. Chip, and he couldn’t help but force a smile.

“Jacob, follow the route I’m about to give you.” As the young leader of the Faulen Pier, Leylin couldn’t allow its prosperous image to be damaged, come what may. If word got out about a heir to a noble family getting attacked in a ruckus at the port, it could be a huge blow to the port’s prestige. Many of the less influential merchants would be afraid of getting into trouble, and would rather take a detour than come back again to replenish their supplies. Hence, although Leylin had already discovered the assassins, he couldn’t take action in the middle of the city centre.

Jacob clearly knew this as well, and firmly followed the route that Leylin gave.

Under Leylin’s directions, the carriage swiftly drove out of the market as smoothly as a loach. They arrived at a small road in the countryside, and the assassins hurriedly surrounded them one by one.

“Are you ready? Jacob, break through their line of defense right away, and send a signal to gather the patrolling team!” Leylin appeared very confident.

“But young master, your safety!” Jacob was rather hesitant.

“That’s not an issue. Don’t forget that I’m a wizard, and someone stronger than you at that.” Leylin said without a trace of politeness.

Jacob’s face flushed red, as though he had recalled the few experiences when he had suffered defeat under Leylin’s hands, “Your wish is my command, young master!”

At this moment, a few shadows that appeared to be highly bewildered pounced on them. They had evidently realised that they had been fooled by Leylin earlier on at the port. Their fury even led to them drawing out their murder weapons immediately.

“Are these the bombs of a goblin alchemist?” Leylin shook his head in disapproval as he saw a few jet black objects launched towards the carriage.

If they were attacked by these prohibited items with such immense power in the port, even if Leylin himself wouldn’t suffer the slightest damage, Jacob would definitely sustain injuries or even die, much less the civilians involved.

But now they were in the wilderness. With a widened field of view and Leylin’s prior warning, even Jacob would be able to avoid it.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!*

The violent explosion even caused the entire carriage to disintegrate into pieces, and numerous splinters shot all over the place.

But before this happened, two figures had jumped out of the carriage.

“One, two, three, four. There’s still one more!” Leylin said to himself as he noticed the four figures surrounding him.

He had detected five people through the A.I. Chip, but now it seemed that there was another fellow hiding in the darkness, who was evidently their leader.

“Quick, leave!” Leylin turned around at yelled at Jacob, who had a few traces of blood on his body. He was clearly affected by the explosion just now.“The power of the alchemical bombs are not bad, but unfortunately they are prohibited items. Even if there was a channel to smuggle them, the quantity from before should be their limit.”

“Young master, take care!” Jacob shouted loudly. His muscles were bulging, a sign that his fighting spirit had been aroused. With his hands clenched tight around a decapitator, he rushed swiftly in the direction of the port.

“One of you, follow him! Don’t let him get away!” The four figures seemed to still be immersed in how it was a pity that the alchemical bombs earlier weren’t effective. Seeing how Jacob actually abandoned his master and escaped, their eyes were filled with disbelief. However, as compared to the leader of the imperial bodyguards, Leylin was clearly more important. They made a decision after a few moments of a daze.

A black snake-like figure chased after Jacob, while the other three assassins surrounded Leylin in a triangular formation.

“Heh heh… A noble young master with such thin skin and tender meat!” One of the assassins licked the dagger in his hand, as green light shot out from his eyes like a wolf.

“Act quickly, this is still his territory after all. Someone will come soon!” The explosion earlier on obviously couldn’t be hidden. The three assassins kept drawing closer, their eyes fixated on Leylin’s heart, throat and other vital points. They evidently weren’t planning to let him live for long.

“He’s a wizard, be careful of his tricks!” The moment the voice stopped, a few figures started to encircle Leylin as fast as the wind, and they didn’t even give him the chance to speak.

Three daggers that resembled viper fangs surrounded Leylin. The sharp breeze even sliced at Leylin’s skin.

“They’re well trained.” Leylin quickly made a gesture at the speed of lightning, and he suddenly spat out a single syllable.

*BOOM!* A deafening explosion sounded out, louder than the earlier boms. It deafened the three assassins, and was followed by a ball of fiery white light bursting out from Leylin’s finger. It caused them to involuntarily close their eyes.

These were the rank 0 spells Rank 0 spells Flare and Sonic Snap! Given the situations, instantaneous spells like them were the most appropriate to use. Moreover, Leylin could also adjust and select the spell to his liking, basing it on the circumstances he would encounter. This was much better than those inflexible wizards.

Although they suffered a double blow which caused them to go blind and become giddy, the daggers of the three assassins still sluggishly headed for Leylin. Yet at this instant, Leylin suddenly made his move.

His hand stretched out as quick as lightning, and the dagger of the assassin in the middle came to a stop. An acupoint on his arm seemed to have been hit, and it fell limp and feeble like a dead snake.

‘No…Oh no!’ Before the assassin could even finish this thought, the dagger in his hand had changed ownership and was now in Leylin’s possession.

*Thump! Thump!* Two figures flew backwards. The assassin in the centre, however, was not as fortunate. He knelt on the floor with his hands held behind his back, while the dagger that was previously in his hand was pressed against his neck.

The sensation of the sharp blade made every single strand of hair on his neck stand on end.

“Did you think that I was just a wizard?” Leylin laughed coldly.

Wizards were all relatively solitary. Leylin had moved out long ago by himself, thus practically no one knew about about his wizard rank apart from Ernest. Even his expertise in martial arts was concealed by Jacob under the Baron’s orders.

“I wanted to ask who sent you guys, but it seems like you won’t say…” Leylin’s deep voice sounded like the muttering of a demon to the assassin who was kneeling on the floor.

Moments later, the dagger in Leylin’s hand suddenly cut straight through the assassin’s throat. Great quantities of fresh blood started gushing out of his throat as he gasped greedily for air. The radiance in his eyes slowly dimmed, and he collapsed onto the ground.

Seeing how Leylin killed as if it meant nothing and how he did not even seem to have an uncomfortable reaction to it, the other two surviving assassins stole a glance at each other, both intending to flee.

They never knew that the target they were up against would be this difficult to handle. Not only did he possess rather good magic abilities, he was also proficient in combat. His exquisite control over the battlefield and his merciless killing style were not things that a young nobleman who was inexperienced in life would be capable of.

Now, they practically suspected that some sort of devil resided in this young nobleman’s body, or perhaps this was someone else impersonating him.

‘But we still have hope!’ Determination flashed in both of the assassins’ eyes, and they suddenly started to make their escape.

Chapter 811: Sneak Attack

*Whoosh!* The night sea winds had a fishy, chilly smell that made Jacob shrink back.

As a member of the Faulen Family, he might have long since gotten used to these winds and waves, but the deck that was creaking up and down, as well as the billowing sails above, made him as if he was in a dream. This feeling reached its peak when he saw Leylin, standing proudly at the head of the ship.

They were in a typical double mast sailboat. They weren’t squeezed together even with over 80 people there.

But it wasn’t difficult at all to acquire such a thing with the Faulen Family’s status. No, what shocked Jacob was Young Master Leylin’s behaviour!

‘No… Actually everyone is shocked…’ Jacob looked at the leaders beside him who were scared out of their wits, yet at the same time had a fire burning in their eyes, and chuckled wryly.

Just before they had left, Leylin had cast Nondetection in front of everyone. By Oghma! This was a rank 3 spell, and the young master had not used any items or scrolls at all!

That he could cast a rank 3 spell by himself meant Leylin was rank 7. Without any warning, their young master had become a rank 7 wizard!

‘Gods… Isn’t advancing as a wizard supposed to be the most challenging? Young master’s advancement to rank 5 just two years ago was already enough to have mouths fall agape… And now…’ Jacob sighed. His abundant experiences as an adventurer left him clear on what exactly a fifteen year old rank 7 wizard meant.

If nothing were to happen, he could possibly become a great rank 15 wizard in a few centuries of training! There were few great wizards in the Dambrath Kingdom, and a few of them hired by the royalty had great statuses. His majesty the King had generously given them positions as Earls and territory to rope them in.

However, no great wizard cared for such things that drove others crazy with envy. At their level, the only thing in their sights was the realm of Legends.

And now, a great wizard was about to appear in the Faulen Family? Jacob suddenly felt giddy.

“Cousin Leylin, you’ve worked hard in deceiving me…” Beside Leylin, Isabel didn’t have as many thoughts. While she seemed to be complaining, it was obvious that she was delighted by Leylin’s achievements.

“I never thought my cousin was a genius as a wizard!” Isabel’s eyes twinkled like there were countless stars in them.

“Hehe… everyone has their secrets, just as you do!” Leylin got closer, causing her to look panicked, “I anticipate the day where you will tell me…”

“What kind of joke is this?” Isabel turned her head and left, while Leylin sank deep into thought.

‘There’s no other choice but to do this…’ Leylin sighed. The reason he had shown his strength right before the battle was to strengthen his men’s confidence and will to resist.

Otherwise, the moment they knew that they could be against the personal guard of a Marquis of the Kingdom, even if moral did not immediately crumble, it would be greatly diminished.

Now, with such a young wizard, some would think it was worth it to risk their lives. Even if those regular soldiers did not know what being a 15 year old rank 7 wizard implied, others would gladly warn or tell them.

‘Furthermore, our target this time is only a notorious group of pirates. Even if someone intentionally leaks this out, many would not believe it…’ Leylin sighed once more. He had already done all that he could to the best of his abilities, and all that was left was their luck.

“My lord, we’re here!” A sailor with triangular eyes and a gaze as sharp as a poisonous snake came before Leylin, reporting quietly. There was a thirst in his eyes for blood, as well as a fervour for destruction.

If this was a gaze seen in the manor, Leylin would send down the order for this person to be hung, but now?

‘This is the right attitude if you want to kill someone!’ Leylin was confident that with his methods, even if this person was a poisonous snake, he’d be able to tame him.

“Your name is Robin Hood? You’re a great first mate and navigator! Are you in charge of this ship as well?” Leylin observed the man. He could sense a bloody aura that came from frequent killings, which made it obvious that this person had a very ‘exciting’ life in private.

“Yes, young master Faulen!” Evidently, Robin Hood was surprised that Leylin had been able to remember his name.

“Good!” Leylin had his hands behind his back as he watched the faint image of the islet from the fog. He quickly commanded, “Send down the order. Everyone is to remain hidden. Try not to make any sounds.”

In order to take precautions against the detection and divination spells, Leylin had especially boosted himself with Nondetection before leaving, and had been exceptionally cautious and nimble along the way. It could be said that the chances of being discovered were very low.

Besides, even if they were discovered, nothing much changed except for the scale of the losses that would be incurred.

When the first wave sneakily swam up to the shore and began to mount a secret attack on the opponents’ anchored ships, Leylin knew that the general conclusion had been decided.

Watching the bloody battles, Leylin suddenly laughed. “Seems like the pirates aren’t as strong as I imagined them to be…”

Initially, he had thought that they had the support of the nobles and might have superb equipment and even maybe a magic weapon, but from the looks of it… These pirates wore shabby clothing, and there were even some people of other races and mixed blood in their midst. There weren’t really powerful people in there, and it felt like they were just cannon fodder and not the real deal.

‘Even if we manage to subdue these pirates, they would just be treated as replaceable?’ Leylin stroked his chin as he thought of something.

In such a situation, where his side had been prepared and launched a secret attack with equipment of superior quality to theirs, there was no possibility of failure if their numbers were about equal.

‘Of course, this is a world of exemplaries. The situation might change if a few powerful people show up,’ Leylin stared at a corner of the camp on the barren island. He could sense powerful energy undulations from there.

“Is that leader of the Black Tiger pirates a rank 10 Professional?” Leylin sneered, “Jacob, take over the command. Pay attention to their ships and don’t let anyone get away!”

“Understood, young master!” Jacob answered loudly. He already wanted to prostrate himself when he looked at Leylin’s skills as a commander. Leadership came naturally to the young master, and such a thing was something he had never been able to learn himself.

‘This potential… Does that mean there really is a darling child of the gods in this world?’ Jacob had no time to be bothered by the shock to his worldview, and did all he could to constrain the formation of the troops and surround the camp.

“Isabel, come with me. Let us see to that leader, Steve!” Leylin rapidly moved towards the frontlines of the battle, with Isabel following closely behind.

……

As the infamous leader of the Black Tigers, Steve had the boorish and villainous face unique to pirates. He had long since lost an eye and an ear, the price he paid when his first mate mutinied against him.

Of course, this fellow who dared betrayed him had soon gotten his limbs cut off, and was tossed into the sea. The man could only repent with the sea god.

After being recruited by Marquis Louis, it had been made clear that if he were to be successful in this operation, he would become a knight with land of his own, and he might even become a real lord!

‘I’ll become a lord in the future!’ Every time he thought of this, Steve could not help but gaze at his right hand. He had lost it, among many other things, in ten years of bloody fights and struggles. Still, he felt like the sacrifice was worth it. As he was right now, he was a rank 10 fighter, and the Black Tigers that he led had made a name for themselves in these waters.

‘The target this time is only the manor of a baron that has lost most of its elites. How powerful can they be?’ Steve thought indifferently. If not for him restraining them with all his might, all his underlings would have gone out to have fun long ago.

Up to this point, everything was going well without a hitch. But all of a sudden, yells and shouts could be heard that immediately woke Steve up from his reverie.

“What’s going on?” Steve tossed the bottle of rum in his hand away, and his right hand opened up a huge tear in the tent. He arrived at the camp.

“It’s an enemy invasion! There are too many of them, and they have excellent equipment!” His second mate, a tiger-headed merman, came before him, expression unable to hide his panic.

After noticing the situation, Steve’s face twitched. This crafty captain immediately felt that this was not going well, “Where did they come from? Why did the detection spells and alarm points not react? More importantly, who are they?”

Even now Steve didn’t think these people were sent by his target. With Leylin’s Nondetection spell, the detection magic artifacts he had bought at exorbitant prices lost their effects. The alarm points had all been discovered and removed by Leylin.

Steve grabbed the collar of the second mate and shouted, “Get the men and charge to the ship!”

Chapter 813: Post-battle Review

‘That was close!’ Steve could feel some cold sweat on his palm. Only he knew how dangerous that had been.

Once he regained his senses, he glanced at Leylin. The youth now had a crossbow in his hands, and there was a merciless expression on his face. Isabel had pushed her way to stand beside him, and aside from her Jacob and a few other soldiers had rushed over in a hurry as well.

With Isabel delaying them, Leylin had enough time to defeat the enemy and even seize the pirate ship. Now, Jacob brought the rest of the soldiers and the many crossbows in the Faulen Family’s collection and surrounded the area.

The Faulen soldiers had gained the upper hand in all the other zones, and more and more soldiers gathered together. Under the light of the flames, Steve’s face turned pale as a corpse. He knew very well that after the battle was over, the Black Tigers might just be erased from history.

‘What’s going on? Why did things turn out this way?’ Steve was completely dazed.

However, his fox-like cunning that had been honed over the years told him that this was the time to escape. As long as there were some people left alive, he would be able to pull the Black Tigers back together, and bring about their rise once more. When the time came, he would exact extreme vengeance on this young wizard!

“Shoot!” But how could Leylin give him the chance to do so? With his command, the countless crossbows that Jacob directed on his own produced terrifying sounds. Numerous arrows blocked all the escape routes that Steve had.

“Damn it!” Steve cursed, his figure twisting at a strange angle in midair. A dark shield appeared, crashing into a sharp arrow.

The dark-coloured shield shattered to pieces, but the power of the arrow was greatly reduced. It could only leave a shallow cut on Steve’s body.

*Boom!* Steve’s body fell freely to the ground. He glared at Leylin venomously, and then rushed out of the camp. Once he got outside, he would definitely be able to leave with ease. He was still a rank 10 fighter after all.

At this moment, things suddenly changed! A huge white spiderweb opened up from the ground, shrouding him in darkness.

‘But when did he–?’ Steve’s expression filled with fear as he recognised this web, ‘Rank 2 spell, Web. Once it twines around me, I’ll be caught…’

He looked fierce as he raised the sword in his left hand. However, Leylin had long since set this trap. How could he give Steve the chance to escape?

“Ray of Enfeeblement! Sleep! Restrict!”

A few rank 1 spells flashed over Steve’s head. With the drain from the huge battle just prior, Steve was unable to dodge them in time. Immediately after, he felt a sense of confusion, as his body suddenly weakened.

*Clang!* His machete fell to the ground, and immediately after Steve was caught up in the web. It was extremely sticky, and even a reckless bull would not be able to escape from it.

“Take aim. Prepare to shoot! The opponent is a rank 10 warrior, so be careful!” At this moment, the soldiers holding crossbows aimed at Steve calmly. Only morons would miss an immobile target like this.

“You’re still thinking of running because you have a trump card up your sleeve, don’t you?” Leylin approached the spiderweb, watching Steve from above, eyes full of mockery.

“Don’t think you can hide the Lifesteal effect on your right hand. I’m a wizard!” When Leylin said this, he could see that Steve’s eyes were first filled with fear and despair, followed by a desperate struggle.

Leylin snickered, quickly retreating and dodging the bloody rays shooting from his hand.

“Be careful. The hook on his right hand has the Lifesteal effect. Don’t let it touch you, or your life force will be absorbed…”

Leylin smirked at Steve, causing him to pale even further The terror from being completely seen through caused the pirate to feel muddle-headed. “You’re a devil. A devil!”

“Knock him unconscious,” Leylin’s eyebrows furrowed, “And then get rid of his arms and legs!” Without the assistance of a powerful cleric, such terrifying injuries would end up crippling him.

As for how to deal with this person, Leylin did not have plans yet. As he had been at the forefront in hindering the Faulen Family, he should have made contact with Viscount Tim before, which made him a pretty good witness. But who would believe the words of a pirate? At the most, it would cause some slight trouble for the Viscount.

“His true value is in keeping him from Tim…” Leylin watched the amputated Steve who was now unconscious, his eyes profound. In his view, the pirate only had two functions. One was as bait, attracting more assassins and experts over from the other party so he could ambush them. However, things could easily go wrong that way. If an existence that Leylin could not deal with arrived, that was just shooting himself in the foot.

On the other hand, he could use Steve to negotiate with Tim, forcing the Viscount to back off. After all, the Faulen Family wasn’t the only one with land in the seas. Once his side showed their power and sent Steve back, saying that they had no plans to go to war, he could be able to achieve a period of harmony.

Of course, Leylin never counted on the benevolence and hesitation of his enemies for his own safety. However, giving himself more time was a good method. After all, his strength was still increasing by the day, and on top of that with the complete wipe-out of the probing on the Faulen Family, perhaps they would pause for a bit anyway?

Leylin stroked his chin, “Be quick about it. Bring all the slaves. Kill those who resist.”

““Understood!”” Numerous soldiers yelled together. After seeing that their leader, Steve, had been taken captive, most of the pirates had lost their morale, and with the suppression by Isabel and the crossbowmen they were utterly defeated. Even those futilely thinking of swimming across the sea were killed by the sailors on the ship, not letting any leave. Soon, a whole region of the sea was dyed red.

In this situation, even the fiercest pirate would involuntarily have thoughts of surrender. Soon enough, the sounds of weaponry being tossed to the ground sounded. The soldiers hurried to tie these people up and sent them to the ship.

“Set fire to this place before we leave,” Leylin commanded.

Following that, he returned to the double mast ship he had arrived in. At the moment, the seized pirate ship had been tied up behind theirs. It was the spoils of their battle.

Seeing the sea of red, Leylin listened as Jacob reported, “Nine soldiers are dead, fifteen critically injured. The rest have some form of light injuries…”

This was even though this was a surprise attack and they had the advantage in equipment. Jacob could not help but feel embarrassed at the results. He’d gotten a better understanding of the ferociousness of pirates today. If the Black Tigers had managed to set foot on Faulen Island, the consequences would’ve been dire.

“Mm. What have we captured?” Leylin looked calm, not minding such a tiny issue.

“We have killed 37 pirates and taken 52 prisoner. There are a few with unknown whereabouts. We have taken Steve, and the Black Tigers can be said to be completely wiped out.” At this point, Jacob began to look excited, “It’s a pity that there aren’t any spoils. There’s only some rum and jerky. We haven’t found any letters or anything…”

Leylin shook his head and laughed involuntarily, “Pirates are poor anyway. What more do you want?”

These low-ranked pirates did not have much money on them anyway, and if they were lucky enough to get a large amount, that would quickly be wasted on the bad alcohol in the harbour, barbequed meat and gambling dens. When, on the next day, they had not a single copper in their pockets, they would follow their captain to sea like wolves, roaring as they attacked other ships.

‘Even if you add up the wealth of all the prisoners, that would still be nothing compared to Steve’s own private hoard!’ Leylin chuckled.

‘I really need to interrogate Steve well. Though it’s unlikely that he has a letter from nobility, I need to know about his stash and things like that…’

If he could find evidence of a connection with Viscount Tim, Leylin would not have to be vexed. However, this was impossible.The other side would not be so foolish as to leave letters and the like behind. Hence, Leylin could only give this a try without placing too much hope in it.

As for money… that was just a consolation prize. At the very least, these soldiers would need to be rewarded amply for the deaths, else nobody would be willing to work under him.

Having taken care of everything, Leylin walked to the hold of the ship. As there were many more captives to return with, the concealed hold was very squeezy and somewhat chaotic. Leylin naturally would not imprison the group on the pirate ship behind them, that would only be creating trouble for himself.

Even in this situation, Isabel had a room of her own. This was a privilege reserved for the nobility and the strong.

“Can I come in?” Leylin asked after walking up to her door.

“Please!”

Opening the door, Leylin entered the room and cast a silencing spell. This immediately resulted in a serious look on Isabel’s face.

Leylin twitched his nose. There was a herbal smell in the air, and Isabel’s clothing was slightly in disarray. Evidently, in her hurry, she had not had everything arranged properly.

Chapter 816: Trade

Leylin’s solemn tone immediately had Jonas on his guard. He glanced towards Ernest, and the man immediately flicked his fingers. He’d cast Nondetection and Sound Isolation.

With all the preparation done, Leylin spoke quietly, “I’ve already become a rank 7 wizard…”

“What? …. Wha– what?” Ernest’s eyes grew as round as saucers. He’d been completely thrown off his lack of reaction.

“Hasn’t it been less than a year since you broke through to rank 6?” Ernest’s expression was comical, as if he wanted to both cry and burst out in laughter.

“Oh Goddess, do you speak the truth?” Ernest’s face was on the verge of pressing into Leylin’s nose.

“In the name of the Goddess of the Weave, Mystra, I swear that all I say is true!” Leylin looked serious as he swore on the name of the goddess that numerous wizards held faith in.

The price of offending the Goddess of the Weave was that one could possibly be permanently restricted from using the Weave, rendering them a piece of trash. Leylin’s pledge was very serious, and Ernest believed him immediately.

“Heavens, what are you? A bastard son of Mystra?” This rate of advancement immediately depressed Ernest. He was still a mid-rank 9 wizard, so by the looks of it Leylin would probably catch up to him in a year or two.

It was normal to be overtaken by one’s student, but to be surpassed by a punk who wasn’t even twenty yet? Ernest grew very dispirited, almost on the verge of hiding away into a corner and drawing circles on the ground.

Meanwhile, Baron Jonas turned awkward, not getting it at all. He truly knew little about wizards, so he immediately suppressed his awkwardness to ask, “Ernest, my friend, what does this mean? Why the reaction?”

“Oh, my apologies, my friend!” Ernest flushed, and then replaced that with more fervour, “Leylin is a fifteen year old rank 7 wizard! From what I know this talent puts him among the top hundred talents of the past 300 years!”

At this point, he turned serious, “Don’t underestimate this ranking. Many of them became great wizards in the future, with some even becoming Legends…”

“…Cough cough… So…” This instantly shocked Baron Jonas. He watched his son, eyes full of disbelief.

“While I don’t have any acknowledgment from the wizard guild, it’s no problem to cast rank 3 spells…” Leylin looked towards his mentor, “If news of this gets out during negotiations, do you think Marquis Louis will back off?”

The great chances of Leylin becoming a great wizard was enough to inspire fear. After all, few high-ranked wizards in the Dambrath Kingdom obeyed the royal family. If they found out that the Faulen Family had a genius wizard, the possibility of the other side conceading was high.

Of course, the other possibility was that they would be driven into a corner, sparing no expense to eliminate Leylin so as to avoid any repercussions. This way, they would not be harmed.Of course, they might be driven to a corner and spared no expense to kill Leylin in order to take care of whatever repercussions there might be. This way, they would not be at harm.

“Well, that’s very possible, but there are also other options. After all, growth and talent don’t represent power…” Ernest warned.

“No, no! This news absolutely cannot get out. I will send down an order for everyone to keep their lips sealed!” Baron Jonas immediately understood. Even if there was a mere 0.0001% possibility, he was unwilling to risk Leylin dying.

After all, with Leylin’s talent, it would only be a matter of time before he became a high-ranked wizard if nurtured well. He even had hope to become a Legend! Compared to that, the losses now meant nothing.

Seeing his father and master so resolute, Leylin could only laugh wryly and toss this thought away.

“Alright! However, Father, please allow me to train my magic in secret outside the manor in the future…”

“Training in secret…” Ernest could not understand it. Wizards weren’t the kind to practice hard like that; was there a need to abandon a life of luxury in order to train one’s will?

But watching this student of his, a 15 year old who had become a rank 7, Ernest wisely chose to shut his mouth. Leylin’s achievements would represent everything. Who knew, this method could allow him to make rapid progress.

Ernest touched his chin, feeling that he might should probably start training like this.

“Since your mentor isn’t against it, I have no opinions. Remember that you’re the future of our family, always prioritise your safety! Even if I were to lose the Faulen Island, I can’t lose you. Do you understand?” Baron Jonas warned.

“Yes!” Leylin nodded then followed up, “There’s something else, and it regards the management of the family.”

“Oh! Seems like you’re giving me a lot of surprises today!” Baron Jonas was actually extremely fatigued now, but he still rubbed at the area between his eyebrows, looking like he was listening closely.

“I think we should alter our system of giving rewards based on the services rendered at our family port.”

Leylin’s first words were already astonishing, “I noticed that this occurred because we’re too weak to protect our own territory. It’s likely that we’ll have a lot of enemies coveting our land. We need to recruit even more soldiers and Professionals to expand out power, which means we need more sources of revenue.”

“That’s easy to say, but most of the trade on these seas is taken up by Marquis Louis’ Baltic archipelago. What can we offer?” Baron Jonas smiled wryly. No noble would reject opportunities to expand their strength and wealth. He’d also explored this before, but had not gotten any gains.

“Leylin must’ve mentioned this because he has a proposal. Let’s consider it first.” Ernest was aware that this student of his always made plans before acting, and would never say anything without thinking it through beforehand. This aroused his interest.

“I’ve checked, and there are only three things that make great profits with a foundation in sea trade: slaves, sea salt and sugar,” Leylin’s eyes glinted, “The slave trade has a bad reputation and it’s been controlled by Marquis Louis. We can’t interfere with that, so I’d choose sea salt and sugar!”

“Sea salt and… sugar?” Baron Jonas scratched his hair in confusion, “But our island isn’t anything like those in the south with spices and cane sugar. Those plants can’t survive here…”

“No! I plan to buy coarse sugar, and then refine it into high-grade white sugar for sale. As for the sea salt, I’m planning to use fish floss!”

“Fish floss?!”

“Yes! Mash the flesh of the fish and dry it in the sun, and then use techniques to preserve it for a long time. Because there’s salt and meat, I’m sure it will be welcomed by the commoners and adventurers on the continent!”

Leylin was someone who’d travelled over from another world. He’d be foolish if he didn’t use the knowledge he gained from his previous world to gain some benefits.

Though there were differences in the physical laws of the two worlds, there were still some similarities. Concerned about the family’s strength, Leylin was trying to expand their revenue to help himself in the future. He’d long since thought this through.

While he only somewhat remembered the methods to refine sugar and create fish floss by drying them in the sun, that was alright. He was a noble! As long as he supplied them with a general idea, his underlings would make it a reality.

Though Leylin remembered a lot more as well, he’d run tests through the years and he realised that he could only build an industry around these two items, they complemented the laws of the World of Gods.

As for other techniques, it wasn’t that they could not be used, but they would destabilize the situation now. Paper would definitely be valued highly by the church of knowledge, so he could easily gain the favour of Oghma. However, he would attract the ire of the other gods, and Leylin was afraid of that.

Refined sugar and fish floss were two things that wouldn’t have as great an effect.

After Leylin explained his thoughts on this industry, Baron Jonas sank into deep thought. While he did not know about this, Leylin’s words seemed to be plausible. At the very least, Ernest beside him had eyes that were twinkling as if he had seen sudden huge profits.

“In that case, you can try that!” At the end, Baron Jonas agreed. After all, Leylin had proven with his battle achievements that he was not just a braggart. What was the harm of letting him try? At worst, it could be considered business training.

As a successor of a noble family, one might not need to know how to manage businesses, but they couldn’t afford to be cheated by businessmen.

“However, be cautious!” Jonas warned after thinking it over once more. He was still worried.

“I understand. Many thanks, Father!” Leylin stood and bowed.

In reality, he just needed to have the approval of the Baron in name. As for the people and money? Steve would probably be more than ‘willing’ to provide that.

“The banquet’s almost prepared, let’s go together. By the way, where’s your cousin Isabel?” Jonas asked suddenly at the end.

“Oh… I let her leave…” Leylin’s eyes flashed with his unhesitating answer. He still didn’t want to divulge the fact that he was establishing a pirate crew.

“Is she gone? That’s good too!” Baron Jonas nodded and did not ask more, leaving with his hands behind his back.

It was evident that he’d long since had his own conjectures on Isabel’s change. However, the situation had been urgent then, and he’d felt bad about abandoning a diligent branch member of the Faulen Family. That was why he’d said nothing then, and now that she’d left, there would now be no awkwardness between them.

Chapter 820: Smash

Wizards were often more intimidatingly powerful than high-ranking fighters, knights and other such Professionals.

“I’ll count to three, and if you don’t put down your arms and kneel in surrender, you’ll follow his example!” With a tug of the rope, the charred remains were immediately scattered into the ocean. This intimidating strength immediately made many pirates think of retreating.

It was a pity that this was the ocean, and they were surrounded by water as far as the eye could see. Even if they wanted to run, they had nowhere to go.

“One.” Leylin’s face twitched as he announced without any hesitation.

“Two.” Two rays of ice flew out, turning the fleeing pirates into ice sculptures.

“Three!” Leylin’s eyes were filled with a heavy killing intent.

These terrifying eyes finally led to the collapse of the pirates. They abandoned their weapons one by one, and knelt on the floor while weeping bitterly.

“Robin Hood, tie them all up!” Leylin rubbed his hands together. After all, he could not possibly kill all of these captive pirates. If he did, who would sail the ship?

In this world, a captain could only fight to the death in the face of mass mutiny. However, powerful people like him could put down their entire crew with a hand tied behind their back.

“As you command, Captain!” Although this was not the first time they had seen the young master’s power, the soldiers’ eyes were still filled with respect.

Given that those pirates didn’t dare to rebel, the soldiers on the deck could easily control them. Even if there were troubles on the ship, Isabel would resolve them before Leylin could even grow impatient.

Isabel would’ve taken care of the situation this time even if Leylin hadn’t. It was just that the situation would have ended up with many pointless deaths.

In the end, all of the captives who had taken part in the rebellion had been tied together and gathered on the deck. The soldiers and the rescued pirates who had not taken part in the rebellion erected several enormous wooden crucifixes there.

Leylin peacefully stood in front of the pirates, but he did not say a single world. However, this made the pirates begin to tremble in fear. Leylin was determined to go through with this purge, and did not have any intention of letting them off.

“Find me the leader of the rebellion!” With Leylin’s command, as well as the pirates identifying each other themselves, several wild and untameable ones were pushed out from the crowd.

“There’s only four or five? This is far too few!” Leylin shook his head, “Robin Hood, pick one out of every five to kill!”

Soon after, the remaining pirates huddled together in alarm. Robin Hood counted here and there, and every fifth pirate was immediately dragged out by the soldiers. This repeated until 5 poor devils had been chosen.

This was a method from Leylin’s previous life, called decimation. It was a way of investigation, used similarly to what he had employed to execute criminals.

“This is your sentence.” Leylin waved his hand, and his subordinates quickly swarmed around the criminals, binding them on top of the crucifixes.

*Thud! Thud! Thud!* The other pirates were alarmed by the sounds as several nails were hammered into the offenders, even if they avoided the vitals. Drops of blood ran down the nails.

“Bastard! I won’t let you off!” “Even if I die, I’ll drag you to hell with me!” “My lord, please spare us! Please spare us!”

Blood-curdling screams rang out, intermixed with curses and pleas.

“Aren’t you lively? I hope you can be like that tomorrow too!” Leylin smiled faintly.

This method of crucifixion was very inhumane. The targets inched closer and closer to death as they gradually bled out. The sort of fear it induced could lead to a nervous breakdown in normal people.

These physically strong people could perhaps stay alive until the second day. However, that was of no use; it only meant more insane pain and torment.

The violent sunlight of the sea would drain them of every drop of moisture in their body, until they were mummified. And in the end, they could only chose between bleeding to death, dying from sunburn, or dying of thirst.

Many of the captives who thought of this scene were so frightened that they couldn’t help but wet themselves. They didn’t even dare to meet Leylin’s eyes; the smell of urine spread.

“As for the rest of you, I’ll be gracious and show you mercy. You will only receive ten lashes. Now all of you, clean the decks immediately! If I see even a single speck of dust tomorrow, you’ll have to lick it clean! Do you all understand?” Leylin shouted.

When grace was absent, the fear of death was an effective deterrent. Of course, the prerequisite was that one needed enough power. Still, who amongst Leylin’s subordinates could surpass him in strength?

*Thwack! Thwack! Thwack!* Leather whips specially soaked in seawater were used to punish these pirates. On one hand, the salt in the water would prevent the wounds festering, but on the other hand, the pain would be even more severe.

These lucky pirates did not dare to grumble, and they began to clean up the deck even more quickly. Those who were currently crucified were deeply reminded of their betrayal.

‘Fear me, respect me, hate me!’ Leylin stood at the ship’s bow like a tall mountain, filled with a deep and immeasurable strength.

‘The hate and resentment of an ordinary person seem to result in some additional spiritual force and soul force emanating from them.’ Leylin shut his eyes, sensing the respect from the pirates on the ship.

‘What a pity… If this number was multiplied by a thousand times, and continued for over 10 years, it would be possible for me to comprehend divinity, and become a divine being.’ The power of fear was a standard tool for demons and devils. It was very effective, a god only needed to absorb the energy of faith arising from mortal fear. His subordinates’ shifting moods had allowed Leylin to touch on a path to divinity.

‘Pity. This method is completely undesirable, not to mention what the churches would do once they discover me trying to spread fear to become a god. Perhaps their first course of action would be to come and destroy me…’ It was very foolish to peep into the realm of gods without even becoming a Legend.

“Cousin, aren’t you going to rest?” Isabel arrived at Leylin’s side at this moment. She was the only one who would dare to do so.

At the same time, Leylin noticed that Isabel was looking at these condemned convicts with eyes filled with regret. Naturally, she wasn’t regretting their deaths, but she felt it was a great pity to lose so many sacrificial offerings.

“My dear cousin!” Leylin began as he watched Isabel, “You shouldn’t just act according to the other party’s wishes when dealing with an abnormal life form. Sometimes you need to negotiate, and even refuse… Perhaps this can help you.”

Leylin took out a black notebook and passed it over to her.

“Rules of Negotiation with Abnormal Entities- Demon Edition!” Isabel let out a low cry. This book contained knowledge about demons, and to the churches it was a standard demonic item.

“This is part of my teacher’s collection, I copied it out using magic. Perhaps it can help you, don’t let anyone else see it,” Leylin smiled faintly. In fact, this was from Beelzebub’s memories. After all, he was the commander of the devils’ army, and he had a deep understanding of those demons that were his enemies.

At the same time, devils were also the greatest experts in deceit, threats, and modifying contracts. With Beelzebub’s knowledge, the least it could do was to ensure that she wouldn’t suffer too big a loss when making deals in hell or the abyss.

“Even if you sell your soul, make sure it fetches a good price. Don’t be swayed by a few words and offer it up without thinking it through. That would simply be too foolish…”

“T-Thank you!” Isabel hugged the black notebook close, as if it was her entire world.

“Also, it seems like we won’t get any rest tonight…” Leylin waved his hand and said to Isabel, “Be careful!”

“What should I be careful of… AH!” Isabel was rather doubtful, but she immediately felt a huge jolt. As she was still firmly holding onto the notebook with both hands, she almost fell to the deck.

At this moment, a pair of powerful hands held her up steadily.

“If you feel that the storm is too much, go back to your room and leave this place to me,” Leylin’s words were filled with self-confidence, and it seemed to give her a great sense of security. Isabel agreed in a rather foolish manner, and really walked back to her cabin.

Yet after a short moment, she’d changed into her leather armour and grabbed her longsword, rushing back out.

“I’ve put away the thing you gave me!” Isabel’s face was flushed as she flusteredly explained.

At this moment, Robin Hood’s voice rang out, sounding completely exasperated, “Tigershark! It’s a Mutant Tigershark!”

The expressions of the people on the ship immediately changed greatly. The Mutant Tigershark was a type of deep sea monster. It possessed an enormous body larger than ordinary whales, and it had a savage nature. It particularly enjoyed hunting at night.

This Tigershark’s body could easily flip over the Black Tiger. Such a thing was exactly why these pirates were so afraid of sailing at night.

“What are you panicking for? Calm down now!” Leylin’s voice spread immediately, charged with a pacifying force. In just a moment all of the alarmed pirates calmed down.

The ship’s hull was tilted to an alarming degree, and it was tipping further. It was like a powerful monster was shaking the bottom of the ocean. At this moment, everyone on the ship could only pin their hopes on Leylin, the wizard.

Isabel stood the closest to Leylin, and she discovered that he had a strangely excited expression on his face.

“Finally! I’ve been waiting for this. This opponent is mine, don’t interfere!” Without even waiting for her to respond, Leylin immediately jumped off the deck of the ship.

Chapter 821: Level 1 Magic Weave

The bitterly cold seawater seemed to chill one to the bone as the mountainous black figure suddenly appeared in front of Leylin.

As the A.I. Chip finished scanning, the Tigershark’s stats appeared in front of him.

[Mutant Tigershark, Estimated Stats: Strength: 7+, Agility: 2-4, Vitality: 13+, Spirit: 3. Abilities: 1. Sharkskin: A Tigershark’s skin has a slight resistance to physical and magical attacks. 2. Lesser Regeneration: Slight ability to restore a certain amount of life force.]

“Not bad, not bad. With this physique and abundant energy, it’s worthy of being called a deep sea creature…” Leylin’s eyes seemed to glow a crimson red.

Aquatic Swiftness! A glowing enchantment draped itself over Leylin’s body, and he obtained greater speed in the water. It made him as nimble in the water as he was on land.

An enormous sound wave spread out, causing massive vibrations. The forcefield around Leylin’s Mage Armour creaked, as if unable to bear the attack.

The Tigershark seemed to care very little for the insignificantly tiny Leylin, and it occasionally used its giant dorsal fin to smash against the Black Tiger. It looked like it wanted to flip the ship over.

In this situation, Leylin immediately arrived at the back of the Tigershark, and climbed up the coarse surface of the shark’s skin.

“According to the perspective drawing on the map, it should be here!”

Numerous shadowy daggers suddenly appeared from Leylin’s hand as he shouted, “Cloud of Daggers! Ice Knife!”

*Shlook!* The ice daggers plunged into the Mutant Tigershark’s back, making it suddenly swing its entire body around. Copious amounts of fresh blood poured out from its wounds. Its sharkskin seemed like paper under Leylin’s attack.

*Bang! Bang! Bang!* At this moment, the Mutant Tigershark’s body seemed to become a burden to it. As it was so enormous, it could only violently shake its body and hope that this would throw Leylin far away. It was to the point where the Tigershark once slammed the part of its body where Leylin was against the ship. It seemed to want to crush Leylin to death.

However, long before that enormous collision could occur, a glowing dagger that was the colour of blood appeared in Leylin’s hand, the Devilblood Dagger.

“Its artery is here!” Leylin’s eyes seemed to glow, and he stabbed down.

The Mutant Tigershark bellowed with rage, and its movements momentarily stilled. Afterwards, it began to sway and twitch even more violently than before, which made Leylin feel like he was riding a rollercoaster.

Leylin used Adhesion, and was finally able to stick firmly to the Tigershark’s body like a lizard. He felt a strong heat flowing from his palm, the dagger in it like a greedy devil that was relentlessly absorbing the Tigershark’s life force.

Accompanying the absorption of life force by the Devilblood Dagger, the Mutant Tigershark’s back began to atrophy first, exposing dried-up and eroded flesh. Following this, the corrosion began to spread. The Tigershark’s death throes were extremely violent. It gave up on the Black Tiger, and began to travel at a great speed into the sea, swimming deeper without stopping.

However, Leylin remained unmoved by the situation. The Tigershark had such a powerful body that the boost he gained from it was very considerable. He listened to the A.I. Chip’s constant prompts and saw his own slowly increasing stats, clearly feeling the surging life force of the creature constantly being drained. The Devilblood Dagger converted its life force into another form of energy, and transferred it into his body.

Finally, the Mutant Tigershark had one last spurt of movement before it stilled. Its malevolent eyes lost their lustre, and it slowly fell towards the seabed like a sunken ship, dead.

It did not end just like that. The Tigershark’s originally glistening skin had completely dried up, now looking like ancient tree bark even as it had shrunk to half its former size. If it was dissected, then it would be possible to see that the Tigershark’s internal organs had also lost all their life force and had become a pile of waste.

[Beep! Host has killed the Mutant Tigershark, and received a boost from the Devilblood Dagger. Strength has increased by 0.1, vitality increased by 0.3, spiritual force increased by 0.009.]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip sent over its final summary, and Leylin noticed his updated stats.

[Leylin Faulen. Race: Human, Rank 7 Wizard. Strength: 2.6, Agility: 2, Vitality: 4, Spirit: 7. Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite. Spell Slots: Rank 3(1), Rank 2(3), Rank 1(4), Rank 0(???)]

‘This Tigershark seems to be much stronger than the assassin from before. However it only raised my stats a little, and the most it did was to raise my vitality by 0.3. My spiritual force doesn’t seem to have changed…’ Leylin’s expression was a little gloomy.

As his stats increased, and every stat broke through 10, the Devilblood Dagger would grow less useful. He would eventually grow completely immune to its effects.

‘However, the open sea is full of resources. Many drops of water make up an ocean, so it should be enough to let me advance to become a rank 9 or even rank 10 wizard…’ Leylin’s expression clouded over.

This was one of his plans. The Devilblood Dagger’s flesh devouring ability meant that outside of high-level Professionals, the only place that had enough flesh to feed it was the open sea. The bodies of deep sea creatures were terrifyingly massive, and organisms full of life force could be found everywhere.

Naturally, these monsters all had their own intelligence and faith, so slaughtering them as one pleased would damage one’s reputation and could even attract an intervention from the gods of other races. It could even draw the attention of druids, who were all lunatics and naturally hostile towards those who destroyed nature.

Now however, the blood on the Black Tiger had attracted the spontaneous attack of many monsters so it wasn’t possible to give them preferential treatment.

One could imagine that in the near future, more than one sea monster would be attracted by Leylin, and all of them would become an unending stream of life force, pushing forward his advancement.

Leylin’s body split open the surface of the sea with a loud splash, and he landed on the deck.

“Cousin Leylin! Are you alright?” Isabel looked at him worry in her eyes.

“I’m alright, continue sailing!” Leylin waved his hand, and all the sailors who heard his command suddenly became sluggish.

He was alright, but it was clear that the terrifyingly powerful monster from earlier was still howling unstoppably on the seabed. They could guess at the powerful battle that occurred after Leylin jumped into the sea, while standing on the deck.

It appeared like their captain could kill even a Mutant Tigershark!

Very quickly, even the most frightening pirates looked at Leylin with eyes filled with respect. They only admired the strong, and now that Leylin had revealed his savage nature, he had also exposed his own powerful abilities.

This carrot-and-stick method was enough to subdue these old pirates. The subconscious actions of theirs made Leylin smile at the scene that would occur many, many more times in the future.

After the battle of Half-Merfolk Island, he would possibly possess an army of pirates that only listened to him.

……

Under the sunny and cloudless sky, Robin Hood’s eyes were filled with unconcealed respect as he reported from behind Leylin. “Captain, we will arrive at Half-Merfolk Island in half an hourglass’ time!”

“I know, pass on the order. Prepare for battle!” Leylin looked out towards the distance, and seemed to be rather distracted. Yet Robin Hood did not notice that, and immediately began to carry out his order.

In reality, Leylin was experiencing an enormous change at this very moment. Ever since he had fought that Mutant Tigershark, he had also attacked various other sea monsters. Under Leylin’s Devilblood Dagger, they all became gifts of experience which helped his stats steadily rise.

The most important thing was that after the boost from this power, the A.I. Chip’s rate of analysing the Weave had increased greatly. Many rank 0 and 1 symbols glowed in front of Leylin, as if forming the mystery of the universe in their array.

Only when he heard a sharp and clear ring did Leylin snap out of his trance-like state. The A.I. Chip displayed its newest progress in front of him.

[Beep! Rank 1 Weave has been fully analysed! Progress is 100%]

[Weave Analysis Progress: Rank 0 Weave: 100%. Rank 1 Weave: 100%. Rank 2 Weave: 13.61%. Rank 3 Weave: 0.45%]

The higher the rank of the Weave, the harder it was to analyse it. This was especially true of the rank 3 Weave, the analysis of which hadn’t even reached 1% yet. However, Leylin was already very satisfied.

[Beep! Rank 1 Weave has been fully analysed. The host now has all rank 1 magic models, and spells will not be deleted. Host is exempt from forgetting magic!]

The A.I. Chip’s prompts came incessantly.

Leylin now felt that a layer of the Weave had been uncovered, and many rank 1 spell models, from the most basic Alarm to the Endure Element spells and even frightening spells like the Necromancer’s Ray of Enfeeblement were displayed before him.

After the breakthrough of the rank 1 Weave, not only did was he exempt from all the limitations of rank 1 spell models, he could directly use spiritual force to perform magic. It even gave him a lot of authority within the Weave.

It could be said that the benefits brought about by the advancement were of greater help to him than advancing to a higher rank as a wizard, especially when he was on the verge of attacking Half-Merfolk Island.

Leylin couldn’t help but glance over his stats:

[Leylin Faulen, Race: Human, Rank 7 Wizard, Strength: 3.5, Agility: 3, Vitality: 4.5, Spirit: 7.9, Status: Healthy. Innate skills: Sturdy, Erudite. Spell slots: Rank 3 (1), rank 2 (3), rank 1 (???), rank 0 (???)]

Day after day of sailing, as well as constantly attracting sea monsters, had made enormous contributions to his strength.

Chapter 823: Bloodsucker

‘I don’t really want the other two ships, but this main battleship is rather good!’ Leylin purposefully lifted the effects of the Flight spell, and landed on the Merfolk Pirates’ deck.

“What? This foolish wizard dared come here by himself?” The captain of the Merfolk Pirates was overjoyed, “Get up there! Kill him!”

Two odd-looking pirates, with the heads of a crab and a squid, swarmed around Leylin and surrounded him completely. Their eyes were filled with ferocity.

*Puff! Puff!* The air seemed to twist, and two sharp daggers which looked just like a pair of poisonous snakes appeared and bared their sharp teeth at Leylin.

“Mm! This Sneak of Shadows is comparable to Mankeh’s…” Leylin had a ferocious smile on his face, “What a shame that you squids alone aren’t enough!”

In a flash of blood-red light, the Devilblood Dagger appeared in Leylin’s hand. As he held the dagger, he seemed to transform into the image of a night elf, his every act and every move seeming to be filled with a unique beauty.

“Shadow Dance!” With the A.I Chip’s support, Leylin used a skill that could normally only be used by high-ranking rogues and assassins. The blood-red light turned into a whirlwind, immediately dragging the two assassins into itself.

The dagger’s lifesteal greatly surpassed that of a vampire. Once stabbed by it, the two assassins were instantly turned into corpses, falling to the floor.

*Bang! Bang!* Metal weapons clashed against each other loudly, and the mermen closest to Leylin fell to the ground. As traces of their blood-red energy was absorbed by Leylin’s dagger, they completely lost all of their life force, to the point where their corpses would scatter into dust at the lightest touch.

“He’s a devil! A demon from the abyss!” This horrifying scene scared all of the ferocious pirates so much that they wet themselves. All intelligent creatures feared the unknown. Although they could usually kill without even batting an eye, they had apparently never seen this sort of tragic manner of death before.

“As expected, personally harvesting lives myself is the most enjoyable experience…” Leylin’s lips quirked up into a rather evil smile, “Bull’s Strength! Cat’s Grace!”

Two rays of magic light flickered, and after receiving the boost of strength and agility, Leylin seemed to become death incarnate, reaping the lives of all the pirates around him. While he was killing, countless rank 0 and rank 1 spells shot out from Leylin’s hands without stopping.

The Devilblood Dagger was not some ordinary metal weapon. Of course, it did not have any effect on a wizard’s spellcasting, but without the Weave impeding him, Leylin’s movement was even quicker and smoother.

“As expected! On of a shipful of pirates, all of them have close-ranged professions, and there’s not a single Conjurer…” Leylin was like a tiger amongst a flock of sheep. His eyes swept across the entire ship, as if he was hunting for prey.

If anyone of the Conjurer profession came out to fight, even if they only had the Web or Grease spells they would become rather troublesome.

However it was a pity. The Merfolk Pirates were secretly controlled by Marquis Louis, and he wouldn’t put a Sorcerer or other high-ranked Professional with a bunch of pirates. Perhaps only the three largest pirate groups would have a Sorcerer in their midst.

“Did you see that? Our boss has already destroyed two of their ships, and there’s only one left. Get up there and kill them all!” Robin Hood lay on top of a railing, and after seeing Leylin’s success in battle, he roared loudly from the back.

At this moment, the pirate prisoners also let out a wolf-like howl, “Kill them! Kill them!”

The pirates who previously completely lacked morale now exploded forth with 200% of their fighting spirit and hot-bloodedness, loudly roaring at the Merfolk Pirates as they clashed in battle.

The battle between the ships would erupt at any moment, when they came side to side.

“We can’t continue like this! Fuck, where are these pirates from? They’re so strong and they even have a wizard supporting them, and they’re still coming here to cause me trouble?” The Merfolk Pirate captain looked as the sight of his underlings being killed one by one, and the Black Tiger pirate ship advancing quickly ahead. His expression grew even uglier.

Yet at this moment, the wizard was clearly advancing with thoughts of destroying the captain, and whatever ideas or hopes he had were all for naught. This captain understood very well that even if he chose to surrender, perhaps the normal pirates would end up alright, but he and his confidantes would absolutely be forced to walk the plank.

At this thought, his eyes gleamed ruthlessly. He tore off the cloak on his body, revealing stainless steel armour beneath.

“Make way! Archers, prepare!” As he was forced to an impasse, the captain prepared to personally enter the fray. After all, as the captain of the crew he was very strong.

“Battle skill— Charge!” The pirate captain was completely wrapped up in a dense layer of qi. He charged forwards like a battle tank.

“He should be a rank 10 warrior, and his armour and ring…” Leylin quickly retreated, his gleaming eyes making the pirate captain shiver.

At this moment, the A.I. Chip had already collected the captain’s stats and displayed them to Leylin. [Name Unknown, Sex: Male, Estimated stats, Strength: 11+, Agility: 5, Vitality: 8, Spirit: 3, Predicted Fighter Rank: 11. Evaluation: Dangerous! Armour and ring are radiating magic, deduced to be magic items!]

After his Charge skill, the pirate captain swung from his waist, and the broadsword in his hand began to rotate like a windmill. “Ha! Battle skill— Whirling Slash!”

*Bang! Bang! Crack!* The sword flew like the wind everywhere he went, slashing most of the deck open. Wooden splinters flew everywhere.

This battle skill was something the captain was very proud of, and something he had learnt very recently. He had to work hard under a Professional fighter’s guidance for three years before he had managed to gain their recognition and tutorship.

However, this was all worth it. After learning this skill, he had used its terrifying revolving strength to kill several warriors of a higher rank than him, and finally gained the treasured position of the captain of the Merfolk Pirates.

Needless to say, his opponent was only a wizard, and even if he had the abilities of a rogue, he could not beat a warrior of similar rank to him.

The pirate captain’s mouth split open into a wide grin. If the wizard was caught by Whirling Slash, then he could almost see his body being torn apart.

“You have a rather good battle skill there, it’s a pity that you’re too slow…”

*Puff!* The sound of a heavy hammer hitting leather rang out, and a layer of protection suddenly burst from the captain’s armour, offsetting the dagger’s attack trajectory. Even so, the tip of the blood-red dagger left a very deep mark on his chest.

Seeing that his armour had almost been cut through, the pirate captain’s face was filled with triumph at his luck.

‘What a pity! If I hadn’t used a rank 3 spell slot to memorise Flight, then one Dispel Magic could have broken through his defense just now and killed him.’ Leylin’s figure hadn’t stopped at all, and he charged once again through the group of pirates. Several severed heads were sent flying into the air, and fountains of blood gushed out.

Before it had the chance to touch the ground, the blood was absorbed by the dagger in Leylin’s hand. All the small cuts to his body healed immediately, as if they had never been inflicted in the first place.

“This ability… You’re a vampire!” The pirate captain seemed to recall a rather unpleasant memory, which made him cry out in alarm. This ability to absorb life force and and his quick regenerative ability, was very similar to that of the rumoured vampires.

*Bang!* A huge impact spread across the deck like a grade 8 earthquake.

Just when Leylin had single-handedly contained all the pirates, the Black Tiger smashed against the side of the ship. Many small boats hooked onto it, and pirates climbed the cables aboard. A great number of them waved their glowing blue weapons as they came on deck.

These weapons which had been soaked in Leylin’s poison did a great deal of damage to the Merfolk Pirates. Even the tiniest cut would paralyze them and drop them to the ground, to then be killed by their enemies.

The magic weapons that Leylin had enchanted, used by the guards, were even more formidable. Isabel took the lead like a Valkyrie, and many Merfolk Pirates were killed so quickly that they died in confusion.

“What? Thinking of escaping?” Leylin’s face was wreathed in smiles as he looked at the ugly expression on the pirate captain’s face.

“Ha! Battle skill— Blast Slash!” It was clear that this pirate captain knew that unless he could thoroughly shake Leylin off his trail, he didn’t have a single hope of escaping. After his expression changed, he charged forwards immediately, his broadsword shining like a blade of light.

Just as the captain was charging towards Leylin, the ring on his right hand suddenly emitted a beautiful burst of magical light.

“Swift Explosion!” The sudden blessing from the spell increased the captain’s attack speed fivefold. If his enemy did not notice this, they were sure to regret it.

However, Leylin had long anticipated this. He only smiled at the pirate captain, and gave him a signal, “Grease!”

*Clang!* The deck immediately became impossibly slippery, and the expression of the charging captain changed. He completely lost his balance.

“I already know about all your trump cards. Under these circumstances, you only have one fate, and that is to peacefully walk the path of death…” Leylin seemed as graceful as a dancer as he began to step out, his elegant figure flying over to the Merfolk Pirate.

A severed head flew high up into the air, and soon after blood rushed out from his neck.

The Devilblood Dagger let out an icy-cold laughter after it had feasted on the fresh blood, and its wings seemed to become even more true to life, as if the demon sealed within it had recovered.

Chapter 826: Pirates’ Cove

The only thing Leylin could do now was hide somewhere secret, where his enemies could never find him. Only a fool would jump about shouting when he was weak.

“Isabel, Robin Hood!” he suddenly called out.

“You were looking for me, boss?” Robin Hood respectfully arrived in front of Leylin. After the battle, this first mate seemed to have changed dramatically.

Leylin stretched his hand out on the map of the ocean. “Mm, the two of you take the merfolk ship and bring the slaves to the pirates’ families.”

Be it Faulen Island or Marquis Louis’ fiefdom, the Baltic archipelago, they were all new discoveries in the waters surrounding the Dambrath Kingdom, and that was also the only characteristic they shared. New, uninhabited islands seemed to emerge endlessly one after the other, full of both wealth and dangers. It was simply too easy to find a temporary base for his crew.

Of course, the condition was that Leylin could deal with the dangerous beasts in those territories, and they could brave the harsh weather and environment.

Taking into consideration that Robin Hood had the other sailors’ loyalty, Leylin intentionally sent his cousin Isabel over as well. With her there, even if he couldn’t control the entire ship, he could presumably intimidate the disloyal ones without much problem.

As a matter of fact, Leylin had plans to nurture this cousin of his. After all, he couldn’t remain here commanding the pirates forever, so Isabel would serve as his stand-in. Although Robin Hood was more suited to this role, he was too feral. Leylin could not give this fellow too much space to make decisions so early on in his venture. It wasn’t because he was scared that Robin would betray him, but it was just that Robin didn’t have the instincts of a superior.

On the other hand, Isabel did not possess much authoritative power, but what she did have was enough to cow these pirates into submission.

Watching the merfolk ship leave, Leylin waved his hand. “Set off, we’re going to Pirates’ Cove!”

Pirates’ Cove was a port that provided services for pirates. It could be called the gathering part for the shady figures of the seas.

The port sold intelligence, goods, and even top-grade elven slaves. Of course, one needed to have the courage to take the risk and buy something; as a port where pirates disposed of stolen goods, the things they sold were definitely unclean in origin. Even Marquis Louis, who controlled the Baltic archipelago, did not allow too many stolen treasures pass through his territory, regretfully giving up on the profits that came to Pirates’ Cove.

As for the port’s location, many of the old pirates under Leylin knew of it. The route wouldn’t be a problem at all, but there were several dangerous areas they had to pass through.

“Are you sure the route won’t have any problems, Cyclops?” Leylin opened up the map of the ocean as he called over a one-eyed pirate. The sailor had a courage bred from years of killing, and although he had only one eye its gleam caused others to tremble with fear.

It was only at this moment that a flower-like smile bloomed on Cyclops’ stubbled face. He revealed his few yellowing teeth, “Don’t worry, Boss. I’ve sailed to Pirates’ Cove with Steve a few times, and at that time I was even the navigator’s assistant. I can get there with my eyes closed!”

“Very well, you’re now the ship’s navigator. If you do well, you’ll be the Scarlet Tiger’s first mate once we reach the port.” This was the promise Leylin made to this pirate in whom he had just placed his trust.

“Yes, boss!” A first mate would receive a greater share of the booty than the other pirates, and would also have authority over the others. Cyclops’ remaining eye gleamed with excitement.

“Very well, you can leave now. Send Giant over!” Leylin waved his hand and watched Cyclops’ back as he left. His eyes showed that he had fallen into deep thought.

Although he was giving these defeated pirates positions one by one, he hadn’t completely let his guard down against them. For example, he couldn’t trust that Cyclops wasn’t deliberately leading the fleet into dangerous waters. He had already obtained the coordinates of Pirates’ Cove through other means, from merchants and pirates.

‘He told me the correct location, and also suggested the most efficient route. It looks like he’s truly pledged his allegiance to me.’ Cyclops didn’t know that he had just narrowly avoided death’s door. On the contrary, he was in good spirits from Leylin’s promise, and he quickly executed the tasks that Leylin had asked him to do.

“Boss, lookin’ fer me?” A deep, coarse voice sounded as a heavyset man walked in. He was more than 8 feet tall, and he had to lower his head to enter the captain’s cabin. His flesh trembled with every step he took, like he was some sort of half-giant.

“Yes. Giant, I want you to lead the Scarlet Tiger’s battle squad. Choose ten men for now, wait until we reach Pirates’ Cove and recruit more.” Leylin told him the plan with crossed arms.

The leader of the battle squadron was often the right-hand man of the captain. The battle squad was also at the forefront of every fight, so the position of its leaders had rather stringent requirements on strength.

Leylin had personally tested the might of this pirate that was called Giant. Not only did he have boundless strength, but he also had unparalleled talent in cultivation as a fighter. He could already release his qi and use martial techniques. Other than Leylin himself, only Isabe; could match him in close quarters combat.

Furthermore, this Giant had a straightforward personality; after numerous losses while dueling Leylin, he became more obedient and was easy for Leylin to control.

“Just pick anyone, huh?” Giant asked, clearly thinking of putting his own men into his team. However this was normal, otherwise even if he was strong as an individual, he would still be crushed by the other pirates.

“Yes, the sailors on the Scarlet Tiger, be it my sailors or the captured pirates, are all for your choosing,” With regards to this point, Leylin turned a blind eye.

“Aye, I’ll go and wake them up, and choose them one-on-one!” Giant looked extremely excited.

“As you wish!” Leylin didn’t have anything to say about Giant’s method of recruitment, and just waved him away.

As the leader of the battle squadron, if there weren’t a few trusted aides on the battlefield to take a knife for him, then perhaps he wouldn’t even be able to survive a single battle. It was necessary to allow him to choose his aides.

Furthermore, Leylin also believed that Giant wouldn’t dare to betray him. He was confident that the cost of rebellion was so incredibly high that it would eliminate all thoughts of betrayal…

The endless voyage, the battles and the struggle, challenged them over and over again. Leylin was confident that this journey to Pirates’ Cove would whip his crew into shape.

‘On the whole, even a well-known pirate crew on the outer seas needs about a hundred pirates,’ Leylin traced his finger on the map carelessly, ‘Take the Black Tigers, or even the Merfolk Pirates which we just destroyed; normal pirate crews all have more than a hundred people, and their captains are even rank 10 Professionals with exceedingly good equipment.’

‘Truly large-scale pirate crews need at least 300 pirates and above, and also need a number of ships. If I want a main battleship, it will have to be magically refitted or receive a cleric’s blessing.’

Such a crew was configured like the small coastal fleet of a minor coastal duchy. If he had such strength, Leylin would be able to find a rather good position amongst the continent’s navy, or even that of other countries. Who, then, would fight him without good reason?

As a result, there were only three truly large scaled pirate crews in the Dambrath Seas: the Black Skeletons, Tigersharks, and Barbarians.

Two of those pirate crews were even under the control of Marquis Louis. In addition, the other fleets owned by the marquis could not be underestimated. One of them was a professional slavers’ fleet.

This fleet had always been at the forefront of clashes with the natives, and Marquis Louis had used a lot of gold coins to arm it. It was even more powerful than the kingdom’s elite navy!

Leylin’s elimination of the Black Tigers and Merfolk Pirates would at best be him taking out the marquis’ trashe. He couldn’t be considered to have encountered the marquis’ main force.

Only once he was able to destroy the Black Skeletons, Tigersharks and the slavers’ fleet in one fell swoop would he be able to deal a fatal strike to the Baltic archipelago’s trade. However, this was almost impossible. Leylin could only continue to act from the shadows, and first clip the marquis’ wings.

It was very unrealistic for Leylin to fight against a Marquis of the kingdom now. However, Leylin was not an ordinary person. He would use any means necessary to accomplish his goals, without fear of the consequences.

He was the sort of person that could described as a reasonable lunatic, or perhaps he was the most insanely reasonable man.

“I’ll need many men to accomplish this goal… Or allies,” Leylin naturally would not be stupid enough to act against the marquis alone.

Furthermore, fighting Marquis Louis was one thing, but Viscount Tim was another. Although Leylin had targeted Marquis Louis all along, the one who would bear the brunt of it was still the Viscount who coveted the Faulen lands.

Leylin wasn’t sailing to Pirates’ Cove for no reason. Besides recruiting the men he needed, he was preparing to look for more supporters. Marquis Louis would have offended quite a few people with his dominant character, even if he had done so unintentionally, and Leylin wanted to round those people up and take advantage of their power.

Leylin pressed his fingers heavily on the mark of the Pirates’ Cove on the map, his eyes regaining their previous calm.

Chapter 829: Cry for Help

Elves were a populous intelligent race that all lived a secluded life on an enormous island. There were however remnants of some branch families on the mainland. They lived well under the protection of the elven god, and were blessed with good talent and long lives. Many of them made prominent contributions to the arts.

Naturally, elven slaves were highly sought after. Despite the protests and warnings of their race, their price had only increased, with wave after wave of adventurers hunting for them.

Half-elves were more common than purebloods. They still inherited the elfin beauty and elegance, and most of them stood out in terms of appearance, which had led to several disasters. It was not particularly surprising to see a half-elf maid in Pirates’ Cove, but Leylin’s expression had changed in spite of that.

“What’s your name?”

“My name is Karen, respected young master!” The ‘half-elf’ forced a smile. It appeared that she was not very well trained, and could not properly display her bodily assets to her customers.

“It looks like you haven’t been doing this for very long, how much are you for one night?” Leylin asked directly.

This sort of sudden humiliation made Karen want to clench her teeth, but she held herself back and revealed a dazzling smile, “One Dambrath gold coin…”

The price was a little high, but Leylin still nodded, “It’s a reasonable price, especially for a half-drow like you…”

The moment he called her half-drow, Karen rose up angrily. She was like a kitten whose tail had been stepped on.

“How do you know that?” she blurted out. She immediately covered her mouth, but clearly realised that she’d already all but confirmed it.

“Your eye colour. The colouring agent you used to stain it can’t fool me. You ears are also pointier than normal mixed-bloods by 12.4%, and they are slightly concave…” Leylin lightly pointed out the gaps in her disguise. His sharp observations made Karen subconsciously take a few steps back.

The corner of Leylin’s mouth tilted up in a smile as he saw Karen’s stats:

[Name: Karen, Rank 5 Assassin, Race: Half-Drow. Stats: Strength: 1 (3), Agility: 2 (5), Vitality: 0.5 (2), Spirit: 3, Feats: 1. Night Vision: Dark elves have the ability to see even at night. 2. Shadow Perception: Dark elves are sensitive to shadow particles, and are innately gifted assassins and pirates. Status: Poisoned by unknown toxin, causing strength, vitality and agility to fall!]

Karen’s physical stats somewhat surprised Leylin. She even had the abilities of a rank 5 assassin, but some unknown poison had taken control of her, locking half of her strength away.

It was very clear that the person who controlled Karen from the shadows only thought that she was an ordinary half-elf, otherwise they would never have let her come here. Would that not be like sending someone out to assassinate himself?

Leylin smiled faintly. This rank 5 assassin could not touch even a hair on his head.

“Haven’t dark elves always lived underground? How could you appear here, and even take up this line of work?”

Dark elves were a type of elf which were rumoured to live in the darkness. They had awoken the dark nature in their blood, becoming extremely brutal. They longed for violence, blood and chaos, and had separated from the regular elves to move underground. Some rumours said that their gifts in bed could make both men and immortals die of pleasure, that it was comparable to charm and pleasure magic.

“I’m a halfblood. I moved out from the underground with my clan, but we were all scattered in an attack. When I woke up, I was on a trading ship which was later attacked by the Barbarians…” Leylin’s eyes seemed to be filled with magic charm, and Karen could only helplessly tell her story.

‘No wonder… Half-drow really don’t differ too much from half-elves, and only a specialised scholar would be able to tell the difference. She’s a rank 5 assassin, and she did not have enough power to fight back against the entire Barbarian pirate fleet, not to mention that she was affected by the toxin’s restrictions… Of course, an assassin’s camouflage and disguise abilities could let her fool others, so that they thought that she was an ordinary half-elf.’

Something dawned in Leylin’s eyes as he said, “And after that you were controlled by the pirates, and now work for them as a maid?”

“Yes…” Karen nodded, and her eyes seemed to fill with momentary hope. She immediately knelt on the ground, looking up at Leylin, “Sir! I beg you, please save me from this hellhole!”

“Save you?” Leylin had an evil smile on his face as he sat back down, “Why would I save you? Give me a reason.”

Even Leylin had to admit that Karen was a rare beauty, especially with her eyes which were like the ocean waves. Her unique charm gave him a subconscious favourable impression of her.

“I…” Karen bit her lip, “I’m a rank 5 assassin. If you can save me, I’m be willing to serve you for a hundred years. I swear it in the name of the Dark Maiden!”

The Dark Maiden was a god who tended towards the good alignment, and could not be reconciled with the gods that other dark elves believed in. If Karen believed in this god, then perhaps this was the reason why she had been driven away from the underground.

“Why would you do that? Can’t you save up money to buy back your freedom?” Although she seemed rather out of practice, this was clearly not the first time she had done this sort of thing. This sort of life wasn’t completely unsuitable for a half-drow, and Leylin couldn’t think of why she would want to pay such a huge price for freedom.

“Is their price very high?” Leylin could only guess.

“No!” Karen’s lips curved into a rather heartbreaking smile, “They won’t ever let me go. As a slave, I don’t have the authority to buy my freedom. After I can’t be a maid anymore, those barbarians will sacrifice me to their gods…”

Leylin realised that the barbarians had saved her for some bloody and violent sacrificial rituals. Seeing Karen in that state, perhaps she had recently seen this happen several times, and so she began to plan her escape, begging Leylin for his help.

Even though she was pleading for help, she would meet an even worse fate if she asked the wrong person. Leylin seemed to have an air of nobility about him, and Karen was sure that he was not a pirate.

As a result, after realising that her cover had been broken, Karen immediately asked him for help. She almost did not mind promising to become his slave instead.

‘He’s a young man after all, if I could charm him…’ her eyes were filled with anticipation.

As a half-drow, she was born with the knowledge of how to handle males, and did not require further education on that matter. Although Leylin did not look too easily charmed, she was quite willing to at least try. When she thought of this, Karen’s heart seemed to be fired up, leaving two faint traces of a blush on her face. She appeared even more charming and lovely.

“A rank 5 assassin?” Leylin looked as if he was thinking over the matter with some difficulty, making Karen reluctant to mention her thoughts.

“You… Do you know anything about sailing?” After a long moment, Leylin stopped pondering and asked this question.

“Sailing?” Karen was shocked dumb. She originally thought that Leylin would come out with an outrageous request, but she had long made her mind up to use all her techniques to mesmerise him. She never thought that he would ask such a completely irrelevant question.

“Yes, I am a pirate captain, and I’m in need of sailors to be my underlings.” Leylin waved his hand and seemed to admit it very reluctantly. There was a trace of humour in his eyes, as if he was playing a joke on her, and Karen immediately knew that he had seen through all her plots.

“I… Honestly I don’t, but I will work hard to learn. I beg you, Sir,” Karen wanted to come up to Leylin and hug him, but Leylin nimbly dodged her.

“Then it looks like you aren’t much use to me,” Leylin said, making Karen’s heart completely sink.

“However, since you’re a dark elf, and you lived in the Underdark before, then you’re slightly worth something,” Leylin continued, his voice drifting into Karen’s ears and raising a thread of hope once again.

“Tell me, Karen, are you willing to become my dagger in the shadows, to help me dispatch my rivals, and drink the blood of my enemies?”

An invisible hand tilted Karen’s chin upwards, making her eyes widen considerably. “Mage Hand! You’re a wizard!”

This nobleman had come to a port where pirates fenced their goods, and although she did not know why, all Karen could see was opportunity! “I’m willing! In the name of the Dark Maiden I swear this— I will become your sharpest dagger!” Karen respectfully knelt down on her knees, making a strange gesture with her hand.

“Very well,” Leylin nodded. He really had recruited her on the basis of her being a half-drow assassin.

After all, he currently lacked a spy network and assassin group. Since Karen had recently lived in the Underdark, she would have good experience and knowledge in torture and interrogation as well as assassination. As a rank 5 professional assassin, she was just barely good enough to be of use…

Chapter 830: Tillen

“Very well, I’ll speak with the boss later about the issue of your ransom,” Leylin promised, rubbing his hands together.

“Many thanks, master!” Karen immediately began to address him differently. Although she currently looked like a weak little elfling, Leylin knew that once he cured her of her poison and armed her with a sharp dagger, this half-drow would immediately become a powerful god of death in the shadows.

After she had thanked him, the room’s atmosphere immediately grew awkward.

“Master… Would you like me to call my sister maids over?” Karen twisted the corner of her skirt, and looked extremely embarrassed.

“There’s no need. Didn’t you come to help me pour the hot water?” Leylin smiled faintly. The bloody battles and the accumulation of a great deal of life energy had left a fire in him that needed quenching.

“Yes, master!” Karen’s lips curved into a charming smile, and the entire room was soon enveloped in a layer of youthful lust.

Breakfast in the Barbarian Inn was a rich affair. The staples of fluffy and soft wheat bread and milk were present, and the intoxicating aroma of cheese and fried eggs was in the air. There were even several strings of juicy berries in a rattan basket nearby, to tempt one’s appetite.

There was a white napkin around Leylin’s neck as he enjoyed his meal with fluid movements. Karen sat on his side and occasionally stole a few glances at him with a blush on her face. These gestures made Leylin smile inwardly; she was a very lovely creature indeed, and he had exceedingly enjoyed his stay last night.

The half-drow seemed to have special talent in that area, but Leylin was not some incapable youth himself. His strength was too much even for a dark elf.

At this moment, Cyclops’ voice came from just outside the door, “Boss, can we come in?”

“Enter!” With Leylin’s command, Cyclops, Giant and Hulk entered the place all at once.

Looking at the massive dark circles and bags under their eyes, it was easy to tell that what kind of merriment they had gotten up to last night. Even after they had diligently cleaned themselves, Leylin could still smell a strong stench of alcohol and perfume on them.

Cyclops and the others noticed Karen by Leylin’s side, but the three pretended as if they hadn’t seen her, their eyes filled with a rather questionable smile.

“I’ll leave for now, master,” Karen said after seeing the others enter. She knew that Leylin had things to discuss with his subordinates, and smartly prepared to leave despite not finishing her breakfast.

“No need. You’re one of us now, so you should stay and listen,” Leylin said, motioning for Karen to stay.

Cyclops was shocked at this action, and he looked over the girl in appraisal. She was certainly just an elfling girl, and also a part-time prostitute, so why would she be recruited by the captain of their crew? However, since this was Leylin’s decision, they could not object to it.

Leylin picked up the white silk napkin and wiped the corners of his mouth before turning to Cyclops and the others, “So, how was last night?”

Cyclops knew that Leylin was naturally not enquiring about what mischief they had gotten up to. He cleared his throat, and began revealing the information they’d found, “Boss! I’ve already fully found out…

“In Pirates’ Cove, there are several merchant families that are interesting in our goods. However, our biggest patron is the boss of this inn… Haha.”

“That fox girl?” Leylin nodded, “What offer has she made us?”

“860 Dambrath gold coins for the whole lot! This price is rather average amongst the offers we have received, but it would be the safest option,” Cyclops spat fiercely before continuing, “Other families may have offered us a higher price, but I can tell with just one eye what they are planning. Those fuckers!”

Cyclops was a pirate after all, and he subconsciously exploded into foul curses. However, Leylin did not mind the merchants. Pirates’ Cove had a mixed bag of characters, and it was not surprising that a pirate would have their own ideas and want to devour their fleet and their goods all in one go.

Compared to this, as the Barbarians were the biggest players in Pirates’ Cove, it was entirely normal for them to take in these stolen goods to sell them for a profit.

“Mm, this price isn’t bad.” Although Leylin had buckled down on a pile of sugar for himself, the rest of his goods were worth at least 3000 gold coins and above. Since they were stolen goods and therefore ‘dirty’, Leylin would be satisfied with a small profit after it had changed hands a few times.

“This is a detailed map of Pirates’ Cove, including the locations of all the churches!” Hulk respectfully handed a sheepskin scroll to Leylin, and also brought a reply from the shipyard, “The shipyard’s owner has already had a look at the Scarlet Tiger, and has said that there shouldn’t be any problems repairing it. However, the owner said that it would be impossible to magically refit the ship. As for the cost, he will need at least 300 gold coins more…”

“Our little bunny rabbits played hard last night, but nothing big happened. They only had a fight with a few other drunkards,” Giant triumphantly announced, and just looking at his face one could tell that he did not lose the fight.

“Mm, we’ll rest here for 5 days. Hand the maintenance duties over to the shipyard owner, and ask him to finish the work as quickly as possible. We can make some concessions on the price.” It was only routine ship maintenance, and was not as if the ship’s entire keel was being replaced or massively refitted. In this world of extraordinary ability, if the shipyard master could put in all his effort to quickly complete it, there should virtually be no problems.

“Rest assured, boss!” Cyclops beat his chest confidently, taking control of the task. Hulk, who stood at his side, had a rather gloomy expression on his face.

Leylin pretended not to see this sort of infighting amongst his men’s factions. As long as it didn’t interfere with his or the others’ ability to fight, he didn’t particularly want to intercede.

“Mm, so Cyclops can sort it out. Hulk and Giant, come with me to get rid of the goods and hire some men as well.”

“Alright!” “Yes boss!” Since Leylin had issued the command, everything proceeded as expected.

The main hall of the inn was not as noisy as it had been last night, but there were bits of debris on the ground, and even drunkards on the floor.

“All of you, take this drunkard who can’t pay my money back to the docks. Put him in hard labour, and give him a harsh whipping every day until he pays back his debts. Don’t let him leave until then,” the fox girl boss from yesterday ordered the two barbarians from behind the counter, her hands on her hips.

“Oh, young master! Why have you gotten up so early?” After seeing Leylin, her expression quickly changed. She eyed Karen who was standing to one side, and under her piercing gaze, the elfling couldn’t help but unconsciously shrink back.

“Unless you’re dissatisfied with Karen’s service, in which case I’ll swap her for someone else for you!”

“No, no need. She’s very good,” Leylin scratched his nose, “I still don’t know my lady’s name?”

“Haha, my name is Tillen. You can call me Madam Tillen!” Madam Tillen smiled amorously at Leylin, a smile filled with the charm of a mature woman.

“Mm. Dear Madam Tillen, I want to talk about our transaction, and about this maid’s ransom as well,” Leylin said directly.

“Ransom?” Tillen swept her eyes across Karen, her eyes filled with a special look, “Well, it looks like our Karen has satisfied the young master well…”

Tillen seemed to yawn lazily. “This isn’t the place to talk, follow me!”

She swayed her sinuous hips as she left, leaving behind the strong fragrance of her perfume. Leylin smiled a little before following Her into a small room.

Madam Tillen brewed a floral tea that was said to come from the elves, and waited until white steam had risen before a shrewd expression appeared on her face. “You’ve asked me for my name, young master, but I don’t know how to address you.”

“You can call me Leylin,” Leylin replied with a smile. Since he wanted to form an alliance with her, trust was crucial. She was only asking for his name, which she could have easily found out later with some investigations.

“Alright, young master Leylin!” Madam Tillen crossed her long, slender legs, her fiery fox tail caressing her supply waist.

“I can take charge of the negotiations for the goods, but Karen is a slave of our inn. If it’s to do with her, I don’t have the authority to deal with this matter.”

“I know everything here is the personal property of the Barbarians!” Leylin smiled as he rubbed his hands.

*Crackle!* A powerful electric current flashed, filling the room with a piercingly bright light.

“Since it’s like this, call the person who can make a decision here.” He followed up in a deep voice, his powerful magic force lingering near his body.

“Wizard! You’re a wizard!” Madam Tillen’s voice grew somewhat shrill, and it was clear that she had not discovered Leylin’s identity.

A noble wizard was very rare in the outer seas. On top of that, Tillen realised that the energy undulations rolling off of Leylin put his strength higher than rank 5. A wizard of that level was a decent adventurer, and could even have a stronger master backing them!

‘A wizard named Leylin… That’s enough for me to find out who he is!’ Unless he used a fake identity, Tillen was certain that Leylin would not be able to escape her information network.

“I never thought that my guest would be such a powerful wizard,” Tillen clasped her hands to her bosom, inadvertently revealing a wide and creamy expanse of her delicate skin.

However, Leylin made very clear the division between business and pleasure, “When is your boss coming over?”

“Don’t be in such a hurry! The latest you’ll meet him will be tonight,” Tillen threw a flirtatious glance, “Before that, our store has many things to pass time with, does my guest care to have a look?”

Chapter 831: Thieves’ Guild

“No need, I still have matters to attend to. I’ll return at night,” Leylin got up to reject her, ignoring Madam Tillen’s resentful expression behind his back.

“Master, where are we going?” Karen stood next to Leylin, as well-behaved as a maid. Although the talks had not even begun, she acted as if she already belonged to him.

Hulk and Giant stood further away like a pair of loyal Imperial bodyguards.

“Call a few over to come with us and recruit the sailors,” Leylin said. Be it the Scarlet Tiger or the merfolk ship, they currently had a severe shortage in sailors. As a result, they needed to recruit a great number of sailors as quickly as possible. Pirates’ Cove would always have plenty of these fellows, one only needed to carefully choose from them.

‘Whips and Whiskey!’ Leylin looked at the tavern’s name rather speechlessly, but still opened the wooden door. Although it was still morning, the tavern was filled with people doing business, as well as many hungover drunkards.

“Boss! We found some people last night, and they’re all waiting here for you!” Giant smiled in his simple manner, suddenly hammering on the surface of the counter. It made all the hanging beer mugs shake chaotically with an ear-splitting sound.

“So it’s you, the fellow from last night! Hurry up and settle your bar tab!” A bleary-eyed old drunkard crawled out from the small door behind the bar, glaring at Giant with disdain. Once he saw Leylin however, his eyes seemed to brighten up considerably.

Perhaps he had seen the beautiful clothes that Leylin wore, and reckoned that this was the golden benefactor who could settle the bad debt.

“Greetings, dear customer!” The old man bowed deeply, smiling until his eyes almost seemed to disappear into his wrinkles.

There was a huge gap in his treatment of Leylin and how he had treated Giant before, but Giant only muttered a few words under his breath, and did not dare to say anything else.

After all, he had tasted Leylin’s methods before.

“What would you like?”

“A glass of rum! The rest of you are free to choose your own!” Leylin waved his hand and sat next to the counter, “Where are the people you found? Call them out and let me have a look at them.”

His standards were not too high at the moment, and ordinary pirates would suffice. Death would help him select the cream of the crop.

“Wait, boss!” Giant scratched his head, and rushed to gap between a few sofas like a hurricane, and began to beat the sofas up with kicks and punches. Loud curses could be heard from inside the sofas.

After a few seconds, over ten badly battered pirates with swollen faces and bleeding noses were driven out by Giant. Although they were wounded, these pirates had a rather lively temperament, which was beyond Leylin’s expectations.

“Giant, are these the people you fought with last night?” Leylin suddenly had a premonition.

“That’s right, boss!” Giant laughed in his simple manner, “These fellows are pretty tough, and they can hold their own against my beatings. I think they would do well in the battle squadron…”

Giant’s gifted strength was already on the level of a rank 5 Warrior, and he would not do badly against rank 6 or rank 7 Warriors either. For him to give this evaluation, the men must be rather powerful themselves.

At that point, they also knew that Leylin might become their employer, and they looked uneasily at the big fellow standing in the middle amongst them.

“Mm? What’s your name?” Leylin looked at the fellow that was obviously their leader. He had a bearded face, and a pair of eyes that looked half-asleep, which glimmered with intelligence from time to time.

“This is a fellow with a lot of stories to tell!” Leylin judged him on his very first glance.

“Ronald! My name is Ronald, my lord!” His tone of voice was very respectful and decorous, and he even seemed to have learnt a little noble etiquette.

“Can you read?” This sort of subtle distinction aroused Leylin’s interest.

“I previously spent some time in the Tillen scholars’ family learning how to write,” Ronald was very humble, and although they had only just met, he had immediately realised that Leylin was not an ordinary youth.

Not only could he subdue a subordinate like Giant, his temperament was different.

Only a life of abundance, and a long period of etiquette and culture lessons could nurture such an awe-inspiring presence, and an air of nobility.

In these times, a man like him represented hope!

“Very good! Ronald, are you willing to swear loyalty to me?” Leylin smiled, requesting loyalty rather than employment. This was clearly the invitation of a noble, and Ronald was stunned by it.

He was only startled for a short moment however. Ronald clenched his teeth and asked, “I want to ask my lord if you’re part of the Louis family? If so, then please forgive me, as it would be difficult for me to agree!”

“Why is that? Are they your enemies?” Leylin asked with great interest. He immediately saw a trace of hatred within Ronald’s eyes.

This complex change in emotion surfaced only for a moment, but it could not be concealed from Leylin’s gaze.

“Yes,” Ronald clenched his teeth and took a gamble. After all, if Leylin was a young master from the Louis family, then this situation would not end well for him.

At this moment, the atmosphere became rather delicate. The ten pirates next to Ronald glared at Leylin and his men, as if they were ready to leap into action if the response was unfavourable.

The boss of this place had long hid under the counter, and was obviously experienced with these abnormal situations.

“Haha… Haha…” Just when the atmosphere grew so tense that time almost came to standstill, Leylin suddenly laughed. His rippling laughter disrupted the heavy atmosphere, just like a rock being thrown into still water.

“I’m not one of Marquis Louis’ cronies. On the contrary, my family has a grudge against him,” Leylin spoke slowly, “After all, even if the Marquis needed men, it would be impossible for him to come and recruit here in the Pirates’ Cove, wouldn’t it?”

“Then, this Ronald is willing to accept your employment, my lord!” He skillfully answered Leylin’s previous question, and clearly did not put any heart into his reply. However, that was normal.

Leylin was not brain-dead enough to think that once he exuded his oppressing aura as a hero, subordinates would come running over to worship him.

Perhaps only after he had lead Ronald to begin taking action against Marquis Louis, would he be able to obtain true loyalty from him. Only once he had destroyed Marquis Louis would Ronald be willing to die for him.

‘However, having this sort of effect at the beginning is already good!’

“Very well, from now on you will be a sailor on the Scarlet Tiger ship. Ronald, you are my second officer!” Since there were many available positions now, he needed to fill the gaps quickly.

“Haha… This fellow, welcome to the family! Boss, bring the rum!” Giant firmly slapped Ronald’s back, making him stumble.

“No problem!” The boss who had previously hid under the counter immediately stretched out his hand, a cunning expression on his face, “Only… Shouldn’t you clear your bar tab before you continue drinking? Since you’ve already been hired by someone, doesn’t that mean you’ll have money very soon? Poor old Fade can’t stay afloat any longer…”

After he finished, he even winked at Leylin several times and squeezed out a few drops of crocodile tears.

After he heard this, Ronald and the others bowed their heads, and their faces flushed in shame.

‘It looks like these people all didn’t have enough to pay their bill, and were locked up here last night,’ Leylin grudgingly sighed.

“Tell me! How much money do they owe you?”

After walking out of the bar, the group of men behind Leylin’s back still looked rather ashamed.

“I’ve given you the criteria of the men I’d like to recruit, so now it’s up to you to recruit people. I need 100 men!” Leylin said to Hulk, after they had walked for a while.

“Don’t worry, my lord!” As a guard of the Faulen family, Hulk’s loyalty towards Leylin was very strong.

“Mm, go and attend to your business. There’s no need to follow me,” Leylin waved his hand to dismiss the others behind him.

“Master!” Karen followed behind Leylin with a worried expression on her face.

“Don’t worry, once I make a promise, there is no way that it won’t be fulfilled,” Leylin said in a gentle voice, but Karen involuntarily trembled.

“Alright. Please be careful, Pirates’ Cove is extremely chaotic…”

“Mm, I know,” Leylin nodded, disappeared into an alley on the side of the street.

Pirates’ Cove had a complex labyrinth of back alleys, and each one could allow only one person to pass. It was obviously crowded and chaotic and the floor was filled with slop and filthy things, making it smell absolutely awful.

However, Leylin’s gaze was fixed on a unique symbol in a corner of the alleyway. It was a symbol of two crossed daggers, which faintly pointed towards a certain direction.

“The Thieves’ Guild!” Leylin smiled, and immediately walked in the direction that the daggers were pointing to.

In the World of Gods, more and more people were able to advance into a profession. However, the one’s that attracted the most attention and had endured the longest were the three guilds- the Thieves’ Guild, the Warriors’ Guild and Wizards’ Guild!

These three guilds would frequently issue missions, which would bring great benefits to adventurer groups.

In the World of Gods, the number of shrines and whether the three major guilds were hosted there, was a major indicator of the prosperity of a city.

Pirates’ Cove naturally did not host the Wizards’ Guild, but Leylin had seen the Warriors’ Guild as their symbol had been very striking.

The Thieves’ Guild was an enormous organisation which had been secretly hidden in the dark, and their missions tended towards secrecy. Most of them were requests for assassinations or theft.

However, it was this dark network that seemed to permeate the entire continent, and rumour had it that they had the blessings of many gods.

Yes, the three great guilds each had the backing of more than one god!

Chapter 832: Underground

As he walked in the direction that the daggers pointed, his surroundings became increasingly remote. The liveliness of Pirates’ Cove was gradually left behind, and Leylin began to feel a pervasive sense of eeriness and desolation.

This feeling grew even more obvious after he walked down a flight of stone stairs. The terrifying senses of wizards allowed him to notice that there were three pairs of eyes spying on him in the shadows.

“It really feels like I’m walking down to hell!” Leylin chuckled. The sun was covered by vast dark clouds, projecting tremendous shadows.

He pressed his palm onto a gray rock covered in moss, and a gap immediately appeared in a wall nearby. He did not hesitate as he quickly ducked into the gap, simultaneously feeling many astonished gazes directed at him.

There was a very short path behind the wall, and at its end was a wooden door with an iron ring.

*Thump! Thump!* Leylin used the ring to knock loudly on the door, and it let out a distant sound.

The door creaked open slightly, revealing the face of an old man holding an oil lamp. He had practically no facial muscles anymore, looking like a withered corpse under the flickering light of the lamp. His two eyes looked dazed, the eyeballs completely motionless.

“The night is always lonely,” The old man said in a hoarse voice, as if he had not spoken for a long time.

“For those who are seeking brightness and hope!” Leylin smiled slightly, a dagger flying into his hand and beginning to dance through the air as elaborately as a butterfly.

The old man gave Leylin a probing look and opened the wooden door, “Come in, brother from the Underdark!”

With the light from his oil lamp, Leylin could see a deep and pitch-black passageway that seemed to go all the way to the core of the earth. A distant sound increased in volume as he made his way across it, until it turned into what seemed like a market bustling with life.

*Pak!* Two enormous gates opened, revealing an even more expansive underground world.

What entered his sights was a hall formed from a deep cave, with sinkholes in the floor and underground streams trailing off to numerous others. People from all walks of life populated this area, most strangely covering their faces with shrouds. Only pairs of vigilant eyes were revealed.

In the distance were a few wooden constructions and a large announcement board towering ahead. Below were many masked people gesticulating at it. While they tried to lower their volume, the sounds of discussion from the whole crowd joined to form a buzz.

“Welcome to the Thieves’ Guild! Is this your first time, kid?” A slender and tall person like a bamboo stick closed in, trying his best to create a stiff smile, “Need a guide? I…”

“No!” Leylin rejected resolutely.

This was the dark world of Pirates’ Cove. How could there be good people here? Even if one looked to hire people, just showing the slightest of weaknesses would cause these people to pounce on you like wild wolves, dividing everything amongst themselves after murdering you.

“Mister… I…”

“Scram!” Leylin glared at him, and the murderous aura born of indiscriminate slaughter forced the man several steps back.

Having killed people meant nothing. Everyone here had the blood of at least one or two people on their hands themselves, but Leylin’s own murderous aura was far more powerful than that. It was that of someone who’s truly honed themselves on a bloody battlefield, not someone to be trifled with.

An important part of being a thief was knowing oneself well. The slender bamboo stick of a man laughed awkwardly and disappeared into the darkness. He had a feeling that if he were to continue staying here, what happened next would be something he would regret.

“Is this darkness…” Feeling the blood and violence lingering in the air, as well as the pure malicious intent, Leylin revealed a nostalgic look. He was originally a dark Magus after all.

He ran his eyes over his surroundings casually, and began to head towards the large announcement board. The thing seemed to grow bigger the closer he got, until it was the size of a small hill.

Numerous enchanted words flickered on it; just maintaining this effect would require at least tens of gold coins everyday. The extravagance caused Leylin to nod to himself.

‘Mission: Track down whereabouts of a batch of silk cloth!’

‘Mission: Investigate reason and happenings for the fall of the Half Merfolk Island!’

‘Mission: Assassinate Viscount Lorraine’s wife!’

‘Selling information: The recent shipping route of the cargo ships of the Heigel chamber of commerce!’

‘Selling recipe for poison: Tears of Molin! Interested parties must come for a face-to-face meeting!’

All sorts of information and news flickered on the announcement board. The missions for investigation and assassination caused Leylin to let out an involuntary sound of surprise, ‘I didn’t expect news of Half Merfolk Island to travel here so quickly, and… Missions for the assassination of nobility put out here in public…’

The only impression that Leylin got was that as long as money was involved, these assassins could do anything. He gazed steadily at the board as the A.I. Chip rapidly scanned everything, collating the information on all these missions into one system.

While it was only the names of the mission, Leylin grew to understand the outer seas better from it.

‘Crimes and chaos… I like it…’ Though he only saw a corner of this dark world, Leylin knew that things were definitely not all quiet and tranquil in the region.

Many rebellious powers lay low in the shadows, preparing to deal Marquis Louis a fatal blow at any time. This would completely destroy the market dominance that the Baltic archipelago enjoyed, allowing them to plunder the riches and resources there!

Once the A.I. Chip showed a prompt that it had recorded all the information, Leylin walked straight to the wooden house at the back.

Many roads immediately showed up like a dense cobweb. Some fellows with dangerous auras occasionally appeared in Leylin’s senses, but there was only a very fuzzy image of them there.

‘This feeling… Is it a protective layer due to some divine force? In addition, this seems to be from a god I know well…’ Leylin snickered and strode inside.

*Pila!* The void was torn open at this moment, and an icy glint of steel was aimed straight at Leylin’s neck like a poisonous snake’s tongue.

The rank of this assassin seemed to be rather high, and he had almost escaped Leylin’s senses. It was only at the moment of the other party’s attack, that instant when their murderous intent surged out, that Leylin located them.

‘Mage Armour! Fragile Barrier!’ Two layers of protective spells immediately appeared with a thought.

But at the same time, he saw an icy look in the assassin’s eyes. The rays of light from a divine spell shone out.

Dispel Magic! Under the glittering light, Leylin’s protective spells instantly crumbled, revealing his astonished gaze. The dagger in the assassin’s hand ruthlessly swiped at his neck, and he evidently would not stop until it was all over.

Most wizards would need a period of time to recover their senses and contact the Weave after being hit with Dispel Magic. This slight moment would be enough for the assassin to carve Leylin into multiple pieces. After all, a wizard that had lost all ability to cast spells was just a regular human.

[Beep! Host affected by divine spell, suffering a temporary loss of ability to sense level 2 and 3 Weave. Countdown: 5 seconds!]

The A.I. Chip’s prompt arrived in that instant, but strangely enough, there was no mention of the level 0 and 1 Weave. Leylin could sense that his ability to use that still existed.

‘I see. So after I complete the analysis of the Weave, I’m immune to isolating skills?’ Leylin could now cast rank 0 and 1 spells in an instant, drowning this assassin. However, he immediately gave this idea up.

An ability that was too unexpected would give rise to suspicions, which was not beneficial to him at the moment.

‘Since it can seal the magic abilities I have, then…’ A magic scroll instantly appeared in his hands, emitting terrifying light.

“A rank 4 spell!” The assassin produced a sharp cry. Meanwhile, he could feel his dagger piercing into what seemed to be the most solid granite, unable to penetrate through it even by an inch.

“Rank 4 magic, Stone Skin! You despicable maggot, you even made me use such a precious scroll!” Leylin feigned fury as he was completely covered by a layer of stone skin, as if he now wore armour of stone. This was Stone Skin, a rank 4 spell. Its defensive power was outstanding even among other spells of its kind.

This scroll was something that Ernest had given Leylin while he had still been in the manor just in case. He hadn’t used it during the previous times of danger, but he’d done so now.

This was a rank 4 magic scroll! Even if its value wasn’t enough to equal that of a city, it was very precious, and the fury on Leylin’s face was understandable.

“You should not have come here!” The assassin’s voice was hoarse as he hurriedly retreated.

“Trying to leave now?” Leylin’s expression was filled with fury as he swung his fist.

*Thud!* The tip of the dagger was broken off by the stone fist, but it did not stop there. It crashed into the assassin’s body with great power.

*Crack!* A layer of his defence was destroyed, and the assassin’s body was sent flying backwards, the imprint of a fist clear on his chest.

“Never… Never has someone been able to treat me this way. I will kill you…” The assassin pulled his mask down, revealing a sullen face, with blood trickling from the corner of his mouth.

“Let’s see who dies first!” Leylin strode closer, a murderous aura apparent on his face.

“Esteemed guest, please forgive him!” At some point, a figure dressed entirely in a black robe came to the centre, a streak of divine force flying to the assassin’s body.

Under the light, the assassin’s wounds healed at a startling rate.

“Cure Serious Wounds! A rank 3 divine spell!” Leylin’s eyes narrowed as he saw the emblem on the other party’s chest.

Chapter 834: Alliance

“Foreign wizard! I can sense an aura emitting from you, that only clan priests possess!” The high-level barbarian warrior, Odge, had his eyes fixated on Leylin’s hands, “In addition, you’re also a soldier worth respecting!”

His astonishing sharpness allowed him to sense Leylin’s accomplishments as a warrior.

“Then… Speak your purpose in coming here!” After Odge spoke, the fox lady Madam Tillen immediately stood obediently as the side, as though she was a maid showing respect.

Leylin took a deep breath, then said his request, “I would like to join forces with the Barbarians’ to attack the Baltic archipelago!”

“Are you crazy, young lad?” Even the fox woman couldn’t listen to such a fantastical plan. She stood up as her chest heaved violently, “Do you know how many Professionals Marquis Louis has under him? You actually want to rope us in as his enemy? Don’t think we’ll think highly of you because you exterminated the Black Tigers and Half Merfolk Island. Wait till you’ve gotten rid of the Black Skeletons or Tigershark Pirates, before saying that again!”

“But… you’re ALREADY enemies with the Marquis. I’m just offering a helping hand, am I not?” Leylin shrugged his shoulders and said with a smile.

“Good lord! To think that I actually know a chap like you who doesn’t understand the complexity of the situation…” Madam Tillen was so furious that her entire body started to tremble, and she was close to chasing him away immediately.

But at this very moment, an enormously powerful pair of hands stopped Tillen from taking action. “Let him continue!”

“Odge… You…” The fox lady turned around and saw the interested expression in the barbarian’s eyes.

“The enemy of our enemy is our friend!” Leylin smiled and spoke frankly with assurance. “Not only can the Faulens offer you support as a noble family, I am also a wizard, with a formidable tutor as my backing.”

The power of magic was the eternal sorrow of these barbarians. Odge’s expression changed greatly in response. Even though there were a few barbarian priests who had inherited magical abilities, they were always at a disadvantage compared to human wizards.

Upon seeing this, Leylin became more confident. “I presume… that you also know how powerful magic can be, right?”

“Yes, we will require the assistance of formidable magical power to aid us in defeating Boruj!” The Barbarian Warlock nodded.

“Boruj… Is that the chief wizard of Louis’ family?” Leylin quickly recalled the information he had purchased at the Thieves’ Guild.

“That’s right! I can tell you for definite that he’s a high level wizard above rank 15! Without him, if they relied only on Black Skeletons and Tigershark Pirates, I’d have ripped those two pirate crews into shreds a long time ago…”

“A wizard above rank 15!” Leylin exhaled deeply. Such high level wizards often had great mastery over powerful plane transmission spells and life spells, which made killing them exceptionally difficult.

“Such wizards are probably few and far between even in the Dambrath Kingdom, right? Why would he agree to work under Marquis Louis?”

If it was him that was the marquis of the empire, there would still be a possibility of attracting a high-level wizard to work for him. But Marquis Louis evidently didn’t have this qualification. In the entire Dambrath Kingdom, the only person who had the ability to recruit a high-level wizard would only be His Majesty.

“As a matter of fact, I know a little about this…” Seeing that Odge didn’t reject the alliance, and even appeared to admire Leylin, Madam Tillen took a deep breath, no longer looking down on Leylin.

“According to my intelligence reports, that marquis apparently promised to build him a wizard tower, and used this to pay for the wizard’s assistance…”

“We absolutely must not let him successfully build a wizard tower!” Without waiting for Madam Tillen complete her sentence, Leylin had already made up his mind. Even it was a wizard tower of the lowest standards, the amount of wealth required was astronomical. Two million gold coins was the most basic requirement, and they had to be kronas.

With such a huge temptation, it was no wonder that Boruj would cast himself as one of Marquis Louis’ subordinates. It was also not surprising that his table manners were exceptionally unsightly, as he was a person who wanted any kind of benefits.

Acting tastelessly and greedily

But the more it was so, the more Leylin wanted to destroy their alliance.

No one else understood the terror of a wizard tower more clearly than a wizard himself. A low-ranking wizard tower was equivalent to a rank 15 wizard, the sort that did not need to rest day or night, with boundless energy. Once he successfully constructed his wizard tower, the entire Baltic archipelago would be so sturdy that it would be impenetrable under Boruj’s supervision.

With the wizard tower, not only would Boruj take a step forwards to advancement, it also meant that he could groom a steady flow of wizard apprentices!

It only took a few reminders from Leylin before Odge’s eyes shone with resolution.

“But… According to our intelligence reports, Marquis Louis is already secretly buying mithril and refined gold in bulk, and they even increased the intensity of their slavers’ fleet. He even sent people to the mainland to acquire high-grade construction blueprints…”

“The more he moves forward, the more we cannot let them succeed, or else his will be the only voice in the outer sea in the future!” Leylin’s expression was serious, “I’ll incessantly raid his shipping routes from now, I’ll need your cooperation for intelligence reports and to fence stolen goods.”

Hearing Leylin’s simple yet crude plan, Madam Tillen had a rather thoughtful expression on her face. What he offered was something the Barbarians themselves could not do.

Were they to do such a thing, it would mean the start of a war! The Marquis’ powerful fleet of ships would arrive at Pirates’ Cove in the blink of an eye, but it was different for Leylin. He was executing this in private, but still had the identity of a noble on the surface.

Even Marquis Louis would not dare to commit the heinous crime of attacking another noble family’s territory without any evidence. Besides, only a wizard like himself would be able to avoid the detection and predictive spells of the wizard working under Louis.

As for dispatching pirates and the like, did he think the other nobles were fools? There was a church on Faulen Island as well.

As long as the high-level wizard Boruj was not around, Leylin dared to join up with the Barbarians, and make sure that Boruj would walk the path of no return.

Many thoughts passed through the barbarian’s mind. One should not be baffled by his appearance; although he was a barbarian, his ability to hold the throne of leadership showed that he was no simple character.

Moreover, no matter how he looked at it, the one taking the risk would be Leylin and his family. There wouldn’t be any gains or losses on his part. This was what Leylin had planned long ago, and it would soon bring sorrow to his weaker opponents.

“Madam!” At this instant, there was a light knock on the door.

“What’s the matter? Didn’t I say before that you can’t approach the lord if there isn’t anything important?” Madam Tillen scowled, but continued to swing her hips as she opened the door by a small crack.

“Madam!” A maid with extremely clever eyes lowered her head and secretly scanned her surroundings, before whispering something in Madam Tillen’s ear.

After closing the door, Madam Tillen returned to her seat. She looked at Leylin oddly. Her facial expression changed a few times, before she leaned forward on Odge’s shoulder and said a few words to him.

“You’re good!” Odge gave Leylin a profound look. He then whispered urgently and hastily in Madam Tillen’s ear.

A high-ranking warrior of Odge’s level could already manifest their qi into the external environment. Isolating an area from detection was simply a piece of cake for him, and even Leylin couldn’t hear anything they were discussing.

“Alright! Our chief has agreed to form an alliance with you, and even share our intelligence reports and the channel where we dispose our stolen goods with you!”

Madam Tillen grudgingly shot a bitter glance at Leylin, as though he had gotten some huge advantage, “However, we want half of the benefits of your profits every round!”

“Ten percent at most, or else I will not be able to pay my subordinates!”

Once they were back to this matter, Madam Tillen seemed to have returned to being that shrewd wife. Leylin couldn’t give them his benefits just based on a few sentences she uttered, and they settled on the criterion of thirty percent in the end.

Since the leaders of both parties had already confirmed their inclination towards a collaboration, the rest of the matters could be settled by their subordinates. Odge stood up, causing a slight tremor in the process.

“Nobleman from the outer seas, wizard Leylin! Are you my friend?”

“Of course. May our friendship last for a long time, and even carry over to our descendants!” Leylin solemnly made a promise.

*Thump!* Two fists, one large and one small, collided, producing a light crack. This was a contract of their alliance and a pledge between men.

Of course, how long this would be maintained was a question that Leylin found hard to confront. However, before the fall of Marquis Louis’ influence, their relationship as allies would be relatively solid.

After Odge left, the fox lady moved next to Leylin. Her petite frame which could light up a fire in most men was almost completely leaning against his body as she said in a feminine voice in his ear, “Hehe… Odge seems to like you very much?”

“My apologies, Madam! It’s about time for me to leave!” Leylin pushed her away courteously and got up to take his leave.

Hearing his words, a trace of disappointment flashed across her eyes, although it wasn’t clear if it was genuine or false. “Your behaviour really does deeply wound me! However, elder sister still has two gifts for you!”

“Karen! You belong to Mr Leylin from now on. You need to satisfy all of his demands, understand?”

“Understood, Madam!” Karen agreed like it was a conditioned reflex, before a hint of shame and fury flashed across her face, as though she had come to a realisation.

Although he was fully aware that Madam Tillen was being generous, at least she had gotten the approval of the barbarian, or else she definitely wouldn’t have dared to free Karen of her imprisonment. Leylin thanked her anyway.

Chapter 836: Reward

“Master! Your beautiful strength is like a resplendent jewel, brimming with a dazzling brilliance!” Karen, who was standing beside Leylin, immediately complimented him. As a half-drow, she seemed to have regained her natural instincts after being liberated. She was gradually recovering her darkness and thirst for blood, which was characteristic of the drow.

“Alright, get up.”

Cyclops and the other pirates who had long pledged their loyalty were already aware of the outcome, thus they didn’t appear to be flabbergasted. The new pirates, on the other hand, were all frightened out of their wits, especially Ronald and his group.

“So, what do you think? Does anyone else have any objections?”

Leylin ran his eyes over the crowd. The other pirates didn’t dare meet his gaze, yet their eyes were brimming with reverence.

“Excellent! I like the respectful look in your eyes.” Leylin nodded. His subordinates immediately pulled out two trunks of silver kronas and copper coins.

This was the only payment he had obtained from selling the majority of goods he had on hand. Madam Tillen had ruthlessly cut the prices, probably in an attempt to vent her anger.

However, this much was sufficient to maintain the pirate crew for a few months. As for the months after that? Why would he still worry about providing for his men after getting a hold of the riches of the entire sea?

“The pay I promised earlier will not be reduced.” Leylin opened the chest. The twinkling radiance of the silver kronas blinded the eyes of numerous pirates.

“Each buccaneer of the Scarlet Tiger will obtain a fixed salary every month, in addition to the loot plundered,” Leylin announced loudly. This policy was quite different from the usual pirate way, and it instantly received cheers from the pirates.

Although it was akin to opening a huge hole in the finance department, Leylin needed to create a strong pirate crew as fast as possible, and he couldn’t care less about anything else.

After all, immense pressure and death threats were insufficient to govern a huge group. A system that gave encouragement through incentives had to be established. Otherwise, why would they join a crew with a temperamental captain like Leylin, when there are so many other pirate crews?

As soon as news of this spread, no matter how savage Leylin would be rumoured to be, he probably would still have enough manpower sources. Perhaps he could even attract a few Professionals, which would be incredibly amusing.

‘As expected, these pirates don’t have a single bit of loyalty.’

After giving out the money, the newly recruited pirates were immediately in high spirits. They looked as if they had completely forgotten what had happened earlier. Leylin secretly shook his head.

However, this was the objective truth, and there was absolutely nothing that could change that. Leylin could only take a laissez-faire approach.

After all, the control that any pirate captain had over his men was always the same. Unless authority was rooted deeply after long periods of time together, and trust was established through continuous victories, this was all it would amount to.

If it was not like this, Leylin wouldn’t have been able to subdue the Black Tiger crew previously, and set up a new crew with them as the first few subordinates.

‘These incentives… It seems like it is still not enough.’

There was a flash in Leylin’s eyes as he stood on the platform, “Giant!”

“I’m here, boss!” Giant immediately half knelt on the floor. His body resembled a small-scale mountain.

“You killed more than ten enemies when you accompanied me last time. You’re also the Professional with the highest rank among all my men. I want to reward you.”

Leylin waved his hands and a piece of leather armor, that resembled a singlet, flew in front of Giant. There was an armor plating in the most crucial body parts, offering better protection.

Giant put on his sleeveless leather armour. His face, however, changed when a magical brilliance burst from his armour. He couldn’t help but shout in surprise, “This is magical armour!”

“What? Magical armour?” This immediately attracted envious looks from the other pirates.

Even though it was the cheapest of all magical goods, it had to be supported by primary smelting spells, and was worth hundreds of gold coins. Furthermore, a life-saving item such as this one was priceless.

“Yes. It has been reinforced by the “Hardness Spell” three times. Even a heavy hammer would be unable to break through your defense with a single blow.”

Actually, the raw material of this leather armour had been looted from the captain of the Merfolk Pirates after the battle. Leylin had found it to be beneath him, thus he decided to modify it for his men to equip.

Giant didn’t know what else to say and could only scratch his head as he smiled foolishly, while attracting a few jealous looks.

“Also, Ronald!” Leylin turned his gaze to Ronald.

“Young master! You called for me?” Ronald knelt on the floor with one knee, with a strange feeling in his heart.

“Yes! Your earlier actions attest to your loyalty! This rapid explosion ring is yours!”

This had also been a contribution made by those unlucky Merfolk Pirates. Leylin did not feel a tad bit embarrassed.

“Many thanks!” Ronald felt as though he had been struck in the chest by a heavy hammer/

While knowing that he had only coincidentally been there when Leylin needed to point out role models amongst the new pirates, he was still elated.

This was indeed a magical item! It was so valuable that it could be a family heirloom for commoners, knights and lords.

“I will always be loyal to you!” Ronald kissed the ring on his finger, and solemnly accepted this precious treasure into his embrace, also attracting many envious stares. Mainly, many of the new pirates had flushed faces. They gazed at Leylin as though they were looking at a god.

As long as they worked hard , there would be hope. As long as they put in the effort, there would be reward.

More often than not, the people of the lower classes only hoped for so much, yet the upper classes cruelly deprived them of even this slight hope.

But now, Leylin showed them hope of being able to completely change their fates. This alone was sufficient to arouse their enthusiasm and will to fight.

“Raise the flag! Set sail!” Seeing their boosted morales, Leylin loudly announced his command.

“Aye! Aye!” The multitude of pirates immediately started to get busy. Under the directions of Cyclops, Hulk and the others, the Scarlet Tiger was quickly driven out of the dock.

At this moment, the bishop and priest from the God of Murder were silently observing the situation from the shadows, until the ship departed.

The bishop spoke after a long silence, “What do you think?”

“He’s firm when dealing with issues, determined and unscrupulous. It’s hard to believe that he is only fifteen!” The priest seemed unwilling to admit it, but eventually admitted.

“But even so, we don’t have to tell him about ‘that’, right?”

The bishop replied with a cold snort, “Cly has already violated the teachings of our master, and is bent on avenging his brother who betrayed the church long ago. He must be punished for such conduct.”

However, these were just excuses, The pivotal point was that Cly was a hindrance to his own plan.

For a person with great influence, disposing of a small pawn was nothing in the face of the bigger picture.

As long as the glory of the God of Murder continued shining across the seas for eternity, what was the worth of a few highly-ranked assassins?

“I’m looking forward to what will happen to him” The bishop smiled as his silhouette slowly faded into the darkness.

The priest’s eyes were filled with shock. As the bishop left, he started understanding that the bishop actually placed great importance on that young nobleman.

……

The Scarlet Tiger sailed on under the azure skies, although it appeared to be moving slowly, it was travelling at high speeds.

“Five hundred metres ahead! I spotted an unknown ship without a pirate flag!” The mariner on the observation deck called out.

“Boss!” Giant immediately appeared behind Leylin, donned in his newly-attained leather armour.

Cyclops also appeared next to Leylin and reported softly, “I asked around beforehand. A bunch of scurvy dogs are coveting our booty and ship.”

“Organisations that have been blinded by greed?” Leylin suddenly raised his brows, “Their vessel doesn’t look too shabby. We are still lacking a few buccaneers and slaves, aren’t we?”

After hearing Leylin’s words, Giant and the rest were already dedicating a moment of silence in mourning for the pirates on the other ship. They would never know what a terrifying chap they had provoked.

“Prepare for battle. I want to check out the strength of these men,” Leylin instructed Ronald, who was standing behind him.

“On it, young master! You will see it!” Ronald retreated respectfully.

With such a formidable wizard on board, he couldn’t see the slightest possibility of them being defeated.

The two ships came into contact. Without the slightest bit of hesitation or shouting, they both launched their attacks.

After the whistling of the harpoons and numerous rounds of feathered arrows flying back and forth, they immediately jumped aboard each other’s ships and descended into a chaotic battle.

Giant laughed maniacally as he brandished the enormous claw hammer in his hand. He was covered in the enemy’s blood and resembled a fiend emerging from the abyss as he charged forth in the frontline.

Behind him, Ronald commanded the new pirates, and assembled them into a few simple formations, obtaining favourable results. He felt as if he possessed an irresistible force, especially with the weapon infused with poison that Leylin had provided.

Seeing his fluent commanding skills, Leylin couldn’t help but be fond of him, ‘Who would have thought that Ronald would be a military genius?’

“You guys attack them as well. I’m going to meet with an old friend.” Leylin waved his hands and flew out of his ship, landing onto the opponent’s deck.

Ray of Frost! Fireball!

A hell made of fire and ice spread across the ship, along with the ghoulish wails and painful howls of numerous pirates.

“He’s a wizard!”

The powerful force generated by the spells instantly dealt a huge blow to the morale of his opponents. The situation seemed to be tipped in favour of Leylin and his party.

At this moment, however, several secret conscients with the intent to kill approached from the darkness. Their keen aura had the characteristic of highly-ranked assassins.

“It’s indeed you guys!” The corners of Leylin’s lips curled into a gentle smile as he tore open the magic scroll in his hands right away.

“Ice Storm!” The snow attack covered an even larger area, and had the powerful might of a rank 4 spell. Leylin’s surroundings instantly turned into a land of ice and snow.

Chapter 841: Goddess of Wealth

“We are all nobility, and can only follow the rules of the game between nobles…” Marquis Louis spoke slowly, “The Faulen Family was very weak before and had no real backing, which was originally a very good opportunity for us, but…”

Having said this, he glared at Tim, resulting in Tim lowering his head further.

The Faulen Family used to be like duckweed floating through the air, but even then Marquis Louis did not dare to deal with them out in the open. He’d only sent out pirates in secret.

Uncertain, no good foundation

Furthermore, if those pirates had succeeded, the family would be annihilated!

But things could no longer be played that way. The Faulen Family now had more connections in the region, as well as backers. The strength they possessed was rapidly increasing. If he did not use all the strength he had at his disposal, Marquis Louis was not confident that he could wipe them out.

But was this possible? Even as a marquis of the kingdom, he could not attack the territory of another noble for no reason.

When it came to pirates, even with both the Black Skeletons and Tigersharks working together, Marquis Louis was still not confident, especially since the opponent had a church on their island.

With such a large-scale pirate invasion. It would be hard to avoid confronting the church.

Furthermore, for those on the outer seas, who did not know that these were the two most powerful pirate groups under Marquis Louis? His goal was far too obvious.

“The timing’s gone! We’ve already lost the best time to attack…” Marquis Louis sighed, “The profits from these two goods, sugar and fish floss, really do measure up to the slave market…”

“Don’t worry, father! I’ll definitely get those two techniques!” William spoke with confidence, “The current situation is that we have many ships and shipping routes out in the open, but the Scarlet Tigers hide in the darkness where they have freedom. They can be the eyes and ears of the Faulen Family. On the surface neither side can make a move, and only rely on battling it out in the shadows. I’ll definitely annihilate the Scarlet Tigers and break off the opponent’s eyes and claws that exist in the darkness!”

Such profound insight immediately had Marquis Louis nodding.

“Very good. I’m relieved that you thought of that! Besides the Black Skeletons, I will order the Tigersharks to listen to you as well. The military fleet will await your orders at any time. You must destroy our enemies!”

At this moment, Marquis Louis’ ruthlessness in staking everything on this was shown.

“Understood, father!” William’s voice trembled slightly. To be able to have so much support made it clear that his status as the successor was unshakeable, and this was already the beginning of the shift of power.

“Also, the opponent has a powerful wizard. We can’t ignore that! Wizard Boruj!”

“Lord Marquis!” An old man wearing grey wizard robes walked out from the shadows, eyes glinting with wisdom. The magic rays around him made those around him feel suffocated.

William and Tim hastily bowed towards the chief wizard of their family. Even Marquis Louis did not dare treat him with disrespect, “We will have to trouble you for this matter!”

“No problem!” Boruj’s voice was hoarse, with the trace of a foreign and exotic accent, “I’ve long since wished to have a duel with that old rival whom I have yet to meet…”

“Henceforth, Wizard Boruj will accompany you until the Scarlet Tigers have been annihilated!” Marquis Louis stated.

“U-Understood!” This abrupt but pleasant surprise made William feel dizzy, and even his voice slightly trembled.

“Good! The future of our family will lie with you. Don’t disappoint me…”

Tim was standing at the side. Seeing the pretty picture of the father and son together made him feel like an outsider. He was roaring inside crazily, but could only put on a calm expression, not daring to show any of his resentment on his face.

……

A giant golden ship slowly sailed to the dock of Port Venus.

This large ship had extremely extravagant decorations, and there was even a layer of metal that emitted golden luster. From afar, it looked like a ship made entirely of pure gold.

At the ship’s bow was a large emblem made of pure gold that shone with dazzling light. This was a symbol of the Goddess of Wealth, taking the form of a huge gold coin.

‘They’re truly nouveau riche! It would be a disservice for them if they didn’t ruthlessly spend this money.’ Although he thought this, Leylin didn’t dare show anything on his face. On the contrary, he had no choice but to put on his friendliest smile and welcome them.

There were others beside him. Baron Jonas, Madam Sarah, housekeeper Leon… Basically all the respected people here showed up. It was obvious how mind-blowing it was for them to see a Gold Priest.

“Welcome to Port Venus. We hope you like it here, beautiful madam!” Against Leylin’s expectations, the Gold Priest who had arrived was a female!

She looked to be about 17 or 18, and her eyes seemed to be shining brightly. They held hints of the shrewdness unique to merchants, and her skin was as exquisite as ivory. She had a tender and splendid smile about her lips that made her look like the little girl next door. Her appearance made it difficult to associate her with the profession of a priest.

However, her brilliant high-ranking priest robe with vibrant colours as well as her powerful divine light, made her status clear.

“Hello, Sire Leylin! My name is Xena. This is a port brimming with hope. I sense the flow of a great origin of wealth…”

As was expected of the priest of the Goddess of Wealth, this was the first thing she mentioned.

“Haha… It’s great that Mistress Priest likes this place!” As the successor of the Faulen Family, as well as the delegate to represent her, Leylin elegantly extended his right hand helped her down.

“Powerful! Is this the power of a high-ranked priest?”

The instant their skin made contact, Leylin seemed to see a body brimming with godly luster. All sorts of power from divine spells converged to form a high-pressure electrical network that kept her safe within it, giving off a sense of danger. This was the path of a priest. High-ranked priests prayed devoutly and borrowed the strength of gods to purify their souls, achieving the effect of existing in harmony with god. There was even the possibility of becoming a holy spirit!

Even the A.I. Chip was unable to scan her exact stats, and could only give the conclusion that she was extremely dangerous.

‘Rank 15! She’s definitely a high-ranked priest who’s at least rank 15!’ Leylin went on his guard. Meanwhile, she seemed to have noticed him spying and shot him a dark look.

“Oh, my apologies!” It was only at this point that Leylin realised he was holding on to her hand. This was rather impolite. However, as someone who had gone through various worlds, he could adapt quickly and immediately took care of the awkwardness.

After the banquet, Baron Jonas returned to the manor, which left Leylin alone to entertain the Gold Priest.

“It’s rumoured that Baron Jonas thinks highly of his first son and has been giving him more authority lately. Seems like it’s true!” Xena, who was on a mission set by the church, watched Leylin sitting opposite her, her eyes flashing with interest.

He seemed to have a unique temperament and a lot of confidence. The fact that a mere 16 year old could have such a presence astonished her. Of course, he seemed to be a decent wizard, though it wasn’t much in Xena’s eyes.

For the rich and overbearing church, cultivating a few spellcasters was no issue. In the Goddess of Wealth’s church, there was no lack of legendary wizards.

After all, for the wizards who readily spent gold coins at every turn, there was nothing more comfortable than being able to embrace the church of wealth’s golden thighs.

“This porcelain is very high quality!” Xena looked at the cup in her hands. It had many complicated and intricate flower patterns, showing the exquisite craft of the elves.

“How about trying the cocoa from the eastern archipelago? It’s said that this marvelous plant has the amazing effect of perking one up without harming the body…” Leylin smiled while pouring her a steaming hot cup of cocoa.

Xena had naturally seen this drink before. The production of cocoa beans was meagre, and on the continent it was sold at an astronomical price. Of course, what shocked her even more was Leylin’s capability.

‘Does that mean… he’s already built up a connection with the eastern pirates?’ Xena’s eyes shone, and she then put down the beautiful porcelain cup in her hands.

“Mister Leylin, I’m sure you know my intentions in coming here. May I know what you think of establishing a church on the port?”

“I’m definitely not opposed to you joining in, but there’s actually a plan already for the Port Venus. Every plot of land has its own function… of course, it’s not a problem to squeeze out a section, but…” Leylin had a standard smile on his face.

“The Goddess of Wealth will not mistreat any follower of hers!” Xena placed a golden card on the table, “This is a proof for the withdrawal of money. With it, you can exchange 10 000 kronas from any church of wealth. Treat it as the capital for buying this land!”

Rich and overbearing, Leylin now knew what rich and overbearing truly meant! The church of the Goddess of Wealth was truly rich, unlike the stingy Tapris who probably wasn’t even willing to pay rent.

Of course, this was a problem left behind from Baron Jonas’ time. This would not happen again with Leylin in charge.

“Then there aren’t any other problems. The city hall will mark out the land tomorrow!” Leylin smiled gently, a hand taking and keeping the golden card on the table without batting an eyelid.

The Goddess of Wealth generously contributed her own divine realm, providing currency storage services. With her divine force as a mark against fraud, trying to trick anyone in this was just shooting oneself in the foot.

However, with this, there were fees to pay if people wanted to store their money with her. Then again, this was to be expected from a goddess even greedier than a dragon.

Chapter 842: Agreement

“Apart from the issue with the church, there is also another matter which is related to why I came…” Xena’s gaze pierced straight into Leylin.

‘Finally, here it comes,’ He thought inwardly. He had long felt that as his profits from his two avenues of trade grew greater and greater, he would eventually attract the attention of larger organisations.

As this moment had come, his earlier alliances to protect his profits were no longer of any use. In reality, Leylin had already planned in his heart to exchange his techniques with them. He’d long since understood the rules of the game in this world, and that he could no longer maintain a monopoly by virtue of his own strength.

He was already surprised that he was able to gobble up a year’s worth of profiteering. Now, he would need to find a sufficiently powerful backer to sell his techniques to. From this point of view, the church of wealth was evidently a rather good option.

“Is it the fish floss and white sugar?” Leylin directly pointed it out.

“Yes, as well as you!” Xena’s eyes were filled with humour, “Compared to those two techniques, the person who invented them is much more worthy of our consideration. You have Midas’ touch!”

“Me!” Leylin pointed at himself, feeling a little ridiculous. Secretly, however, he was constantly on guard and a little apprehensive. It looked like he had been acting too conspicuously recently.

For now, Xena was only interested in his mind, but what if she discovered more things about him?

As he thought about it, Leylin suddenly made up his mind. After he resolved the issue with Marquis Louis, he had to disappear for a while. Otherwise, once he received the attention of even more deities, his troubles would certainly grow.

“These two techniques came about due to luck. I have always loved reading books, and discovered the invention from the writings of the ancients by chance. I’m also very thankful to my father as well, as he allowed my nonsense and even specially bought some craftsmen slaves for me…”

Leylin felt a magic undulation sweep across him, clearly trying to find out whether he was lying. Although Xena’s action was performed in secret, how could he possibly not notice it? He raged in his heart, but on the surface he did not make a single sound.

His expression made Xena rather suspicious, and as she felt the feedback from her divine spell, she grew even more confused.

‘It can’t be, he’s telling me the truth?’ Xena felt a little disappointed, but did not continue to discuss the matter of the two trades with Leylin. No matter how one looked at it, the profits from the fish floss and white sugar were absolutely mind boggling. If she could not stick her hand in these two trade rivers which were overflowing with gold, she was sure to lose Waukeen’s favour, and would be replaced with other priests of gold.

Leylin’s nature and the A.I. Chip’s adjustments were more than enough to hide information from a high-ranking priest. Looking at Xena’s crestfallen face, Leylin inwardly smiled to himself, but his expression was still as serious as ever.
“Then, let’s discuss the issue of the the two trades.”

“Say it! How many gold coins do you want to give me the techniques?” Xena said with a rich and powerful air, suppressing her emotions completely.

“The entire curing process of fish floss, as well as the can sealing method and even the skilled craftsmen can all be given to you for 100,000 gold pieces!”

For Leylin, it was necessary to mass produce things like fish floss. The greater the volume he was able to sell, the more lucrative it would be. The capital and investment necessary was enormous, and the technique was not particularly sophisticated. After a few years it was sure to be imitated, so it was better to sell it off in one go.

“100,000 gold pieces?!” Xena bit her lip.

From her view, this price was on the high side. However if skilled craftsmen and the sealing technique were included, then it was much more worth it.

The crucial point was the sealing technique that Leylin used. Xena could immediately see the advantage in using the sealing jar to preserve food for a long time. Even if it wasn’t used for fish floss, it was enough for her to make a profit.

So what if this industry needed a lot of initial investment? For the church of wealth who threw money at all their problems, that would never become an issue.

“This price is really far too high, unless you include the technique used to refine white sugar as well…” Although she had already inwardly agreed to the deal, she had a forced smile on her face, and on the surface she looked like she was moments away from throwing a tantrum.

“The white sugar purification technique?” Leylin muttered to himself. This was a different technique to the fish floss, and he was secretive about it as there were several key steps to making it.

Additionally, it did not require a big production line or much investment, and it was a business that he could continue in the long-term.

The white sugar trade brought in over half of the Faulen Family’s income, and was like an inexhaustible gold mine! As their profits grew, naturally the number of sharks that were attracted by it also grew. This was something that Leylin understood very well.

“Well?” Xena clearly seemed to understand the difference between the two techniques, and her eyes flashed in anticipation.

“This is…” Leylin’s expression looked as if he was mired in difficulty, and his fingers began to involuntarily drum on the table. Xena’s heart seemed to also throb along to the rhythmic tapping sounds.

‘Why… Why did I do that?’ Xena’s face seemed to flush red as she inwardly chastised herself.

However, Leylin looked at her softly. “The purification technique for white sugar cannot be sold to you. However, can we discuss the matters of the church of wealth?”

“The church of wealth?”

“Yes! For example, how many priests you will dispatch here, how many paladins, and other matters like that…” Leylin smiled like a crafty fox, leaving Xena feeling as if she had met the most unreasonable devil in her career.

After a while, Xena bid farewell and left, looking as if she had been driven to distraction.

“I’ll need to carefully consider your proposal!” were the words she left behind.

As he watched many priests and paladins escorting the figure below him, Leylin’s lips slowly curved into a smile.

As a matter of fact, his proposal was not complicated. It was only to allow the church of wealth to become a partner in the business, and gradually pass on the technique over three years, enough time for the Faulens to fill their own coffers.

Leylin had additionally emphasised a clause in their agreement— If Faulen Island came under attack, the church of wealth would have to send out priests and paladins to fight alongside his guards.

This was practically a request for the church’s protection. Even if they only sent out a low-ranking priest, it would be enough. After all, even Marquis Louis would not dare to declare war on the church of wealth unless he was tired of living.

Leylin had also heard several rumors which made it necessary for him to protect his own lair. Binding the church of wealth to his chariot of war was undoubtedly the safest thing for him to do.

Naturally, he would not have unrealistic expectations of the church protecting the Scarlet Tigers as well. Even if Marquis Louis wanted a truce, Leylin was not willing to agree. Without enough enemies and flesh, how could he fulfil the Devilblood Dagger’s needs and quickly advance?

‘The clause is not too harsh, and I believe that in the end, this Gold Priest won’t be able to withstand the temptation…’ Leylin’s eyes continued to flash, ‘Once the church of wealth puts down their roots here, perhaps my plans can begin…’

After returning to his villa, Leylin waved his hand at Claire and her sister, who had faces full of anticipation, “I won’t need you here for now, leave first!”

“Y–yes, young master!” The sisters had a secretly bitter expression on their faces but did not dare to say much as they meekly left the room.

“Come out!” Leylin looked towards the window sill. For a moment, it seemed as if no one was there and the window was tightly shut, without even a small crack.

However, a shadow slowly emerged from the darkness, and the outline of a curvy body could be seen. The owner of this body was a half-drow, who wore the tight-fitting clothes of an assassin and a thief. “Master!” she immediately knelt down.

“I’m afraid that your stealth is no worse off than some middle-ranking assassins!” In the World of Gods, a middle-ranked class was a formidable Professional of over rank 10. Such an assessment coming from Leylin was indeed high praise. Perhaps this half-drow had practised like she was mad after shedding her past humiliating identity, and made great progress.

Karen currently had the heavy responsibility of communicating between Leylin and the Scarlet Tigers.

“Master, we looted two more merchant ships from the Baltic archipelago this month, the estimated profits are about 5000 gold pieces. Additionally, Miss Isabel has acted according to your plan and begun to intentionally leak our whereabouts…” Karen reported respectfully.

“What about the Barbarians?”

“I have already notified them and they have promised to act when the agreed time comes.” How could Leylin not take advantage of the assistance the Barbarians could offer to recklessly fight Marquis Louis?

“Mm, even so, we would increase our success rate if we could plant a high-ranking spy in their camp…” Leylin said, seemingly with a sigh.

“Master! This humble servant deserves death. The thieves and spies that were previously sent to the Baltic archipelago in the past all seemed to have been uprooted, and the ones that are left can only divulge ordinary information…” Karen immediately begged for forgiveness. Only after working for Leylin for so long did she realise how deeply terrifying he was.

Compared to this master, those pure-blooded drows in the Underdark seemed extremely kind-hearted!

“The reason I said that was not to blame you,” Leylin shook his head, thinking that his servant’s cowardice was not a good thing at all.

Chapter 844: Pirates’ Tide

“Go on! You were sent by William, weren’t you. What are you plotting?” Tim immediately sat down to one side.

“Haha… I’m afraid that your brother can’t order me around. If you want to confirm my identity, how about this?” Karen lifted her hand, and a scroll covered in the Scarlet Tiger’s skull and dagger seal flew directly to Tim.

“It really is you people…” Tim touched the unique imprint on the parchment in disbelief, his eyes slowly growing as round as saucers.

“What do you want?” Without quite knowing why, Tim’s heart began to beat wildly.

“Didn’t I say before? We’re going to help you become the marquis, my lord,” Karen smiled.

“What sort of joke is this, William is still here, and apart from him there’s still…” Tim mumbled.

“Then just let them all die,” Karen’s words were filled with venom.

“Let them all die!” Tim bonelessly flopped onto his chair as he heard her speak his mind, but his eyes actually shone brightly.

“You want me to work undercover and sell out my own family?” He asked slowly.

“That depends on your decision. What do you want, a broken family? Or the glory and power that your brother William currently holds?”

Karen could tell that Tim never really had a choice.

The night wind blew through the window, and the curtains continued to wave in the breeze. However, there was someone missing from their earlier position in front of the window. After a long time sitting uneasily in his chair, Tim felt dizzy and confused. However, an idea had seeded itself deep within his mind.

‘That’s right. If I can’t have it, you can’t either! I’ll destroy everything, this entire Baltic archipelago should belong to me!’Under the moonlight, Tim’s back seemed to have twisted demonically.

……

“Master, everything went smoothly. Tim also gave us the route maps of the Black Skeletons and Tigershark Pirates.” Tim had completely revealed Marquis Louis’ plan to them; the forces he was mobilising, William’s route, even the news of the wizard Boruj’s return.

“Ah, is this Tim crazy?” Isabel stood next to Leylin, looking at the final part of the parchment which held the map of the entire Baltic archipelago. He had completely betrayed his family and even given them the defenses of the marquis’ house.

“Desperate and crazy people can be unreasonable like this. He clearly knows that his family is the only thing left that he can rely on, but he willingly wants to destroy it. It’s really too funny…” Karen knelt down even lower, and did not dare to look Leylin in the eye.

Although she had a rather intimate relationship with this master of hers, she realised that she couldn’t even begin to understand Leylin yet. For the sake of benefits, even his enemies became his allies, and the ability to accurately grasp someone’s heart made him seem like a demon wearing human skin.

Indeed, a demon! In Karen’s heart, perhaps only the Archdevil of the 9th level of hell would have such a cold and cruel mentality.

“What, are you afraid of me?” Even this light thought was discovered by Leylin, and his casual way of asking made Karen tremble all over.

“No! No, your servant was just concerned that Viscount Tim would go back on his word. After all, nobles are not to be trusted. Even if we succeed, I fear that he will act as a witness against us…” Karen immediately replied.

“Before William dies, the likelihood of Tim going back to their side is very small,” Leylin did not get angry after discovering his servant’s fearful state of mind, it was a very normal reaction.

Only in front of the Scarlet Tigers did Leylin abandon his aristocratic airs, showing his true self to the crowd. Because of it, he had earned the other pirates’ genuine awe and fear. Were Isabel not slowly transforming into a demon in body and mind, perhaps even she would feel fearful and alienated by him.

“After we succeed, whether Tim will ask for help from the Dambrath Kingdom or testify against us…” Leylin laughed gently, “Did I let you leave behind any evidence or information that points towards me?”

“No,” Karen dimly began to realise.

“So from beginning to the end, this entire matter is only related to the Scarlet Tigers and Tim. Is Tim willing to gamble away his future and be hanged for the crime, just to testify against a bunch of pirates?”

“Master is wise!” Karen only understood at this moment how deeply Leylin had thought about everything.

“Not only that… Louis and William are the marquis and the marquis’ heir, even containing royal blood. The Baltic archipelago is the marquis’ fiefdom, do you really think we can go swaggering in after disposing of them both and take it over?”

“If that happened, the king would lose his mind and attack us!”

“That’s right, so we should at least support a puppet agent on the surface, and Tim is rather suitable, is he not?” Leylin folded his hands, “With him there, then we can cover up the whole matter as a fight between a noble family’s sons, and isn’t this sort of thing common in the Kingdom?

“This would let his majesty and the royal family save face, and although they will continue to resent us, the possibility of them wasting manpower and resources to exterminate us will be very low.”

“Your servant understands…” Karen’s face was still rather shocked as she respectfully withdrew. It was clear that Leylin’s view extended further into the future than she had realised.

‘Don’t tell me that all humans are as full of convoluted schemes and foresight as him? The extent of this plot, perhaps even those Matriarchs of the Underdark…’ Karen left with a heavy heart.

Leylin was comforting his cousin, “I know your family’s debt of blood includes Tim’s. Don’t worry, when the time is ripe he WILL pay the price…”

“There isn’t a trace of doubt in my mind,” Isabel looked deeply into Leylin’s eyes, “Additionally, I would like to finish him off myself…”

“No problem, I can leave William to you,” Leylin’s eyes flashed coldly, “Notify the Barbarians as well, this time we will eliminate their naval force in one fell swoop!”

A grey falcon with a scroll tied to its leg disappeared into the sky, as quickly as a flash of grey lightning. With this sort of raptor-like speed and flight, it would only take half a night to reach Pirates’ Cove.

A strong breeze flowed past, lifting the heavy curtains.

“What an adorable little fellow, haha…” Madam Tillen caressed its ash-grey beak, and retrieved the message tied to its feet. After glancing through the message, she turned to the Barbarians’ captain in her room, “The operation can begin!”

Several loud grunting sounds could be heard. An enormous hand attached to an arm the size of an entire baby was grasping a huge goblet filled to the brim with golden spirits.

Odge’s throat was gulping down the drink, and occasionally some liquor would leak out from the corners of his mouth and flow down his prickly beard.

“Boruj, Boruj, Boruj! I’ll turn your skull into a wine glass!” Odge growled, snatching up the enormous saber. A powerful spell glinted on the swordpoint.

“Send the order, we act now!” Odge roared, and the two barbarian warriors outside immediately flew out.

Pirates’ Cove immediately burst into a flurry of activity. Under the command of their captain, teams of barbarian warriors boarded their ships in an orderly manner, amongst them shamans who wore colourful feathers and had painted faces.

They were the rare spellcasters of the barbarian tribe, and one could tell Odge’s resolve and caution from how all of them had been dispatched.

“The Pirates’ Tide! It’s similar to the last Pirates’ Tide that happened decades ago…” The barbarian pirate crew did not consist solely of barbarians. As the head of the Dark Alliance in the outer seas, they had many pirates under them of other races which were all currently taking action with them. Several thousand ships sailed out from Pirates’ Cove, which gave off a rather chilling feeling.

“I smell killing, and the plot is afoot… This festival will please our lord greatly!” In a dark corner, the Cyric priest murmured to himself, next to him the bent figure of the bishop from before.

“Prepare your men to assassinate the leaders of both sides, and let the chaos grow even more turbulent!” After this reshuffling of the pirate organisations, the situation in the outer sea would change greatly. However, this bishop’s purpose was greater than that.

All he asked was for there to be chaos! After the chaotic battle, no matter who rose to the top, they would represent order. However, this would clearly displease the God of Murder, as he only wanted an endlessly chaotic outer sea, full of all kinds of murder and conspiracies.

Murder and plots were Cyric’s most favourite things. If they could accomplish this, then he was bound to receive the grace of his god. He would advance by 1 or 2 ranks as a priest at the very least, and even receive other advantages. Compared to that, how could allowing the entire outer sea wither even compare?

“As you command!” The priest now understood the tip of the bishop’s plot. Neither their past neutrality nor the current assassinations mattered, all that was left was a sacrifice of chaos and death!

These sorts of methods obviously brought great pleasure and excitement to him. With high spirits, the priest’s body slowly melded into the shadows, leaving behind the bishop who watched the sails alone.

Chapter 846: Barren Island

“Boss, why do we have to go against the Black Skeletons and Tigersharks? Marquis Louis and the Baltic archipelago are behind them, and we’re no match for THEM… Isn’t it better to stay out of the way like we did in the past? The sea is so vast. They can’t find us…” A pirate who looked kind stood out.

“Are you questioning my decision, Stalker?” Leylin’s voice was low, immediately causing the hall to turn chilly.

This was the disadvantage of staying at Port Venus and avoiding trouble. Since he controlled the pirates from the shadows most of the time, he still didn’t have enough of a grasp on them. This was especially true of those like Stalker who’d just joined. He’d originally commanded a few ships himself, and had never experienced how brutal and callous Leylin could be. There were things he did not understand.

Stalker froze, but still mumbled everything out anyway, “I obviously wouldn’t want to do that, but we have to worry about our brothers…”

“Wouldn’t want to? So that means you’ll still do it?” Leylin chuckled, a flash of lightning shooting out of his hands.

With his strength as a rank 9 wizard, plentiful battle experiences, and excellent techniques, taking care of a Professional merely about rank 10 could be done in an instant.

*Crackle!* Amidst the fierce electric currents, Stalker turned into a few portions of charred ash.

“Ah… Head!” “What are you doing?”

The trusted aide standing behind Stalker brought out his curved knife in his grief, but was immediately drowned out by Ronald’s underlings.

Leylin played with the electric currents that struck fear into the hearts of the pirates, leaving them trembling in their fright. He then ordered in leisure from his seat, “Ronald, go and take over their ship!”

“Understood, Captain!” Ronald immediately brought his men and left, leaving behind a group of pirate leaders quivering at their seats. It was only at this point that they remembered the Scarlet Tigers had been established with the captain’s ruthlessness and cruelty.

They had to carry out his orders with determination. The only other option was being purged callously!

Shouts could be heard, and there was some chaos in the distance but Leylin didn’t care. Sensing the wordless communication amongst his subordinates, He snickered inside, ‘As expected, the truly troublesome ones aren’t hot-blooded. There are more of those who only pay lip service…’

After a year of work, the batch of people under Leylin had all grown rich, gaining control over certain sections. They were now smalltime leaders themselves.

Due to a shortage of manpower, Isabel and Ronald had no choice but to hand over some power to others, which then led to a few other hidden leaders amongst the pirates. Leylin kept them under control by pressuring them with his power. While this made sure that they wouldn’t dare rebel, the hatred in their hearts increased by the day.

After the fools who had the guts to speak out all died, the only resistance was left hidden in the shadows. It was alright if they only paid lip service, but how many out of these people had contact with Marquis Louis and betrayed him, turning into spies?

Leylin sneered on the inside. On the surface, the opponent’s strength far exceeded his, even in terms of his noble status.

This was the loneliness at the top of the pyramid. Worldly matters were like water that would wash away the people beside him, the mere thought of like-minded companions from the past difficult to remember.

‘But even if you work from the shadows, you can’t stop me.’ Leylin was unfeeling and merciless.

“Captain! Stalker’s ship has been cleaned out!” At this moment, Ronald pushed the door open and walked in hurriedly, bloodstains still on his body. “We found some assassins from the church of murder on it, and this too!” A few noble emblems with blood on them were flung to the long table.

“This… It’s the family emblem of Marquis Louis!” Someone who recognised it yelled.

“Hang all the assassins. Kill all of Stalker’s assistants. Let them know what the punishment for treachery is!” Leylin instructed calmly, deciding the life and death of tens of people in an instant.

“Now, do you have any other opinions?” Being glanced at by Leylin’s lightning-like eyes, the many leaders immediately lowered their heads, having no courage to meet his gaze.

……

After the meeting was adjourned, Leylin might have used his might to forcefully allocate tasks, but the undercurrents still flowed. A few suspicious figures sneakily met up at the bottom of a ship’s hold in the deep night.

“Nondetection” An expensive scroll was torn, and once the rays of light from the spell filled the area, the people finally heaved a sigh of relief.

“Is this place safe?” One of them asked with a rough voice.

“I spend a lot of money to get this magic scroll. Even a high-ranked wizard might not be able to find us!” Another voice sounded exasperated.

“Fine, stop quarrelling!” An old and hoarse voice sounded, immediately suppressing the dispute, “I believe Liberty—”

“Didn’t I tell you not to call me by my name? Not even my nickname!” The voice from before sounded again immediately.

“Fine, sorry.” The elderly voice halted, and then continued, “There are now tens of ships. We have people keeping watch over the Scarlet Tiger, and there’s the power of magic involved. He definitely won’t discover us, so we can discuss at ease…”

“The captain’s been getting more ruthless lately. Stalker merely said a word and was killed by him just like that. Even his underlings weren’t spared…” A voice of indignance could be heard.

“Did he discover something?” This was the worried person.

“The reason us brothers are banding together is for our own benefits, but now the captain wants to go to war on those two huge pirate groups. Tell me, what are our chances of winning?”

The elderly voice replied, “Actually, if the captain’s still like before and lets us loot and plunder as we like, while he’s in charge of disposing of the stolen goods and distributing profits, I have no issues with that. The issue is that things are different now. He wants us to risk our lives! Even if we get rid of the Black Skeletons and Tigershark Pirates, they still have the Marquis and Baltic archipelago as their backing and can quickly regain their strength. What about us? On top of that, they have a tremendous slaving fleet…”

At the end of that, the elderly voice suddenly grew louder.

“Then what do we do?” The reason they had gathered was not because they truly had plans to start a rebellion, but were merely agreeing on an alliance in order to protect their own interests.

“We’re pirates. How valuable could trust be? If put in a spot, we can just rebel against him and side with the other pirate groups. Whether it’s Marquis Louis or the Barbarians, anything can be considered…” The aged voice held hints of resentment.

Eyes full of wit shone in the dark room like a pack of wolves.

……

“Reporting! Traces of the Scarlet Pirates have been found!” A pirate respectfully reported.

“Follow them, follow them! Keep a tight hold of them!” William’s eyes brightened.

The huge ships pulled at the sails, and they formed a huge arc in the strong wind. The entire fleet began to sail at a terrifying speed.

‘This is all thanks to master Boruj!’ Experiencing the strong winds in his face, William could not help but take a look at the high-ranked wizard next to him in admiration. The Breeze spell he’d cast had raised the fleet’s speed more than twofold.

Wizards could adapt to all sorts of complex environments. With the numerous types of spells they could cast, they were useful in all sorts of abrupt situations. In his opinion, the Scarlet Tigers would not be able to escape.

“An island has been discovered up ahead, and there are ships anchored there!” At this moment, the sailor at the observation deck exclaimed.

“What?” William immediately darted to the railings, using the telescope to observe. A huge barren island appeared in his line of sight. There was a series of pirate ships anchored at the side, the flag of the Scarlet Tigers extremely obvious on them.

“They’ve abandoned their ships and landed? Have they gone mad?” While still in disbelief, William gritted his teeth, “Go! Sink them!”

Whatever it was, he needed to sink the opponent’s ships. This way, they would be completely trapped. The offensive went smoothly. Not many had been left on watch, and Crowe and Citamo hadn’t even needed to act. Their first and second mates had taken along some people and seized the thirty pirate ships.

All the pirate ships that Leylin had spent a year seizing with his own pirate crew now fell into William’s hands. The process was so smooth-sailing that it was difficult to believe. The merfolk’s ship, and even the Scarlet Tiger with its blood red flag were at his disposal.

“His ships were all very clean and had no traps. Based on the information from the slaves, this is a temporary stopping point for them, and they’ve built a few simple defenses…”

Crowe fiddled with the black curved knife in his hands, “So? Should we sail them away?” Such a huge fleet was worth at least tens of thousands of hold, an impressive amount of wealth. Even large pirate groups would go green in envy at it.

William muttered to himself, and then gritted his teeth. “No. Sink them all! Even if they’ve done anything to the ships, it shouldn’t affect us.”

After all, there were a few terrifying toxins and curses that could be hidden from the senses of magic, and even divine force. He had come out to obtain a beautiful victory to secure his position as the successor. Nothing could go wrong.

“Master Boruj, what do you think?” William did not forget to ask for Boruj’s opinion at this point.

“Alright!” The wizard nodded, causing Crowe and Citamo to curse inside. As expected, wizards were all spendthrifts!

Chapter 849: Two-Legged Wyverns

“Is that the item you made a deal with the devil for?” Once everything was over, Isabel walked in slowly, eyes focused on the bloody knife in Leylin’s hand.

She’d known something was off about her cousin from the start, and that he was evidently hiding something. In addition, Leylin hadn’t tried to hide anything from her just now. Hence, Isabel knew that Leylin’s quick rise in strength definitely had to do with a devil. However, even if she found out, she had no plans to divulge it.

Part of it was because of their relationship from childhood. On the other hand, they were all in the same boat. Although demons and devils shared a completely antagonistic relationship and were two opposing forces, there weren’t many differences in terms of their followers.

Isabel was rather worried, because making deals with devils usually meant giving up one’s soul. On top of that, devils liked to use all sorts of plots in order to nibble away at the contractor’s soul, causing them to completely become depraved.

It could be said that for those who were experienced, devils were far worse than demons. Of course, due to devils keeping to their side of the deal even more strictly, there were even more believers praying to devils than demons in the World of Gods.

After seeing Isabel’s gaze, Leylin could tell what she was thinking.

“Don’t worry. I didn’t deal with my soul!” Leylin launched a fireball from his hands, burning the withered corpses on the ground to ashes. Though there was nothing much to hide from his cousin, it was still better to keep some things secret from his underlings.

“Be careful. The devils’ cunning is famous even in the vast multiverse.” Isabel went silent after the warning, her eyes now filled with some sort of determination. Once they were back to the camp, Ronald and Robin Hood, who had not been seen for a long time, welcomed them.

“My lord, the whole camp has been purged!” Robin Hood reported respectfully. It had originally seemed like he’d been demoted, and few paid attention to him. The truth was that he’d been hidden in the shadows, helping Leylin manage the true elites in his forces.

“Good! Let’s go to the fleet. Things should be lively there…” Leylin’s face lit up with a smile.

……

A while earlier. At the seaside, on the Black Skeletons’ ship.

A teleportation gate burst into existence, and Boruj and William stumbled out pathetically.

Without high-ranked Mage Armour, William had been affected despite having escaped quickly. A large portion of his handsome hair had already been burnt off, and it was now like a bird’s nest. There were burns all over his body.

“What’s going on? What’s that?” Terrifying explosions could be seen even on the shore. William grabbed onto the railings looking dazed, crying out maniacally. The feeling of having a brush with death left fear in his heart.

“It should be the explosions, but the power has increased by quite a bit! My men are going to be annihilated!” Boruj was completely fine, but his brows furrowed while looking doubtful, “Why didn’t I find anything? Is this some sort of new concealment technique, or the effects of a large-scaled spell formation?”

“Something’s off.” All of a sudden, Boruj’s expression changed, and a ring on his hand exploded, producing a powerful magic barrier.

Mage’s Sword! A magic sword appeared, colliding with a huge metallic flying hatchet. A huge crash could be heard in the air, the resulting undulations causing several huge pits to appear on the deck.

“An enemy! Who is it? Where’s Citamo? Show yourself!” William had noticed something was off too. The large explosion from before had attracted their attention, but he had not found anything strange in his surroundings.

It was far too quiet on the deck, and all the pirates who had stayed behind to guard it had disappeared.

“Are you looking for this?” A huge shark head was tossed to the ground. This was the head of a sharkman, and one that William was very familiar with.

Citamo looked to have suffered before death. The area under his neck still had blood dripping unceasingly, and it looked like his neck had been squeezed off him while he was alive.

A huge barbarian appeared in William’s line of sight, his footsteps thudding on the ship’s deck. He raised a huge saber, the bloody injuries on his body already healing quickly in demonstration of his astounding life force.

‘It’s Ogde, the captain of the Barbarians! He sneak attacked the guards who stayed behind!’ William immediately guessed at something.

“It turns out that Hygar Island was just a facade. You’d already left… Everything was a trap!” It would take two days to rush here from the battlefield, but if there was a batch of elites that had set off earlier, this would be easy to conceal from others.

William’s lips quirked bitterly. Most of his family’s power was destroyed, and he might even be in huge danger. This would also be a huge blow to his status.

‘Without our men coordinating with them, this plan would never have worked. Who was it?’ William roared inside.

“Be careful! I might not be able to protect you in a bit!” Boruj’s voice rang, causing William to look even more bitter.

“Hehe… Young master of the Baltic archipelago, we finally meet!” An alluring fox lady walked out from behind Ogde, with tens of barbarian warriors above rank 5 with her.

“What about those Tigersharks? Why did they come here so easily?” William was in denial that the whole Tigershark Pirates had been wiped out. After all, it was a large-scaled group comparable with the Black Skeletons, and even had a huge group of Tigersharks. In the seas, they would definitely be the king.

“You mean those little fish? I’m afraid they’ve sunk to the bottom of the sea. Someone provided Tears of Tigersharks to us, and the effects are pretty good!” Madam Tillen produced an exquisite crystal bottle and shook it, looking innocent and flirtatious like a little girl who had gotten a beloved toy.

William stared at her blankly, beginning to lose focus in his eyes.

“Be careful! This is a bewitching spell by a bloodline holder!”

Calm! A huge sound boomed by William’s ear, allowing him to regain his senses, no longer daring to take another look at the fox lady.

“Boruj, high-ranked wizard Boruj. I will chop off your head and use it as a wine cup!” The leader of the Barbarians huffed roughly, eyes turning red as if he had seen a foe.

As Marquis Louis’ leading wizard, Boruj had worked hard when expanding in the outer seas. The number of Barbarian Pirates who had died at his hand were innumerable, and the relationship between them was completely irreconciliable.

Ogde snarled, his saber emitting sparks that flew for a few meters. Looking nonchalant, he slashed at Boruj.

As the light burst out, even the deck that had been remodelled and covered with a layer of magic seemed to be plowed through by something ruthlessly, revealing huge ‘bruises’.

Boruj looked solemn and serious after witnessing the terrifying offence by the Barbarian, the spell slot in his memories breaking out.

Arcane Hand! A huge magical palm reached out, clashing with the blade to form a terrifying explosion.

Once the undulations had passed, the sharp saber light cut the huge palm into several fragments, its own radiance dimming. However, it still proceeded towards Boruj.

Boruj frowned and pointed towards the ground. “Wall of Iron!” A thick, metallic wall appeared, blocking the blade. Still, there were now terrifying streaks of injuries on him.

“This can’t go on!” Boruj watched the elite barbarian warriors surrounding him, especially with Tillen who could use magic and a few barbarian priests, already having thoughts of retreating.

With a shake of his sleeve, an intricate spell scroll fell to his hand. Gazing at it, a rare expression of heartache appeared, but he still tore at it.

*Bang!* A dark green mist spread above the deck, and the barbarian warriors who were affected immediately collapsed, bodies still twisting unconsciously.

“Be careful, this is a Death Cloud spell!” Madam Tillen’s voice sounded. Afterwards, a few roars could be heard from within the mist, bringing a horror with them.

*Roar!* A few huge dark green monsters pounced from the mist. They looked like giant lizards that had meaty wings on their backs. Their bodies were covered by a layer of scales and they spat out bundles of corrosive fluids.

High-grade Monster Summon! Just as these few two-legged wyverns began to trouble Ogde, another even more enormous two-legged wyvern spread its wings and flew away with two people in tow.

“Ah…” Seeing the two-legged wyvern agilely avoiding the long-distance attacks by the archers, Ogde thundered, breaking the neck of a wyvern in front of him.

“Master, why aren’t we teleporting away?” While on the expansive back of the two-legged wyvern, William grabbed onto a scale and made an enquiry.

“I only memorised one teleportation spell. After that, I’ll need to use scrolls…”

Boruj had a wry smile, “I’m not sure if the enemy will still chase us, so we need to conserve our strength!”

“Damn it! Damn it!” Thinking back to the failure this time, William’s facial muscles began to contort.

“That Leylin and the Barbarians! One day… one day… All the humiliation I have suffered will be returned to you!”

“I’m afraid you won’t get that opportunity!”

Chapter 852: Storm and Capture

Following the complete fall of Marquis Louis’ men at sea, remarkable changes immediately occurred to the situation offshore.

Leylin and the Barbarians originally had no choice but to ally in their fight against Marquis Louis’ oppression. However, with the Black Skeletons and Tigershark Pirates destroyed, that pressure had completely vanished with the sinking of the military fleet he’d painstakingly built. Now, a rivalry formed between the two crews.

As there was still a gigantic cash cow right in front of their eyes, the conflict between both sides certainly hadn’t escalated to a great extent. Still, it was already impossible to prevent future fights.

Leylin had long prepared for this.

“Set sail! Let’s go to the Baltic Harbour, straight into the base camp of that old fox!” Leylin’s order was accompanied by cheers from his pirates. They started up the Scarlet Tiger, which was like a gigantic creature of the sea as they headed towards the Baltic Archipelago.

……

*Thump! Shatter!* The sharp and clear sounds of glass and chinaware falling onto the ground could be heard, occasionally interspersed with bellows of rage.

The maids and subordinates in the marquis’ residence did not even dare to breathe heavily, fearful of becoming the target of his fury. Ever since news of William’s death had made its way here, Louis had sunken into a state of complete hysterial. Several servants had been dragged out and beaten to death, including a few personal female servants that Louis once favoured greatly.

Under such circumstances, it was understandable that the servants were being silent out of fear. For some reason, Tim was secretly very elated upon seeing the situation. He was even filled with the rejuvenating pleasure of someone having taken his revenge.

‘Has that damn William been completely fed to the fishes?’ Tim laughed maniacally inside, yet did not dare to show it. ‘If that old fellow knows about this intelligence report, will he get so angry that he’ll breathe his last?’

“Father! We have the latest news of our family’s fleet!” Tim’s voice was a mix of unease and apprehension, as though he was a criminal waiting to be executed.

“Come in!” Marquis Louis’ voice came from the within the room as he tried to repress his anger. Tim sneered secretly, and entered.

The marquis’ study was currently very messy. Shattered glass and porcelain shards were strewn across the floor. On the desk lay a dead body, totally void of life.

It was a young and beautiful female servant. Her eyes seemed to show a longing for survival, and her body was covered with traces of abuse, particularly the bruises on her neck, which were the main culprits that led to her death.

“Someone, tidy up this place!” Marquis Louis adjusted his shirt collar. With his order, an expressionless butler entered with a few maids, and they quickly cleared up the entire study room.

When the door closed, only Tim and Marquis Louis were left. Seeing that the marquis had seemingly regained peace after venting his anger, Tim suddenly felt a chill in his heart for some reason.

“Father…” Tim tried his best to make his voice appear more sorrowful.

“Speak… Have those bunch of morons been completely wiped out?” Marquis Louis sat on his soft armchair, his expression without a hint of grief or delight.

“Yes. Our family’s military fleet was besieged by the Scarlet Tigers and the Barbarians, and has confirmed to have been totally defeated near the Baltic archipelago.”

What Tim did not expect was that Marquis Louis’ expression did not change much after hearing such earth-shattering news, as though he had long predicted it.

“I know… After the Black Skeletons and Tigershark Pirates were destroyed, our family’s fleet walked down the same road as well? Heh heh… From today onwards, the Gold Thornblossoms’ authority over the Dambrath seas will be thoroughly destroyed…”

The marquis’ eyes seemed unusually bloodshot. It was the pain and insanity of having his life’s work ruined.

However, Tim actually felt more at ease after witnessing this. He would be assured only if the marquis was in such a state.

“Give instructions to prepare to leave this place!” Marquis Louis said to Tim.

“Leave? To where?” Tim seemed rather puzzled.

“Return to the mainland, the Dambrath capital. It’s no longer safe here with the great loss we’ve suffered in our strength. Those pirates will frantically pounce on us like starving dogs. We must leave as soon as possible while their mind is still on the other ports and wealth.”

Marquis Louis explained indifferently as he gazed at Tim with a gentle look in his eyes. “Tim, you’re now my only adult son. As long as we live, the kingdom will not let the Baltic archipelago have a change of ownership.”

The delayed trust made Tim feel as though there were two hot streams crashing into his eyes. He pouted, but said nothing in the end.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* Muffled cannon blasts sounded in the study, interspersed with the whistles of pirates. No matter how good the sound-proofing was, the noise could not be blocked out.

“What’s going on?” Marquis Louis ran to the window and opened it. The sounds became clearer, and he could see many clouds of black smoke. There were even silhouettes of hordes of pirates.

“How could they intrude so quickly? What about the fort and sentinel points that the team of guards had set up? Why aren’t they of any use? Could it be…”

Marquis Louis could finally smell conspiracy. Although he had lost his soul after his beloved son died in battle and after his maritime fleet was entirely wiped out, the marquis who had endured the test of battle immediately reacted at this critical juncture, but it was all too late.

He suddenly turned around, and immediately met with a pair of eyes resembling a wolf’s!

……

“Kill!” “Heh heh… Charge!”

Numerous pirates roared wildly. After destroying the battery and several guard assembly points, the other pirates spread themselves out like maniacs. They charged towards to the refined stores and enormous mansions like wild dogs.

Smashing sounds could be heard everywhere, and lone pirates with luxurious silk hung around their necks and their pockets stuffed with huge amounts of jewelry and gold coins could be seen scuttling across the streets from time to time.

Of course, there were bound to be massacres and death, and even little children could not run from their fate. Women were being disgraced in many dim corners, as they let out sorrowful cries.

Restraining the pirates like they were a military troop would be a joke. These pirates were excited by the tremendous amount of wealth here after they had abruptly broken into the place. They were like rats that had fallen into a rice vat, and had exposed the most despicable side of humanity.

In order to cause the greatest amount of wreckage, Leylin had even lowered his standards. He’d recruited a huge bunch of inferior pirate vassals, and brought them here. These were the scum of all scum, and they instantly displayed their powerful destructive abilities.

One could see that the entire harbour wouldn’t regain its popularity in the next few years after this ended.

On the largest battleship equipped with magical armor—the Scarlet Tiger— Leylin put down the telescope in his hands as he revealed a satisfied expression.

“Excellent. That’s right, kill them all, rob them all, burn them all! When we depart, all I need is to see a wasteland!” Leylin was now wearing a silver mask, and so was Isabel.

They were still noblemen after all, and naturally had to be mindful. Otherwise, they would meet with trouble in the kingdom if they left some magical image behind. Even though the mask covered his expression, Leylin was now like a respected devil of the underworld. His aura made other pirates retreat one by one, their faces filled with panic and fear.

The Baltic archipelago was the feudal land of the kingdom after all, and Leylin could not brazenly occupy this place openly. Thus, he wanted to completely destroy everything here, and turn this beautiful and wealthy archipelago into a purgatory. It would never be able to contest for the spot of an offshore trading centre with Faulen Island henceforth!

“You will see it!” Isabel’s eyes were rather bloodshot. Her aura once again began to rise sharply.

Such slaughter and chaos were evidently a demon’s favourite. If she was able to conduct a ritual before they pillaged the place, perhaps they would reap even greater profits.

But Leylin wouldn’t let her do that, of course. Once devils and demons were involved in something, it would definitely attract the attention of the church. He was still unable to contend against those colossal beings.

“Tim’s map of the port’s defences shows that there are still some forts, and also the residences of several people in authority and their strength. It can’t get any easier to raze this port to ruin.” A harbour was completely different with intel on it than without. Tim had an extremely high status, which was of huge benefit to Leylin as a spy.

At this moment, Robin Hood came forward to report to Leylin. “Boss! The troops stationed here have already been completely wiped out. Ronald is currently bringing our men to attack Marquis Louis’s mansion.” His body was covered with many bloodstains, and there were even pieces of meat and other items hanging from the blade of his sword.

“Marquis Louis must die here! The others don’t matter.”

Marquis Louis was an old fox after all. If he escaped, there might be other troubles that would ensue. Leylin wasn’t that idle to fool around with him.

“That Tim…” Robin Hood seemed like he wanted to say something but stopped himself.

“Depends on his luck. Marquis Louis has a few other children who are not of age yet anyway. We just need someone to succeed the Gold Thornblossom family, so that their feudal land will not be confiscated by the kingdom.”

Leylin waved his hands. “Come with me, there are even more important things to do!”

To Leylin, two places here were the most important sources of wealth. One was the official residence of the marquis, and the other was naturally where Boruj gathered the materials for his wizard tower.

Chapter 855: Emon City

Emon was a port city along the coast of the Dambrath Kingdom. It relied on the flourishing trade of the outer seas to develop, and at one point had over ten thousand free citizens making up its society. The lights never went out at night, and it created the image of prosperity.

However, the Pirates’ Tide in the outer seas, especially after the ransacking of the Baltic archipelago, stopped the sea trade for a while. Many small merchants had even committed suicide in the sea out of bankruptcy, leading to a further decline in prosperity.

This was all until one day, when a young man in grey robes came to the city gates.

“Entry fee is a copper coin!” As they had been standing guard here for a long time, the two guards had developed great insight. Noticing that this young man was not to be messed with, they did not create much trouble. After handing over the fee, the young man entered Emon City.

The city’s roads were desolate, with guards patrolling everywhere. Since this was a port on the sea, there was a theoretical chance of pirate attacks, and those timid aristocrats and nobles were scared stupid by the Pirates’ Tide, increasing the city’s security. Most of them had probably hidden themselves further inside the mainland by now.

“I’ll probably need to go the Mercenary Guild later!” After finding an inn, the young man slipped his hood off, revealing curly hair that was as dazzling as gold and a handsome face.

This was obviously Leylin. After taking care of all the matters and handing over all sorts of materials to Ernest, causing him to go giddy in his ecstacy and begin construction of a wizard’s tower, Leylin openly left Faulen Island, taking a ship to the continent.

Of course, this was in the name of travel and learning, something that was a matter of course for wizards. He currently held a recommendation letter from Ernest in his lap, something that would allow him to train in the capital’s Wizards’ Guild for a while.

Leylin had intended this trip for a while, there was nothing that Ernest could teach him anymore. And with Boruj’s bag of holding, he could now move about with more ease. 10 cubic metres of space was huge, and he could put his tent, rations, and essentials inside it, making things less difficult for him.

After getting on the coast, Leylin was like a drop of water that disappeared into the river of people. Things were rather sensitive right now, and he did not want to cause any trouble.

Travelling at this point was a very troublesome matter. If he lacked proof of free citizenship from the city hall or some other documents like that, he’d be treated like a runaway slave or indentured farmer. The rest of his life would be spent in jail or bankruptcy.

Of course, if he showed his proof of nobility, all cities would leave their doors wide open for him. But he wasn’t foolish enough to do that.

If he became a mercenary, he would be able to move about with no obstruction in most areas, though the guards would roll their eyes at him. Mercenaries who broke order were one of the most headache-inducing issues for security officials.

The Mercenary Guild was located by the Warriors’ Guild, one of their requirements was that one was a Professional.

Of course, this wasn’t too hard. If he trained for many years, could use a few weapons proficiently and had a certain amount of experience, he could easily be certified as a rank 1 fighter.

Leylin entered the Warriors’ Guild that was guarded by two burly warriors, in the distance seeing shrines to the gods of warriors and war. There were even a few resident priests in the guild, overseeing everything. They were in charge of healing injuries, even though it obviously came with a price.

Behind the Warriors’ Guild were a few bigshots. Without their support both on the surface and in the shadows, it would have had no chance to spread throughout the continent. Since warriors were the most common Professionals amongst the many races, becoming one did not require much talent.

“Is this Mister’s first time here?” After seeing Leylin’s entrance, a maid welcomed him while watching him with a strange look.

After all, most warriors were muscled, and it was rare to see people like Leylin.

“Yes. I would like to apply for the fighter test!” Though the Wizards’ Guild was more suitable for him, and being a wizard would gain him more respect, Leylin was here to stay out of trouble. He naturally wouldn’t do that. He was not even planning to use the recommendation letter Ernest had given him.

“Please come with me!” The maid brought Leylin to the second level of the guild. There were many little rings here, where warriors were fighting hand-to-hand or battling it out. While they were using wooden swords, people would still get injured.

At this moment, a priest that had been waiting at the side would be useful.

“Please register first. May I know which rank would you like to take the test for?”

As if afraid that Leylin did not understand well and because of his face, the maid explained to him enthusiastically, “Our tests here are conducted based on varying levels of strength. You’ll need to fight against a similarly-ranked or two lower-ranked opponents for a period of time to be able to pass the test, and there are often casualties…”

“Thank you for your good intentions. I’ll do what I can!” Leylin came to a counter and put in his particulars, filling up the form.

“Let’s see. Your name is Ley, you’re 18, and you want to take the test for a rank 5 warrior?” Sitting at the counter was a withered old man. He lifted his glasses and looked at Leylin, who was outside, “Young man, don’t try to push yourself too far. A rank 5 warrior can already use their qi, and some have even grasped battle techniques. You could maybe try rank 3…”

“What? You’re choosing the rank 5 test?” The maid looked astonished, her sharp voice causing surrounding people to gather around and watch.

“Why didn’t you listen to me?” The maid stamped her feet, pretty flushes appearing on her cheeks.

“I’ve already made up my mind, I’ll do this!” Leylin furrowed his brows. While he had lied about his age, this was still shocking.

Of course, it wasn’t that bad. It was much better than being a 16 year old rank 10 wizard, and he then nodded, “Please accept this application.”

“The application fee is 10 copper coins!” After Leylin paid up, the old man sighed helplessly, “Teenagers these days…”

“Interesting! I haven’t seen such an interesting kid for a long time! Let me be his opponent!” A forthright voice sounded out, and immediately after a burly man who was two heads taller than average pushed the crowd away as he walked over. His upper body was naked, the muscles solid like granite. There were several scabs from blades on his face, emanating red light that made him seem more menacing.

“It’s the Bone Shatterer, Fafnir. This guy’s in for it!”

“It’s rumoured that he’s a savage person who likes to pinch and shatter his opponent’s bones. Why’s he suddenly causing trouble for a kid?”

“It should be for a woman, right? He’s been interested in Nina for a long time!” This immediately caused the maid to blush beet red, “Fafnir, what are you doing?”

“Nothing much. I’m a rank 5 warrior anyway, so isn’t it normal for me to be an examiner? Am I wrong?” Fafnir watched Leylin, a malicious smile on his face.

“What about it?” He looked at the old man at the counter.

“You can give up on this test and come back tomorrow,” The old man sighed. He probably did not want to see a young man like Leylin having such a great setback.

Leylin was speechless inside. He hadn’t expected to meet such a vulgar person.

“It’s fine, he’ll do.” Wait till tomorrow? He didn’t have that much time to waste.

“I won’t worry about you anymore!” This nonchalant attitude resulted in Nina leaving while fuming in anger. Meanwhile, a crisp explosion could be heard produced from Fafnir’s hands.

“Kid, you’re dead meat. I want to pinch and shatter all the bones in your body bit by bit. Hope that you won’t hurt bad enough to call for your mother…” While brushing past him, Fafnir looked at Leylin and made a gesture as if slitting his throat.

“Don’t worry. Isn’t there a priest? I actually hope you brought enough money…” Leylin rolled his shoulders and picked up the long sword used for the testing.

As it was wooden, the handle was very light. However, there was a layer of metal on the blade that made it seem more durable.

The two slowly walked into the ring, and the judge then waved his right arm downwards. “Ready? Begin!”

“Destroy him, Bone Shatterer!”

“I’m supporting you, kid. Hang on!” The other bored warriors immediately began to jeer, and a few got the bets going, on how many moves Leylin could take from Fafnir.

Nina reappeared in the audience, watching the centre of the site anxiously.

“Kid, repent in hell!” Fafnir yelled as he charged.

This speed and technique was far from what Jacob had at the beginning, and Leylin could only shake his head inside. However, he did need to conceal his strength too, and he only dodged ‘by a hair’s breadth’, sword swinging onto his opponent’s shoulder.

“Stop wasting time! I’ve things to do!” A faint layer of qi emanated from Leylin’s body.

“It’s qi! This guy’s already activated qi!!” The onlookers exclaimed.

“This kid’s not bad!” Fafnir immediately began to get serious, and he wrapped himself up in these rays as well. An opponent who had already activated qi was not so easily defeated.

“Battle technique: Shatter Bones!” He accelerated, charging towards Leylin.

Chapter 859: Ashen Hawks

“It’s Lord Siegfried of the Ashen Hawks!”

“With him around, Old Pam’s at ease now!” The dwarf Pam exclaimed excitedly.

‘Powerful’ was Leylin’s first impression of the man. Siegfried was at or above rank 15, and there were even energy traces from magic items on his person. That wasn’t all; the members behind him were the cream of the crop as well, and Leylin even spotted a wizard among them.

While she was clad in black wizard robes, that unique spiritual temperament could not deceive Leylin. However, she did not seem to have a high rank and had only made contact with the third level of the Weave.

Seeing the mercenary group of the Ashen Hawks meet with the medium-scaled merchant groups, as well as the subsequent signal they set off, Leylin asked by Pam’s side, Is that Siegfried very powerful?”

“But of course. Lord Siegfried is the only mithril mercenary in Emon City! Mithril, you know? On top of that, he’s a high-ranked warrior who’s gone through numerous battles. Our city hall even invited him to take charge of the garrison, but he rejected them…” At the very mention of Siegfried, Old Pam talked non-stop, as if he himself was a member of the Ashen Hawks.

The Hawks had a huge reputation, and it resulted in an uproar amongst the large merchant groups. Be it the mercenaries or merchants, all of them had delighted looks on their face, as if just having them around meant their safety was guaranteed.

‘Yet another bunch of tragic people who place their safety in the hands of others…’ Seeing this, Leylin sighed inside, ‘No matter how powerful he is, he’ll definitely be protecting the few medium-sized merchant groups that hired him first and foremost. How could he stay by your side like Pam would? There are over a hundred ogres…’

While some were still immersed in their fantasies, the mixed bag of people set off.

‘How boring…’ Leylin was now dressed like a fighter, armoured in moderately new leather. At his waist was a longsword made of steel, the grip wound with coarse rope that allowed him to unsheath it smoothly at any time.

The large caravan moved very slowly. Apart from the leadership problems, food, water, and camping at night were huge issues for them. Even proper legions couldn’t manage such a thing well, forget this ragtag group. Sometimes they didn’t even make it past a few kilometres a day.

Leylin had already expected this, and he stayed in his group while at ease. With so many people present, he would only be used as cannon fodder to bait the ogres out if they ended up meeting. That would allow him to escape successfully.

He’d already made up his mind. Once he passed the danger of the ogres, he’d immediately leave this large group and proceed on his own. As for the matter of the commission and trust, would he even care?

Leylin thus had nothing going on for now. He’d made a deal with a merchant for one silver, and was allowed on one of the carriages. Besides his requisite patrolling duties, the only things he did were resting, meditation, and secret research.

‘A.I. Chip, show me my current stats!’ Leylin commanded.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 16. Race: Human, Rank 10 Wizard. Strength: 5.2. Agility: 6.5. Vitality: 6.3. Spirit: 10. Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite. Spell Slots: Rank 4(3), Rank 3(5), Rank 2(7), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)] [Analysis of the Weave: Level 0 100%, Level 1 100%, Level 2 37.31%, Level 3 16.78%, Level 4 2.01%.]

The A.I. Chip loyally carried out his orders.

‘My spiritual force is greatly disproportionate to the time I’ve spent meditating. With the reduced effect of the Devilblood Dagger, I can’t advance so easily anymore. I can only try to raise my other stats to 10 points…’

In Leylin’s view, raising of his other stats was a process of perfecting his own genes. Once they all broke past a certain limit, they could give him a pleasant surprise.

Leylin took a quick look at his stats and shifted his attention to the Weave’s analysis, his most important work.

‘Slow as ever…’ Leylin could do nothing about this. The Weave was under Mystra’s control, and she was a powerful goddess. The A.I. Chip analysing the Weave already went against the will of the gods. He couldn’t do much without alerting her.

‘The speed’s decreased after it started on level 2. It would be unnoticeable if not for my increase in rank… Perhaps I should use another method…’ Just as Leylin was pondering over what he should do, an unwelcome guest opened the door of the truck.

“Sister Hera has already explained everything to me. I’m sorry!” Just from the voice, Leylin could tell that this was Rafiniya and he opened his eyes. Even in the darkness of the truck, he could see her flushed face.

“I accept your apology. Are we done now?” Leylin gestured for her to leave.

“How can you do this?” Rafiniya’s embarrassed face reddened further, but this time in fury, “I’m here to apologise to you, yet you’re acting so rudely? Besides… Pam and the others are…”

“I’ve done my tasks for the day. Pam and the others are just unwilling to put in the effort… Also…” Leylin stood up. Just the natural elegance in his movements caused the knight to shrink backwards in retreat, as if she’d her own father in his fury.

“Also… who is it that keeps staying in the employer’s carriage? And who keeps evading patrol duty?” Leylin’s eyes rested on Rafiniya, causing the knight to lower her head. At this moment, she realised that this Ley indeed was doing his duty unlike her.

“That– That’s different! I’m a girl!” Rafiniya stomped her foot, “Who knew travelling was so tedious? There’s grime everywhere, and nowhere to even walk on. It’s even harder to find a washroom…”

Her subconscious thoughts were poured out in front of Leylin. Noticing his half-smile, she couldn’t help but go beet red and lower her head.

“So now you know the hardships of travelling? Don’t be fooled by the glamour of heroes on the surface. In truth, they could be suffering more than you… Go home, little lady!” Leylin rarely showed kindness such as this. He only did it because all it required was for him to speak a bit.

“You sound like you know a lot, but do you really?” Rafiniya turned and left, as if she had gotten used to and annoyed by these lectures. Leylin only sighed, “Rebellious children…”

The days passed, and the ragtag group got closer to the region rumoured to have ogres around. They hadn’t met trouble before this, their numbers enough to scare off vagrants and those with malicious intent. Within the group however, the bandit Professionals had bad luck. No matter where they went, they were watched vigilantly.

When it came time to camp, they did it on a flat field. Numerous mercenaries constructed lofty tents and lit bonfires. Hot water was then poured into pots; with the addition of their rations, some wild vegetables that a few older mercenaries found outside the camp, and jerky, it was cooked into a savoury stew.

Pam hugged his rum bottle while salivating at the pot, occasionally taking a drink.

“Everyone’s worked hard today!” Hera and Rafiniya got off the horse carriage, and the mercenaries of the Night Halls sat around the bonfire.

After spending some time together, Leylin now had another opinion regarding Hera. While she was a slight schemer, it was because of her living conditions. She did not regard herself to be much better than those mercenaries who were working hard.

With his experience, Leylin could naturally tell if she was sincere or putting on a front. Her younger sister seemed to be called Yalani, and was protected well by her sister. She spent most of her time on the carriage, and even Leylin had only seen her a few times before. That meant Hera was aware of the dangers outside.

After Hera brought the dinner that had just been made back to the carriage, Old Pam impatiently drank his rum and began to chatter on.

However, in the long chilly night, there was little to while the time away. Hence, the other members approved of it tacitly. Rafiniya especially seemed to have fun, and probably even took Old Pam’s stories to be true.

“Hello. May I know if this is Lady Hera’s carriage?” At this moment, a person in charge of one of the merchant groups walked over.

“What is it? Please tell me!” Rafiniya blocked the way. Days before, there were a few guys who were lusting over the beauty of the sisters. She’d kicked them out, but she was now on her huard.

The person in charge who had been rejected frowned, but then put on a smile, “Well, we’re reaching the dangerous regions where the ogres appear. Lord Siegfried told me to come inform everyone to remain vigilant at night. Remember to send people to patrol the area…”

Chapter 866: Coincidence

“I don’t care what you’re thinking right now. Give me that warhorse!” Leylin watched him, his eyes full of ridicule.

“He… hehe… I’m only borrowing it from Rafiniya. I was going to…” The archer had a forced smile on his face, but then his expression suddenly changed, “Look there!”

Without waiting for Leylin to turn, he raised his arms and shot three spring-loaded arrows towards Leylin’s face.

“Go!” After shooting those arrows, the archer did not even give Leylin another look. Instead, he whipped the horse he was mounted on, wanting to leave as soon as possible.

He could tell that Leylin had no injuries at all and was in a much better state than he was. To be able to break out of the encirclement of the ogres without injury meant that Leylin was not someone he could contend with at this point. Hence, the archer firmly chose to flee.

“A great decision, though it’s a pity that it’s pointless…” A magic missile flew from Leylin’s hands. With a strange trajectory, it sent the arrows flying, and without losing power struck the archer’s back.

*Pak!* The archer suddenly flew from the horse, a terrifying sunken wound on his back.

“You– You’re a wizard!” The archer struggled, eyes full of longing as he reached towards the skies fiercely with fingers like chicken claws. His body thrashed around wildly as if he was in the throes of death. Seconds later, he stopped moving.

Having lost its new master, Nick stopped galloping. The warhorse whinnied as it began to leisurely nibble at the grass on the side.

“I’m your master now.” Leylin moved forward and grabbed Nick’s reins, swinging onto its back without hesitation as he announced his ownership.

Nick had no objection whatsoever to his actions, as expected of a warhorse with no integrity. Or perhaps, it had a one-track mind and had no ability understand something so profound. As Leylin squeezed his thighs against the horse, the black warhorse immediately seemed to turn into a streak of lightning and began to speed ahead on the ground.

As a knight’s mount, it was obviously more spirited than other horses, and Leylin found it wonderful.

He wasn’t too far from their previous battlefield, and there was the occasional luck, or perhaps unfortunate, person who had escaped the ogres’ pursuit. Leylin chose to pay no attention to their cries for help.

Even if those merchants showed off their sparkling gold kronas, they meant nothing to him. After all, the added wealth of all these little merchants might not even be enough to make up the amount of gold krona that he used in a single experiment. Why would he bother with this?

However, after passing by a small forest, something unexpected happened. Nick, who had been tame all this while, suddenly went mad and dashed into the bushes.

“Why is it doing this? Don’t tell me…” While he could forcefully control the horse, Leylin only pulled at the reins for a bit and then gave up.

In his opinion, there was no harm in doing something if it was convenient for him, and he could even save his own party without putting in a lot of extra effort. He had no idea how effective his help would be, though.

After passing through the thick layer of black brambles, a desperate scene appeared in front of him.

A carriage that had lost its mount had collapsed to the side, whereat Hera and her sister were embracing each other and shivering. Numerous terrifying ogres surrounded them, eyes full of unconcealed greed.

Rafiniya was holding her sword with both hands, her armour full of holes. There were traces of ground flesh and blood on it, and it was clear she had experienced countless bitter battles.

The female knight now had a deep wound on her thigh, where one could even somewhat see the bones. This made the girl grit her teeth, crystalline tears appearing at the corners of her eyes. Despite it all, she maintained the determination on her face. Without her protection, Hera and her sister would long since have become rations for the ogres.

Putting two and two together, Leylin had a general idea of what had happened. After being separated in the streams of people, they had run wildly all over the place. With Rafiniya’s help, they took care of many enemies and had finally arrived here.

“However, if they chose this direction purposely instead if accidentally, Hera is more wise than I previously assumed…” The three ogres that were attacking them were normal warriors, and there were no shamans present. They may be huge threats to the heavily injured Rafiniya, but they were nothing at all to Leylin.

“Hey, beautiful ladies. Good morning!” Leylin seemed to arrive like an unexpected guest, leisurely greeting everyone as if he had coincidentally and naturally bumped into them on his afternoon stroll.

“Nick!” Rafiniya saw her black warhorse, eyes blazing, “And Ley! You darned thief! If not for my companion being stolen, how would I have…”

Leylin was completely immune to the words of this female knight. Upon hearing her words, he merely rolled his eyes, automatically tuning her out.

*Growl…* After seeing Leylin’s appearance, the few ogres with simple minds had no other thoughts as they pounced forward.

“My longsword was discarded just now. What a pity…” Leylin patted at his warhorse, and Nick was able to leap in a way it was unable to usually. It jumped over the ogre’s head and came to Rafiniya’s side.

“Give me that sword.” Rafiniya initially looked ready to refuse, but for some reason she felt a sense of terror as she looked at Leylin’s calm face. She obediently handed it over.

‘Strange… why did I…’ Before she had the time to ponder this, however, her little mouth opened in shock and amazement.

“Not bad!” Leylin shook the knight sword in his hands. As a high-ranked knight, Rafiniya’s equipment was all of a high grade. Whether it was her horse or her sword, they were much better than what he had before.

The glaring brilliance of qi burst forth from Leylin’s hands.

Battle technique: Qi Strengthening! Battle technique: Charge! Battle technique: Cross Slash!

Leylin’s figure instantly turned into a streak of black, and the longsword was enveloped in the luster of qi as he began his assault on the three barbaric beings.

Cross-shaped light-rays flashed ahead, and three malicious heads flew off. Even after the corpses of the giant ogres crumpled to the ground, Rafiniya still seemed to be in disbelief.

‘On top of being able to activate Qi, his advanced battle techniques and his proficient battle techniques are even better than my teacher’s…’ Rafiniya looked absent minded, not even able to catch her longsword properly when Leylin tossed it back.

The battle techniques Leylin had just shown were not inferior to the most powerful person she’d ever seen, and that was a high-ranked paladin!

“Thank you.” At this moment, Hera hugged her little sister as they stood up, eyes full of gratitude aimed at Leylin. If not for Rafiniya and Leylin, she and her sister would long since have turned into jerky for the ogres to stockpile. There was no way to even escape.

As for Leylin’s sudden ‘disappearance’, this lady rationally chose not to pursue this. Things were very dangerous now, and in a situation where Rafiniya was gravely injured, they were in need of Leylin’s protection. Leylin did not even need to harbour malicious intent. As long as he abandoned the three girls, they were in deep trouble.

She immediately spoke out, “Thank you Mister Ley. I’ll increase the commission once we reach the town, I’m sure it will satisfy you.”

She had especially lowered her own status while speaking, and Leylin nodded on the inside.

“Wait… If you’re going to talk about raising the commission, then poor Old Pam should have a part of it too!” At this moment, the carriage at the side completely fell apart, and a dwarf with a broken leg rolled out like a ball.

“Things were completely chaotic when we were surrounded. Thankfully, we had Rafiniya protecting us, and we also bumped into Mister Pam after that…” Hera smiled forcefully as she explained the situation to Leylin. He merely rolled his shoulders, speechless at the dwarf’s luck in keeping his life. Or perhaps, he was really blessed by the Goddess of Luck?

Leylin and the group set out immediately after some rest and reorganisation. This was still a danger zone, after all.

However, the horse carriage from before was now useless. Leylin had no choice but to modify the remains of the carriage to a handcart, allowing Hera, her sister and Rafiniya to squeeze together. They had to bring the dwarf Pam along as well. The warhorse, Nick, was regrettably demoted to a worn-out old horse, exerting all its strength to pull the cart forward slowly.

“You didn’t see it, but three ogres pounced towards Old Pam! Each of their mouths were as large as my head…” From atop the cart came Old Pam’s bragging with gusto. Rafiniya squeezed forward, looking at Leylin.

“When are you returning Nick to me?”

“Give me a ransom in exchange. Don’t forget, this warhorse is something I got from winning against the archer. This is a place is protected by the laws of the kingdom. If you want the horse, go look for the archer…”

Sitting atop Nick, Leylin spoke seriously. This was much like the thinking of a bandit.

“Damn it, that archer’s corpse should have already entered the stomachs of the ogres!” Rafiniya mumbled to herself, occasionally muttering words like ‘thief’. At the end, she unwillingly tossed a gold card at Leylin.

“These are all my savings. I have nothing more…”

“That’s not bad…” Taking a look at the numbers, Leylin then began to whistle contentedly, “Deal! It’s yours!”

Rafiniya then gloomily found out that she was unable to ride Nick due to her injuries. Everything seemed to stay the same as before.

Chapter 867: Gloomwood Castle

“Thank you, Ley!” Rafiniya’s voice sounded after a while.

The female knight was no fool. She knew that without Leylin, they really would have died at the hands of the ogres, disappearing into their mouths. She obviously didn’t want to die like that, and just the thought of it already left her in fear.

All those adventure books were scams! There were no romantic heroes and beautiful princesses. Rather, there were thieves and bandits, as well as ogres who ate people alive!

“So… Now that your fantasies have been destroyed, will you still continue adventuring?” Leylin asked in curiosity.

“Of course. This is my path as a knight!” The female knight’s voice was filled with resolution. “As long as I can endure, evil will be destroyed by my hands one day. With my work, the world will regain its beauty!”

“…” Leylin rolled his eyes speechlessly. This directionally-challenged moron seemed to show no signs of waking up to reality.

“What kind of expression is that?”

“No, I was just thinking that you’re very suited to becoming a paladin of the God of Justice. Really!”

……

Thankfully, the Goddess of Luck finally showed mercy on them, allowing their little group to leave the region where the ogres had wreaked havoc.

If not, once Leylin was surrounded by the ogres, he would probably abandon everyone and make a path for himself to escape. Besides him, everyone, including the warhorse Nick, would become rations and jerky for the ogres.

“Are they all confused because of the commander’s death?” On the way, he bumped into a few members of the merchant groups who had been separated, and even a few thieves and the like.

It was a pity for them that even Rafiniya had learnt to steel her resolve. The high-ranked female knight who had regained a portion of her strength did not need much energy to take care of these people.

All that had continued until this day, when a small city with a black wall appeared in front of Leylin.

“We’re here, this is Gloomwood Castle. After this place, we will reach the central plains of the Dambrath Kingdom, the territories there managed by people directly subordinate to the king.” After seeing this city, Rafiniya screamed in joy. Hera and Yalani smiled, looking as if a weight had been lifted from their shoulders.

They were only halfway through their long trip, but the exhaustion and terror was more than enough to leave them in fear.

“Halt! Stop the vehicle for an inspection!” At the city gate, Leylin’s group of strangely-dressed adventures were immediately stopped by the guards.

‘Oh? These soldiers seem pretty strong… And they’re Professionals who have seen blood already.’ Leylin saw Hera going up ahead to negotiate with them, his brows furrowing slightly. With his experience, he could obviously see that the guards were stronger than usual. They could even be people in charge of Professional groups, incomparable to the previous party.

He could sense tens of elite archers aiming their weapons at this area from the shadows, leaving him with a sense of danger.

‘To even give me a sense of danger… These archers should have equipment like the Spellslayer Arrow. How wealthy…’ Leylin shot a glance towards the top of the city wall discreetly, and then maintained a nonchalant face as he looked at Hera and the rest.

After checking the proof that they were mercenaries and nobles, the middle-aged soldier who seemed to be the leader headed over to them.

“Terrible events have occurred at Gloomwood Castle lately. Don’t stay long if you don’t have business here.”

“Thank you for kind intentions. Officer, is this about the ogres?” A hint of curiosity showed in Hera’s eyes.

“The ogres? They’re far from real devils…” The middle-aged soldier sneered, but did not elaborate. Only when he passed by Leylin and the other mercenaries did he warn them, “Don’t stir up trouble inside, or else…”

His threatening words immediately angered Rafiniya. Leylin and Old Pam, on the other hand, had met such situations before. They rolled their shoulders back in answer, though it was not obvious whether they truly took heed of the advice.

“Hmph…” The leader did not argue about this with Hera, looking disappointed. He waved his hand, “Go on!”

“The strength of this legion doesn’t lose out to the ogre tribes…” Leylin hung his head, eyes flickering with wit.

‘Seems like the kingdom’s power and soldiers are the true trump cards of the human race in the World of Gods. Those inferior mercenary groups can’t be compared at all…’ Leylin could finally see the aura of a nation’s soldiers, with as many sharp swords as there were trees in the forest and as many pikes as there were thorns in a bush. They might even have the support of wizards and priests. The mid-ranked officer just now had an aura very similar to a high-ranked warrior, and he had evidently gone through numerous battles. The aura of someone who had seen blood in battle was something most mercenaries could not match.

‘With how he spoke, something definitely happened here…’ The desolate streets and the tight security in the city left Leylin frowning.

“We plan to rest here for a while. We might also need to buy a carriage and recruit a few more mercenaries…” Hera said once they found an inn, looking tired as she spoke to Leylin and the rest.

“Mm, we do need a new carriage.” Rafiniya was obviously approved of this plan. They had finally made it to a human city with great difficulty, and she could not wait to get some good rest. For a lady of nobility, there was nothing harder to endure than filth and grime. It was a pity that there was no lack of these on the journey, especially for mercenaries. That the poor girl hadn’t already gone insane showed the resolve she’d gained from her knight training.

Pam approved of this well. He was already itching to exchange the ogre ears for the commission, as well as buy a new batch of rum.

“Alright, we’ll meet here three days from now.”

Leylin nodded without much care. He was now slightly curious about the events in Gloomwood Castle.

“Wait, Ley! Your friend is in need of your help! My injuries need healing from a priest…” When the time to part came, Old Pam grasped Leylin firmly, eyes gleaming with tears.

Looking at the state he was in, Leylin had no choice but to roll his shoulders back and bring Old Pam, with his broken leg, along. The dwarf worshipped the God of Warriors anyway, and the church wasn’t too far off from the Mercenary Guild.

“Divine spell— Cure Moderate Wounds!” Holy light shone from the priest’s hands at the church of warriors, and the injury on Pam’s thigh quickly recovered. A new layer of tender flesh grew out.

“The fee is 5 kronas!” The priest looked pious, but did not lower the fees at all. Most churches functioned by getting money for healing the wounds of their followers.

The gods needed money themselves to construct their extravagant churches. More importantly, they needed to lure in worshippers with more generous conditions. Old Pam, who was usually miserly, paid up happily and did not dare take advantage of this at all. Only after he left the church did he look regretful.

“If not for our employer wanting to leave in the next few days, Old Pam would rather look for a doctor or potioneer. Damn it, 5 kronas! How many bottles of rum would that get me… Oh, mighty God, Old Pam did not say that on purpose…”

Old Pam continued to mumble, “No! This should be included in the fees we get from our employer. You’ll back me up, right, Ley?”

Leylin pretended not to hear anything, walking to the entrance of the Mercenary Guild with the dwarf. Old Pam impatiently exchanged the ogre ears to make up for his losses, while Leylin went to the mission hall.

The hall was much smaller than the one in Emon City. A few mercenaries were seated there, and whether in terms of quality or quantity they seemed to be lacking.

This strange atmosphere was explained after Leylin looked at the mission board.

“High grade mission: Track down traces of devil followers. This mission is extremely dangerous. Please think over it carefully before choosing it.”

“High grade mission: Investigate the evil god ceremony in the home of Lord Wokdo.”

“High grade mission: Investigate cause of death of Baron Faylen.”

Numerous high grade missions were hung up in a row, looking marvellous. It was a pity that few mercenaries dared take them on.

‘Interesting. A devil?’ A smile rose about Leylin’s lips all of a sudden. As he recalled the unusual mobilisation of the troops, as well as the worried look on the mid-ranked officer’s face, everything grew clear.

Gloomwood Castle was in a strange state because of the activities of devil worshippers. These high-difficulty missions were usually left to the churches and nation’s troops. It was no wonder that the mercenaries were not interested.

However, them having no interest did not mean that Leylin was the same. He’d always been curious about hell and the devils in this world. Beelzebub’s memories had ensured that he knew as much about them as an Archduke, but theory and reality were two separate things.

‘Based on his memories, there are nine levels of hell here. Each have their own rulers governing them, as well as a few public regions… To be able to break through the restrictions of the dimension and arrive at the prime material world to spread belief… This is something that only a ruler of the same rank as him could accomplish…’

At his most powerful, the Sovereign King of Gluttony, Beelzebub, was as strong as a Magus who’d comprehended laws. At the very least, he was stronger than the lesser gods here.

It was no wonder then that the traces of devils had set the city on high alert.

The scene that the soul seed had projected at the beginning appeared before his eyes once again. ‘I wonder how that little guy Tiff is doing now? He received the power of the soul seed from my main body. If he managed to adapt to it, he should be rather strong now…’

Chapter 869: Act

Leylin looked at himself in the mirror, and was satisfied with his new appearance. He originally looked like a westerner in the World of Gods, with bright golden blonde hair and clear blue eyes. However, his locks were now dyed black, and his eyes were a rich dark with blood-red sclera. His new appearance Exuded a never-ending aura of evil.

“With this extent, I don’t think anyone will associate me with the young master of the Faulen Family.” Leylin wore a sinister looking silver mask over his face and disappeared into the darkness.

Obviously, a change in appearance wouldn’t be enough. Thus, when Leylin reappeared his whole body seemed to have undergone an even greater and more terrifying transformation. He looked as if he were someone wrapped in mysteries, sinister energy encircling his body with a charming trace of the power of laws.

Once all the brilliant energy had fused into his body, Leylin completely resembled a devil who had ascended from hell, and even the aura of his soul had changed. A sense of power and danger emanated from his body in waves, and the surrounding space seemed to fold in on itself, as if everything was being devoured.

This was divinity! Only a divine power could accomplish this! Leylin had now become a divine being who grasped some power in the domain of devouring!

‘This imitation isn’t bad at all.’ Leylin looked at his new self and nodded in approval. His understanding of the law of devouring had already reached a peak. Only after he acquired Beelzebub’s divine force and divinity could he advance to become a rank 7 Magus. In the World of Gods, this would be considered as having achieved godhood.

His understanding of the law would not disappear with reincarnation. Though it was tough to create and draw out divinity from nothing, it was still an effortless task for the A.I. Chip to imitate the aura and appearance of a divine being with the power of devouring.

‘I definitely cannot ascend to godhood solely in the domain of devouring. Even if I do that, I’m afraid I’ll be sent straight to hell. Even if I’m going to go there in the end, I can’t be thrown down so passively…’

There was also another advantage of being in his current form. Divine beings were practically immune to scrying spells, and Leylin, an otherworldly guest, was obviously immune too. It would be an absolute joke if anyone tried to gain more information on him through scrying.

“The show has begun,” Leylin turned his gaze to the bright moon before his silhouette suddenly blurred and disappeared into the darkness.

Most of Beelzebub’s truesoul and divinity had been devoured by Leylin, along with a hundred thousand years of his memories as a devil. Thus, all of his followers were nothing but tragic beings in front of Leylin.

Everything was stored in his A.I. Chip, included Beelzebub’s methods to communicate with them, or his habits and disposition and even the list of bishops and demons in different regions of the prime material plane.

Beelzebub’s followers were unable to hide from Leylin, and thus Leylin had already made his plans after strolling about the castle.

Leylin’s deified incarnation arrived in front of a vast building. Two guards there were loyally carrying out their responsibilities, making sure the entrance was secure.

‘Even security officers fell to the attacks, no wonder they could carry out the blood sacrifice of an entire city so brazenly…’ Leylin put both his hands behind his back and swaggered into the mansion.

The moment he stepped into the vicinity, he couldn’t help but take a deep breath at the aura of evil within. He would have been completely unable to sense the soul undulations so precisely without the divinity that his current body possessed. Evil forces continued to circulate in Leylin’s surroundings, making the glow of his imitated godhood even brighter. It seemed as if it was turning his pretense into reality.

‘Eye of the Divine!’ Through his imitated divine powers, Leylin was able to use something like magic to make himself invisible to the tight security. Once he passed through, he followed his instinct to a descending passageway behind a rock garden that was obviously concealed.

“The stench of human blood… and the aura of low-ranked devils…” Leylin sniffed, but did not plan on making his way further.

“Who’s that?” His movement had alerted a nearby watchman, but he deliberately lowered his voice, seeming like he didn’t want to blow the matter up.

But in the darkness, a handful of otherworldly beings have already felt their way towards Leylin, obviously with the intention of mounting a sneak attack. However, when he saw these creatures up close, he didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry at the sight of them. “Are these what you are relying on? Devil priests like these? Is this an insult?”

Through his night vision, he had already seen who his attacker was—an amalgamation of badly damaged human carcass parts and heads. It looked like a massive ball of flesh. This inferior devil was of the lowest grade, and it was also the most common cannon fodder in the ninth level of hell.

The A.I. chip sent over the creature’s data to him.

[Inferior devil. Strength: 3 Agility: 1 Vitality: 5 Spirit: 0.1 Description: This is a common magical creature found in hell, usually a reincarnation of deceitful humans. Its IQ equates to that of a retarded human, and it is easily controlled by high-ranked devils. Feats: 1. Fire Immunity, Poison Immunity. 2. Cold Resistance. 3. Acid Attack]

“Scram, you lowly ants!” Leylin said icily, using the language of the devils of hell.

Instantly, those poor devils were rendered completely defenceless under Leylin, someone who was as good as a near Archdevil. They immediately fell under his control.

The watchmen were left in shock, “W-Who are you exactly?”

“You aren’t qualified to know that.”

They did not dare to retaliate even as Leylin walked further in. Naturally, that was perhaps because they felt the intrinsic quality of a devil within him. Once he pushed through a door covered in fresh blood curses, a room that looked like a dining hall appeared in front of Leylin.

Fresh, steaming flesh was laid on the long dining table, and many worshippers raised their heads to look at Leylin who was an unwanted and unexpected guests. In their shock, they forgot to even wipe off the remnant blood from the side of their lips.

“What’s going on? Sybar, why did you let an outsider in?” The plump noble seated right in the centre sounded unhappy, and put on an resentful expression.

‘The bloody banquet. Isn’t this another one of Beelzebub’s favourite ceremonies?’ Leylin recognised the ceremony being conducted.

“All you maggots, can’t you tell?” Leylin’s voice was low but powerful, exploding with the dignity of divinity.

“This- This is the divine force of our Lord!” A devil priest yelped out of surprise, and the whole room suddenly followed him as they knelt down before Leylin.

“My Lord, you haven’t made contact with your followers for 20 years…” Tears filled the eyes of the priest.

“I have received the gift of our Lord and have become his Chosen and his substitute to lead you! Any objections?” Leylin announced bluntly.

Pretending to be Beelzebub’s Chosen and a divine being would allow Leylin to take control of all his followers as well as his priest network in the prime material world.

This was Leylin’s goal. He’d grown jealous of what was formed by a hundred thousand years of operations by an Archdevil. Moreover, he already had the Manderhawke Plate.

“None at all!” The priest was the first to surrender his loyalty to Leylin, dropping to his knees and kissing Leylin’s boots.

“Hold up, even if he has the favour of our Lord and and has gained divinity, what give him the rights to take control of us completely?” A royal raised up his opinion from the crowd, feeling like his interests were breached.

But he was silenced shortly after. A crimson blade was pinned into his throat in a split second, and the terrifying power of devouring had sucked him dry in no time.

Many took in sharp breaths and others cried out in surprise, “The Devilblood Dagger!”

“Any more objections?” The blade returned to Leylin’s hand as the carcass of the royal turned to ash, and in return Leylin gained the respectful gazes of almost everyone in the room. As Beelzebub’s worshippers, they definitely knew what the Devilblood Dagger could do.

One had to have sacrificed the flesh of more than ten thousand humans and high-ranked priests to receive such a terrifying weapon. One needed to prove their strength to complete the sacrificial ceremony and survive for so long, and the Devilblood Dagger confirmed Leylin’s.

“Great Lord, we pledge our loyalty to you!” Many followers chanted.

“Very well! Our Lord is currently injured and needs time to recover. My mission is to act on behalf of his conscient, and bring together all the churches in the prime material world to restore our Lord’s health with enough faith and followers.” Leylin said halfheartedly.

“I see…” Most of them had already guessed that Beelzebub was hurt, but at this point in time it was too late for them to turn their backs on Leylin.

“Now, I’ll give out the first mission. A team of paladins is heading towards us, I’ll need your help.” With his divinity, he was a Chosen of the church. He could sometimes even override the church head’s authority!

After confirming his identity, Leylin deployed every follower with specific roles and ordered them to stall those paladins. These people were no match for them, but they were proficient at plots to stall time, as well as scheming and intrigue.

Chapter 870: False God

“In addition, stop performing large-scale blood sacrifices. There’s no need for such obstructive activity before you hear further from me, especially something that’ll attract the attention of the churches,” Leylin reminded them again before leaving.

“Of course, Chosen of our Lord!” The devil priest answered without hesitation, not that he had any authority to go against Leylin’s words. Moreover, the reason for their enormous blood sacrifices was to attract Beelzebub’s attention. Now that he had already sent a substitute, there was no need for that anymore.

“Lord’s substitute, please grant us your name!” The aged devil priest plucked up his courage to ask right before Leylin left.

“My name?” Leylin smirked beneath his mask. “My name is Kukulkan!”

The power of faith essentially came from fear and obedience, respect and admiration, or from one’s soul force. Godhood originated from that as well. With a specific name, great power, and falsely assuming the identity of Beelzebub’s Chosen, he could win the reverence of these devil worshippers. He could even disseminate and spread Beelzebub’s faith before usurping everything.

However, this was the only mature organisation of Beelzebub’s that Leylin found somewhat acceptable. When he would build his own church in the future, these people would not be of much help. After all, Leylin would not want his own church to be a gathering point for devil worshippers.

The next step was to cancel certain blood sacrifices and evil rituals that violated his core values. This was the domain of a benevolent god, and also an essential step for a divine being to gain extensive approval in the prime material plane.

“Lord Kukulkan, we will do as you wish and prepare for the recovery of our Lord!” Leylin was startled from his reverie as he watched the devil followers shouting his name loudly. A special energy akin to soul force enveloped him within the zealous ambience.

The false divine power of devouring almost went out of control and wanted to swallow this energy to transform completely, but Leylin resisted it.

‘The power of faith?’ Leylin signed internally before disappearing into a private room.

“You heard the Lord’s orders!” The devil priest straightened his back and looked at all of the followers, especially directing his gaze at the nobles. Having lost the powers that the devil bestowed upon him, the arrival of this divine being allowed him to regain some confidence.

“Get the tasks done quickly so that we can welcome those paladins of the God of Justice!” There was no room for reconciliation between devil worshippers and paladins. If they met, it would be a fight to the death.

While one paladin was more than enough to slaughter an entire room of devil worshippers, strategy, allocation of manpower, and hidden actions would make things difficult for them.

“Of course!” A few of the nobles laughed sinisterly, the shadows they cast on the wall behind them looking like terrifying demons themselves.

……

‘I can’t believe I have to play to dress up as god and play the devil twice in a day…’ Leylin had currently arrived outside the city.

He looked around vigilantly. His appearance of a powerful divine being was but a pretense, and he himself was only a rank 10 wizard. Had the devil worshippers just now rebelled against him, he was not sure that he’d have been able to suppress them. However, as he’d borrowed the superior aura of a high-ranked devil, he was certain he wouldn’t lose out.

However, him pretending to be a divine being, on top of his possession of the Devilblood Dagger, was enough to scare the hell out of those followers. Moreover, those who had offered sacrifices to the devils already had shackles on their souls. If they did not wish to be tortured even after death, they had to act according to Leylin’s wishes.

‘Compared to dealing with those low-ranked followers, this needs more attention…’ Leylin pulled himself together with a slight sigh, and a thread of flames appeared on his figure, taking the shape of a flame-winged serpent. The small blaze lit up the Gloomwood, giving off a demonic feeling.

‘He’s here!’ Leylin turned quickly. A black spirit was running towards him so quickly that it couldn’t be followed by the naked eye.

‘Advanced Barrier!’ ‘Advanced Protection!’ ‘Advanced Invisibility!’ A few enormous spell barriers were erected, separating the area from the outside world completely.

‘A high-ranked Professional? No, he’s even stronger than Odge and Boruj, almost a Legend…’ Leylin inwardly assessed as the person he was thinking of arrived in front of him.

“Tiff!” Formidable divine power circulated around the area, making Leylin seem like a god as he called out to Tiff. At the same time, the aura of his original form also rolled off his body.

“You’re not my God, but you have his power!” Tiff was indeed standing in front of Leylin, but he did not look like his previous self. His hair was now greying at the temples, and his vigilant eyes glared unwaveringly at Leylin.

Leylin felt several different probing spells targeted at him immediately, and if not for the fact that he was the original body and had the A.I. Chip’s help in concealing his abilities, it would be have been difficult to deal with the fellow.

Brilliant divine power floated above Leylin’s hand as he stared Tiff in the eye, “So, do you still have any suspicions?”

“I wouldn’t dare! You are the favoured one of my Lord!” Tiff pressed his right hand to his chest as a form of respect and bowed, showing his acknowledgement of Leylin’s identity.

Strong beings like this were not easily subdued. Honestly, if Tiff were to make any moves, he would have found out that Leylin was only a pretentious false god. Once he figured that out, taking care of Leylin would be as easy as popping a bubble.

“Since you’ve summoned me, what can I help you with?” Tiff still looked suspicious about the whole situation.

“Our Lord has already defeated the Archdevil Beelzebub and I’ve received orders to take over everything Beelzebub has in the prime material plane!” He kept to the truth. Tiff was the one person Leylin trusted the most here, even if he seemed doubtful of everything right now.

Even if the boy decided to go against him, Leylin could use the power he’d formerly left with Tiff to make him turn back.

‘However, he was able to use the energy I left behind as a foundation to receive magical powers and become similar to a bloodline holder… Or should I say half-chose? He’s somewhat talented…’ Leylin seemed to have already seen beyond Tiff’s facade.

“You’ve defeated the Archdevil? The Sovereign King of Gluttony?” Tiff’s voice involuntarily cracked. He had obviously heard about this earth-shaking rumour. The loyalty of these worshippers, who’d already lost the magic abilities bestowed by the devil, had long been shaken. Some information had spread out.

Worshippers in the prime material plane were shallow. If Leylin had waited to make his move a couple of decades later, Beelzebub’s people would have almost completely disappeared. Thankfully, that was not the case.

“Mm. I’ll need your help, how much manpower do you have in the Dambrath Kingdom?” Leylin asked. Unless his background wasn’t optimal, a near-legend like Tiff would have a certain amount of influence.

“I’ve created an organisation with faith in our Lord. There are fewer than 300 followers right now, and the highest ranked among them is a Baron…” Tiff clenched his teeth, and told Leylin unwillingly. The familiar soul suppression was too strong on him, and he had no choice but to speak the truth.

‘An organisation in worship of me?’ Leylin was pretty taken aback. ‘To sustain a miniature organisation without the support of divine power… He has a lot of potential…’

The difference between true and false gods was that one could grant their priests divine spells and other powers, ranging in ranks from rank 1 to rank 9. With the great power separating their planes and the prime material plane, the highest rank of spell a powerful devil or demon could bestow upon their worshippers was rank 5. Anything past that would require a blood sacrifice to go through, or have some other such restriction. This type of worship of false gods would suffer a unanimous crackdown by the true gods.

Demigods were similar. Without enough power to grant high-ranked spells to their followers, they were not widely spread. The Feathered Snake God, Kukulkan, that Leylin had made up previously was an otherworldly demigod who was still in deep sleep! He would not be able to grant even a rank 1 spell.

Leylin felt a special respect for the fact that Tiff could still sustain worship for Kukulkan under conditions like these, to the extent of enticing a baron. While he’d have used his own methods for it, it was still rather amazing.

‘But I can’t let this situation continue for too long… I’ll soon have to give them some hope!’ Leylin decided. A god that was unable to respond to prayers and grant spells would be eliminated like Beelzebub sooner or later.

‘If his original form is still recovering from his injuries, it doesn’t make sense for me to confer divine spells in his stead!’ Leylin’s original form as a near rank 7 Magus was from another world after all, and the World Will of the World of Gods was hostile towards his power. Not to mention the amount of energy that would be consumed by crossing the crystal sphere shell. If he were to use his original form to bestow divine spells, he would quickly go bankrupt and even die.

‘The only way is to advance to become a Legend is the and condense my divine force. By doing that, I’ll have the most basic capability to respond to my followers.’ Leylin gritted his teeth.

“Devout follower of our Lord, Tiff! I have something for you to do. Let us meet at the capital city of the Dambrath Kingdom.”

Chapter 872: Contempt

“Ohoh… Fiancé? Hera, you actually brought your sister here to get married?” Rafiniya was the first to shout, her eyes seemingly full of stars, “Gallant adventurers protecting the beautiful princess, who has come to the imperial capital to meet her prince. There’s nothing more romantic than this…”

Pam and Leylin said their congratulations, making Yalani blush a little, but Leylin was rather flabbergasted. He had thought that this journey revolved around Hera, but who would have thought that the final lead was actually Yalani, the young lady who hadn’t even reached adulthood yet?

‘Plus, her elder sister is the one sending her off to get married? Such a tradition doesn’t seem to exist in the kingdom. Did something happen to their elders?’ Leylin could sense that something was not right.

Seeing the mercenaries make a racket in front of them, the two bodyguards standing at the gate of the mansion could no longer hold themselves back. “What are you doing? Don’t you know that this is the viscount’s residence?”

A bodyguard walked out. He was wearing a brand new set of armor, wiped so conscientiously that it was shining without a single speck of dust on it. He towered over Leylin and his company, his eyes filled with disdain.

The reputation mercenaries held in the imperial city was only slightly better than that of bandits and gangsters. They were never a synonym of law-abiding citizens, and the nobles even loathed having any sort of relation to them. It would be so embarrassing!

As for the fiancé and so on? The bodyguard sized up Hera and her sister, who were dressed plainly, and evidently chose not to believe them. Yalani tugged at the hem of her elder sister’s skirt, then turned to look at her own clothes. Her family wasn’t very well off to begin with, and they had encountered huge misfortune. After a long and arduous journey on foot, even their best clothing would look like beggars’ rags.

She and her sister now looked like unsophisticated girls from the countryside, entering the city for the first time.

The young lady lowered her head, and practically wanted to bury her head underground. “Young sir…”

Hera was flushed red, but could only pick herself up and negotiate. “I’m from Emon City…”

She simultaneously took out a small cloth bundle that she treasured. Peeling it open layer by layer, she revealed the medal of a noble family that was in good condition. Perhaps it was the effect of the badge; the bodyguard glanced at Hera before taking the badge in to inform others, even if he was still doubtful.

Leylin and his company waited in the wind for more than half an hour. Rafiniya had grown rather impatient by the time the entrance to the viscount’s mansion finally opened slowly. Someone who looked like a butler walked out, his face plastered with a professional smile.

“May I know who is the young miss from the Lanta family?” Hera inhaled deeply and walked forward, with a smile to please. “I’m Hera Lanta! She’s my sister, Yalani!”

This was their reality: they had no choice. She and her younger sister had no one to rely on in the imperial city, and they could only attach themselves to Yalani’s viscount fiancé if they wanted a good life. They couldn’t leave a bad impression on the butler whom he trusted as well.

“Respected young ladies, please follow me in. The viscount is waiting for you!” The butler bowed at the side.

“Also… They are the mercenaries I hired. I was able to make it safely to the imperial city all thanks to them…” Hera looked over at Leylin and the rest and explained herself.

“Mercenaries?!” Disdain was apparent in the butler’s eyes, and only Rafiniya, who was riding a warhorse, made him do a double take. “But the viscount only mentioned two ladies…”

“Hera, you guys head in first! We’ll just wait a while longer at most…” Leylin smiled as he said to Hera. He glanced at the scornful look in the butler’s eyes, and inwardly smiled to himself. ‘This expression… Does he treat Hera and her sister like poor relatives who came knocking because they ran out of money? Interesting, interesting!”

Leylin magnanimously forgave the butler’s offense because he was watching a show. He even pulled Rafiniya back, someone whose expression showed that she had a belly full of anger, leaving her with no one to vent it on. Leylin was laughing so hard to himself that his stomach was about to start cramping.

Hera sent him an appreciative look, then took her sister’s hand as she walked into the entrance.

“Ley, look at them! That expression!” Rafiniya’s hair was completely about to explode, like an enraged kitten. “Ahh… I can’t take it. At worst, I won’t take the commission this time…”

“You don’t have to take it if you don’t want to, but don’t drag the rest of us down…” Leylin’s sarcastic blows at the side met with Old Pam’s common sentiments. His eyes went watery. “Missy! You can’t let poor Old Pam leave without a salary…”

“You haven’t gotten your salary? Just the mere ogre ears we got on the way should be enough of a profit…” Rafiniya mumbled to herself, but her temper did not flare up.

In actual fact, Hera and her sister didn’t have many assets to begin with. The two announced that they would raise the commission on the way, but after half the journey their group was stunned; the amount of cash they had on them was not even enough to pay what they’d promised before!

Furthermore, they hadn’t paid half of the coachman’s commission and the fee for the carriage at the Gloomwood Castle!

Although Rafiniya didn’t give a hoot about that little sum of money, she couldn’t not care about the others. After hearing what Leylin and Old Pam said, she could only walk away while fuming. “Anyway, I won’t demand the money, you guys can split it among yourselves…”

“Oh, Rafiniya! You’re really the most kindhearted lady in the world!” The dwarf, Old Pam, immediately cheered. Even the coachman at the side revealed a smile. He had gained a deeper understanding about this strange team of mercenaries after spending time with them.

Rafiniya didn’t lack money at all, and neither did the mysterious Ley. The only remaining people who would split the money would be him and Old Pam. People of the lower class never once minded having an extra share, even if it was just a few copper coins.

*Clang!* The main door swung open once again. Yalani’s arm was hooked onto a young nobleman’s, while Hera and the butler were standing behind them.

“These the mercenaries you employed? There’s even a dwarf? I think joining a circus would be more suitable for it… Oh, right, have you seen the the Golden Dwarf Circus?” This youthful nobleman had a wan face and very dark eyebags, making him look like a person whose body had been wasted entirely on wine and women. He appeared very depressed, and completely disregarded Leylin and company, turning around to chat with Hera instead.

“Daniel, Rafiniya and Leylin are both extremely powerful Professionals…” Hera smiled cordially as she began to turn the nobleman’s attention to Leylin and the others. “I believe that they’ll be of help to you if you win them over…”

Although she had started to notice that Daniel was harbouring malicious intentions, Hera still tried as much as possible to indirectly make her point, even though this made Rafiniya shoot a resentful look at her. She was indeed trying her best to ‘help’ Leylin and the others from the bottom of her heart.

Rafiniya aside, the only way out for civilian Professionals was to wait upon a noble family. This way, if they did great service decades later, they might be able to receive their master’s favour, and obtain the position of an honorary knight or a lord.

With this, they would be able to seek a piece of territory and gain a hereditary title. From then on, they would have entered the ranks of the upper class. In actual fact, that was how Leylin’s grandfather started out, just that the person he had vowed his loyalty to was the king.

“Hm… You’re right!” Viscount Daniel couldn’t help but swallow a mouthful of saliva as he stared at Hera’s full bosom. As compared to his fiancée, who was still a young girl, her sister was evidently a much more mature woman. Of course, it would be perfect if he could have both of them.

Under the beauty’s pleading, Daniel finally looked at them in the eye reluctantly as he sized them up. “You are very lucky. I, Viscount Daniel, am willing to accept all of you as my followers. Kneel and swear an oath!

“And you! You can be my honorary knight, my personal one…” When his gaze fell on Rafiniya, Daniel’s eyes clearly got brighter, and his eyes lingered for a little longer on her slender thighs. His butler, however, was trying his best to bite his lips, and didn’t say anything.

He understood his young master’s character very well, and knew that he would absolutely turn a deaf ear to any advice. But how could he promise to take them in as followers so easily, especially when there was also a dwarf and a coachman in their party?

However, the young master would regret his decision after a few days at most, and give them a random position as a guard or a servant or something. They would be satisfied anyway.

Even if they were servants, people in the viscount’s mansion were a notch higher than average civilians! This was an established theory in the butler’s mindset.

“What? Aren’t you going to quickly thank the viscount for his grace?” Hera signalled at Leylin and the others with her eyes.

She thought that she had found the best way out for these mercenaries. After all, compared to living a life of brushes with death, what was so bad about being a nobleman’s subordinate?

It was an unavoidable fact that although she was sharp-witted, she had a rigid mind. Or perhaps this was the way nobles thought.

“Mighty master, I, Pollan, hereby swear that…” What exceeded her expectations was that Rafiniya, Leylin and even Old Pam did not move an inch, only the coachman leapt forward with bright eyes.

“We are extremely grateful for your kindness, distinguished viscount. Unfortunately, I do not have any intention to serve a noble family. We are here just to settle our commission…”

“You all…” Hera was flushed with anger. This was the first time she felt hateful towards Leylin. How dare he decline her good intentions? Did he not know that there was a world of difference between a noble and a civilian?

Even Rafiniya frowned at this move, not appreciative of Hera’s ‘kindness’. Now that she thought herself to be the mistress of the viscount’s mansion, Leylin’s actions instantly made her feel like her pride had been hurt.

Chapter 876: Black and White

Meribald was a 367 year old high-ranking wizard, although he preferred to be called a scholar. With the power of his magic, even at his age he was plenty vigorous, and had very supple skin as though he was a young man. Only his greying hair betrayed his age, but it seemed more like an accent to his wisdom and foresight.

He had served as president of the Wizards’ Guild in the Dambrath Imperial Capital for over a hundred years, and had handled innumerable major events. He had also awarded numerous medals to talented wizards, and judged notorious ones. By now, he’d begun to think his still and unfeeling heart would no longer receive any blows.

He hadn’t expected how stunned he would be today.

Meribald pushed his spectacles up, his finger brushing against the uneven imprints on the identification document. There was no problem with the magic imprint! That was what his abundance of experience was telling him, but he was horrified by what the results of his investigation meant.

“Proof of nobility! Wizard Ernest’s testimonial! And the final round of examination of the documents didn’t meet with any issues! In that case, this young noble, who is just sixteen years of age, is really a rank 10 wizard? In Azuth’s name…” Meribald’s jaw slowly dropped as he looked at the young man in front of him.

With such innate skill at his age… Meribald wondered whether he was about to witness the birth of the kingdom’s wizarding Legend.

“Excuse me, guild leader. Is there any problem?” The question raised by the young wizard across him shook Meribald from his reverie.

“Of… Of course not! Congratulations, wizard Leylin!” Meribald secretly sighed as he placed his magic imprint on the wizard ranking document. This document would be filed away as proof of Leylin’s identity as a wizard.

“From today onwards, you are a mid-ranked wizard as verified by the Wizards’ Guild! May Azuth bless you…” Although this was not the deity he believed in, Leylin still lowered his head respectfully to express his humility.

Meribald passed Leylin a wizard robe enhanced with a ‘Remove Dust’ spell and other coats of arms and documents. When conducting the ceremony, Meribald could see Leylin’s love of magic and the pursuit of truth in his eyes; this same look once existed in his eyes when he was younger!

‘Perhaps only such a person will truly have the ability to break through into the realm of Legends, and become a being that I can only dream of…’ Meribald gasped in admiration to himself, a warm hearted expression on his face. He kindly gave some advice to Leylin as well. “Wizard Leylin! Although you have already entered the ranks of a mid-level wizard, I suggest that you study in the imperial capital’s Wizards’ Guild for a while. A few of the latest philosophies and models in magic are present here, and will be very important for you right now.”

“That is precisely what I wish for, distinguished guild leader!” Leylin performed a wizard’s bow to the high-ranked wizard. His movements were unbelievably graceful.

‘I didn’t expect that things would get this troublesome. It seems like the talent I displayed made me quite outstanding. However, I can’t get the attention of the other guys without doing so…’ Leylin secretly gave a bitter laugh.

A sixteen-year-old rank 10 wizard! Such innate talent seemed rather horrifying. After verifying his rank, a few old fogeys immediately acted as though they had suffered a stroke, and even involved the guild leader.

Fortunately, he’d already earned his fame as a genius wizard. All of his improvements had been witnessed by Ernest, and it had saved him a lot of trouble. With regards to the Devilblood Dagger and other items that would easily be associated with evil, Leylin didn’t carry any of them with him.

‘Proof that I’m a rank 10 wizard. Even if I travel abroad, it’s enough for me to receive preferential treatment…; Leylin fiddled with the wizard insignia in his hand. It was decorated with a silver moon and stars, and there a sense of indistinct beauty to it. In addition, it was also bound to its wizard owner, and outsiders would absolutely be unable to make a counterfeit copy.

“Leylin Faulen!” A few men carrying the symbol of a high-level inspector stood at the door of the wizard guild. A team of guards crowded around Leylin, intercepting him.

Leylin even saw a few priests of the God of Justice among the team, watching him with judgeful stares.

‘They’re only here now? It’s a little late… Or are they afraid of the power of the wizard guild?’

“Is anything the matter?” Leylin asked the inspector in front of him with a smile.

“You are suspected of a crime in the open seas. I need you to assist in our investigations!” The inspector said expressionlessly.

Judges, public security officers, policemen and the like all advocated righteousness, and were the main source of followers for the God of Justice. Leylin wouldn’t be surprised if they had the backing of the church of the God of Justice or if they were tipped off by them.

“If I say no?” Leylin looked at him ridiculously.

“You do not have the authority to reject!” With a wave of the inspector’s hand, a few guards immediately closed in.

“You…” Leylin gaze was as harsh as lightning, and he raised his voice by a few notches.

“Don’t tell me you dare to apprehend an innocent nobleman in the imperial capital? And slander a noble mid-ranked wizard in front of the wizard guild at that!”

Noble! Wizard! Once these two upper-class identities were revealed, many guards immediately retreated in fear.

In their plain and simple thoughts, this was definitely a struggle between influential powers. Why should they take part? Aren’t they afraid of getting into trouble for being involved?

After witnessing this scene, the inspector knitted his brows. But before he could take his next course of action, the intense sound of a horse’s hooves could be heard.

“His Majesty decrees that Leylin Faulen will enter the palace and have an audience with the King!” An imperial knight dressed in a splendid suit of armor dismounted his steed and displayed a document to the inspector with the king’s royal seal stamped on it. “His Majesty wishes to convene a legislative hearing with regards to this, and has specially gathered Viscount Tim to testify…”

For some reason, Leylin’s peaceful state gave the inspector a bad feeling. However, he couldn’t stop this from happening, or he would be declaring war on the law that he had vowed his loyalty and devotion to.

“You know… Even when things seem black and white, there will always be infinitesimal shades of grey existing between them. Isn’t that right, Sir Inspector?” Leylin mounted the horse and taunted.

“Even with Viscount Tim bearing witness, His Majesty definitely will not let you off.” The inspector’s face changed drastically, but he eventually chose to have faith in the king.

“I’ll wait and see,” Leylin smiled lightly as he disappeared into the end of the road along with the knight.

“We’ll wait in front of the main entrance of the court. I don’t believe it…” The inspector bit his lip and waved his hand firmly. Evidently, the unease he felt had become stronger.

“What a pity… If Lorent and the others can reach in time…” The priest of the God of Justice sighed. “Even if that’s the case, the sinner must receive trial and punishment!”

……

The events that followed progressed like a stage play. Numerous people appeared on stage one by one like marionettes at Leylin’s fingertips, and evil got the last laugh.

With the victim, Viscount Tim, testifying personally, as well as the instigation by Marquise Louise, when her husband was asleep, Leylin didn’t even need to open his mouth to speak. When it came to such matters, taking part in them himself would lead to a loss. He had to maintain the reserved and cold attitude of a noble.

The inspector’s last trace of persistence was thoroughly smashed to smithereens with the king’s single statement.

‘With regards to the murder of the Gold Thornblossom Marquis in the open seas, our investigations have confirmed it to be a crime committed by the pirate crew called the Barbarians. I hereby order the arrest of the leaders of the aforementioned, namely Odge and Tillen…”

“Why? Why did it turn out like this?” The inspector knelt on the floor with tears in his eyes as he began to sob silently.

“Because this was a misunderstanding to begin with! In actual fact, I’m proud of how the kingdom has such a responsible and diligent inspector like you…” Leylin happened to walk out at this moment, and saluted elegantly to the inspector upon hearing him. He had the attitude of a person who was trying to put a stop to the enmity between them with a smile.

There were now two more titles to his name. One was his identity as an imperial wizard, and the other was as an honorary viscount. They weren’t of much use, but they had a nice ring to it. He had received them after entertaining the king.

Even though the king used to be brilliant when he was younger, he was clearly addicted to wine and women at present. As long as it didn’t involve his authority and prestige, the king wouldn’t have any reaction. Leylin had his methods of handling such an old fellow.

What made him happier was that after this statement was issued in writing, no one else would give him trouble about the pirates. He could also conveniently hinder the Barbarians. What wasn’t there to be happy about?

“Why…” Leylin smiled gracefully as he skillfully mingled with the circle of nobles in the imperial capital, and was even chatting cheerfully with Viscount Tim as if they were blood brothers. Seeing this, the inspector sunk completely into perplexity. At this moment, his faith was even in danger of being shattered.

“My child… Justice has always been lonely. The road of people persisting in justice is inevitably filled with thorns, but we believe that the ultimate victory will definitely belong to us!” The priest’s warm hand landed on the inspector’s shoulder, becoming his sole support.

‘The God of Justice? Hmph!’ Leylin’s expression didn’t change, but he sneered secretly to himself.

……

Outside the imperial capital, Lorent and company could finally see the city walls after a challenging trek.

“We finally made it. According to our intelligence reports, he’s in the city. He can’t run away this time!” Lorent’s face was filled with excitement, and also a little fury at the same time.

Previously in Gloomwood Castle, they had first been impeded by the matter regarding the devil worshippers. As compared to pirates, the movements of devil worshippers were obviously much more important. But after busying themselves with it, they discovered that it was a false alarm. Not only that, they had wasted a huge amount of time, and even let their original target get to the imperial capital!

Fortunately, with the church’s information network, he had nowhere else to run to now.

“Prepare to accept punishment, Leylin Faulen!” Although they hadn’t met, Lorente had already sketched an image of him in his heart: cunning, savage, and full of evil! This noble should have been burnt alive at the stake!

Chapter 878: Reversal

Leylin was rather satisfied with the current situation in the outer seas on the whole. Were external powers to take root there, extra variables would arise. Marquis Tim was someone he understood very well, so it was fine for him to be there.

Being fully aware of the Faulens’ abilities, Tim definitely wouldn’t stupidly declare war on his own initiative. In fact, Leylin believed that the powers he revealed during this operation were sufficient to intimidate him.

Given that Tim had already completely surrendered himself to him, Leylin didn’t mind letting Tim have a taste of success. After all, Tim was the most influential nobleman in the outer seas, and at the same time, he was a vassal of the royal family. It would be a good thing if Leylin could bind Tim to his chariot of war through a mutually beneficial alliance.

No matter how deep one’s hatred was, it would melt like ice and dissolve in the face of sudden huge profits. Moreover, there were only a few ‘misunderstandings’ between them. Still, although Tim had already expressed his will to pledge his allegiance to him, Leylin certainly wouldn’t put down his guard against him.

“Ooh…. No….”

“Boohoo… Sister… Daniel… Save me!”

A familiar voice could be heard from the room. The guards and maids in the area undoubtedly recognised Leylin, and roughly knew his relationship with their master. They even knew about the transfer of the estate, and thus could only stare blankly at him as they didn’t dare to stop him.

“Interesting! How should we play this game?” The corners of Leylin’s lips curled into a smile as he pondered over this. Shortly after, he suddenly pushed open the door that had been tightly shut.

“What’s going on? Tim, my friend? I think I hear an unusual voice!” Leylin scanned the room with a ‘puzzled’ expression. Daniel stood at the side, his face as red as an apple, while Tim’s pants were already half undone. The pair of beautiful sisters stood next to the office table, weeping.

“Oh, Leylin!” Tim greeted Leylin as if it wasn’t awkward at all, and gave Daniel an introduction at the same time. “He’s a court wizard, an honorable viscount. This is Sir Leylin. My closest friend!”

Tim then turned to Leylin and said, “This is Viscount Daniel!”

“Sir… Sir Leylin!” Daniel felt that Leylin looked rather familiar, but he had long forgotten the mercenaries from earlier, hence he still bowed calmly. Court wizard! Honorary viscount! Although these were empty titles, they also represented an exceptional amount of glory!

He could even be favoured by His Majesty, and Marquis Tim was also his good friend. Just these facts were enough to crush Daniel completely.

“Good day, Sir Daniel!” Leylin had a doubtful expression on his face as he gestured towards Hera and her sister, whose clothes were all over the place.

“Oh! This is a pair of sisters that Daniel sent over from a noble family. What do you think? If you like them, I can give them to you for a while…” Such occurrences were extremely common among nobles and were not worth paying attention to. Tim had evidently misunderstood Leylin’s gesture.

“Yes! Although I’ve popped the younger sister’s cherry, I didn’t touch the older one. She might even be the purest of all virgins…” Daniel was obviously an expert in this field as well.

It was just that from his supposed point of view, that statement seemed wrong. Perhaps he didn’t even intend to actually marry the younger sister, and was just toying with her, thus he could just offer her as a gift without the slightest bit of hesitation.

Hera gave up all hope upon realising this. However, when she saw Leylin once more, her expression suddenly changed drastically. “Ley? You’re Ley! Are you here to save us?”

“Ley?” Yalani was using the clothes on the floor to cover her chest as she sized up the noble who had hastily barged in. He really did look exactly like the mercenary from earlier, just that he now had the air of a noble.

“Ley… The mercenary?” At this point, Daniel had finally realised why Leylin looked so familiar. Wasn’t this Ley the mercenary who had escorted Hera and her sister to his doorstep previously?

It was just that this was a court wizard, an honorary viscount! Compared to a mercenary who was worth as much as mud, they were obviously on two different ends of society. Even Daniel couldn’t immediately see the connection between the two.

Hera felt as though her face was burning hot, and was ashamed to death. She quickly came to her senses.

To think that she thought she had magnanimously given Leylin a way out! Who would have thought this Ley was so secretive that even Marquis Tim, whom Daniel was trying to curry favour with, would be afraid of him?

All her previous actions were probably clownish in his eyes, right? No matter how much adversity they had met with earlier, Hera did not waver. Now, for some reason, streams of tears had begun to flow uncontrollably from her eyes.

“Erm… You guys know each other?” Tim scratched his head as he looked at the people around him, who seemed to be caught in an awkward situation.

“Yes. We met once on the way to the capital…” Leylin spoke very ambiguously. “Viscount Daniel is my friend as well. If there isn’t any other trouble…”

Since it was such a trivial matter, Tim did not particularly mind helping Leylin save face. “No problem. I agree to the matter you raised previously!” Tim said as he clapped Daniel’s shoulder, who immediately showed a joyful expression.

“Thank you so much! Thank you Marquis Tim, and Viscount Leylin! Thank you so much for your help…” Daniel was so emotional that he couldn’t even speak clearly, and could only incoherently express his gratitude towards Leylin and Tim.

‘Hehe… I heard that Yalani is Daniel’s fiancée! He actually even brought her here for this purpose, just to receive a tiny amount of benefits,’ Tim secretly viewed Daniel with disdain, but did not show it. What he was more interested in was the relationship between Leylin and the sisters.

What were women worth to him? If he couldn’t get these two, he could find others. However, if he could use the sisters to discover Leylin’s weak points or the people he held dear, that would be absolutely perfect.

Due to Leylin’s deliberate interruption, the situation that had been about to occur naturally couldn’t continue. Hera and Yalani swiftly rearranged their clothing. “Thank… Thank you…” Hera muttered as they brushed past him, her voice as low as a mosquito’s buzz.

“It’s nothing much.” Leylin looked at Hera, whose face was flushed, and Yalani, who was visibly silent. The corners of his lips suddenly curved into a strange smile. “If you feel like you can’t stay on in his place, perhaps you can look for Marquise Louise!”

“Marquise?” Hera obviously noticed the honorific.

“Yes.” Leylin had to forcefully hold back his urge to laugh. This woman had just crawled out of a trap, yet was about to fall into an even deeper abyss. “Oh, and Lady Delia as well. Go straight to them, I believe they’ll definitely help you.”

“Thank you! Thank you! Leylin, you’re really such a nice person!” Hera looked at Leylin, who was helping them ‘wholeheartedly’, then recalled her attitude towards them earlier. She started to sob so hard that it was silent.

Leylin watched as the sisters departed, and could even hear Yalani and Daniel screaming and quarreling not long after. Seeing this, Leylin’s smile grew wider.

‘My dear Delia! I found you a pair of vain souls, don’t let me down… What will they become with your exploitation? Pleasure devils? Or lust demons? I look forward to it…’

“Sorry for disturbing a happy occasion, Tim!” Leylin turned to Marquis Tim, who was next to him.

“No matter. It’s my pleasure to be of use to you, sir!” Seeing Leylin in this state, Tim suddenly felt a chill in his heart for some reason. Trying to pry into Leylin’s thoughts was really such a foolish decision.

……

Tim eventually left the capital and returned to his territory, the Baltic archipelago. However, with a handwritten letter of alliance from Leylin, Tim now had a little more confidence to continue surviving in the outer seas, and also develop new areas.

After Tim had left, the enormous and magnificent mansion now belonged entirely to Leylin. Tim was even smart enough to leave behind a huge sum of operating funds for Leylin to squander, which pleased him greatly.

With Ernest’s recommendation letter, Leylin successfully met another high-level wizard, Simell, and even obtained the authority to conduct experiments alone in Simell’s wizard tower.

Although the president of the Wizards’ Guild, Meribald, had made the same gesture of goodwill, Leylin eventually chose Simell after thoroughly considering the matter.

After all, given that he was the president of the Wizards’ Guild, choosing Meribald would bring about a lot of trouble, but with Simell, it would purely be a working relationship. Additionally, Master Simell had remarkable academic achievements in alchemy, which appealed greatly to Leylin.

Through his studies, he had gradually fused the alchemy techniques of the Magus World and this world into one, allowing him to regain his original ability as an alchemic Grandmaster.

After reading extensively through the Wizards’ Guild’s latest magic research and the library resources, Leylin’s understanding of magic continuously grew deeper.

Time ticked by, and two years passed within the blink of an eye. Winter had passed and spring had just begun. After the harshest season had passed, the giant trees in the garden were impatiently sprouting their tender buds, full of vitality.

In the study room of his mansion, Leylin was half reclined on his chair. His eyes were slightly shut as he connected to the A.I. Chip.

‘A.I. Chip! Display my current statistics.’ Leylin inwardly commanded.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 18. Race: Rank 10 Human Wizard. Strength: 8.1. Agility: 7.8. Vitality: 9.2. Spirit: 10. Condition: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Multitalented. Spell Slots: Rank 4(3), Rank 3(5), Rank 2(???), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)] [Progress of Weave analysis: Rank 0 Weave 100%. Rank 1 Weave 100%. Rank 2 Weave 100%. Rank 3 Weave 53.71%. Rank 4 Weave 31.99%.]

The A.I. Chip faithfully executed Leylin’s order, and displayed a row of data.

Chapter 883: Meeting

Leylin obviously would not let go of this city of magic. Dambrath didn’t have much information past that to get to the higher ranks, forget becoming a Legend. Furthermore, the A.I. Chip deduced from the ancient notebook Leylin had obtained that the inheritance of arcanists and Arcane Arts was likely to be found in the northern lands. Given all this, it was necessary for Leylin to go to Silverymoon City.

“While the journey took almost a year, it’s not as if I gained nothing…” Leylin smiled as he took a look at his stats.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 18. Race: Human, Rank 11 Wizard. Strength: 10. Agility: 10. Vitality: 10. Spirit: 11. Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body. Spell Slots: Rank 5(2), Rank 4(4), Rank 3(6), Rank 2(???), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)]

After obtaining a Perfect Body, Leylin sensed his body could adapt better to terrible environments. On top of that, his spirit seemed to have broken through some bottleneck. His rate of improvement had increased, as if there was a further boost to his own innate talent in wizardry.

Leylin had broken through to rank 11 after a year of meditation, even without the ability of the Devilblood Dagger. He could now cast rank 5 spells!

In the World of Gods, rank 3 wizards could cast rank 1 spells, rank 5s could cast rank 2 spells, rank 7s rank 3 spells and so on. A rank 11 wizard could cast rank 5 spells, and once one became a rank 15 wizard, they could cast rank 7 spells without backlash. That was when one became a high-ranked wizard.

High-grade professionals above rank 15 would get special treatment no matter where they went, and that was especially so for high-ranked wizards. With a large number of spells that affected groups, their destructive power surpassed that of those that relied purely on their physiques. This put them at the peak of power.

Were there no gods in this world, given that they could cast spells of priests, druids, and sorcerers would long since have named the World of Gods the World of Wizards.

Wizards held the balance of power in the World of Gods. The arcanists had even established a tremendous empire after the the twilight of the gods, but with the comeback of the gods they soon collapsed…

‘It’s because of the powerful abilities of high-ranked wizards that information on these spells are strictly regulated in all nations. The only place where things are less stringent is Silverymoon…’ Leylin thought inside.

This was so because they were extremely wealthy and also had the backing of Mystra, the Goddess of the Weave. They naturally had the means to do so.

‘It’s said that the master of Silverymoon City, the Chosen of the Weave Goddess who is rumoured to be her daughter, is a peerless beauty…’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘The secret rumours state that one can get the favour of the Goddess of the Weave by growing close to her, and it’s even possible to increase the number of low-ranked spell slots in one’s possession…’

This slight benefit was nothing to Leylin. Having analysed the first three levels of the Weave completely, he no longer needed these low-rank spell slots. Furthermore, if he were to get too close to the Goddess, his disguise could be noticed. That would be a true tragedy.

‘Come to think of it, the analysis has progressed more quickly ever since I hit rank 11. Level 3 is almost completely done.’ The higher the rank of a wizard, the further one could make contact with the Weave. The A.I. Chip could therefore analyse the Weave at a faster rate, which was something he had already tested before.

‘Given the resources Silverymoon can provide it won’t be difficult to become a high-ranked wizard, but I’ll need to get lucky to become a Legend. The Devilblood Dagger won’t help much either, there’s no point smelting another one…’

With stats below 5, the dagger’s boost remained obvious. Even from 5 to 10 points it would be found lacking, not to mention its weakness later. On top of that, it wasn’t logical to carry a devil’s item by one’s side for such a slight increase in stats.

After all, this was not a rural area like Dambrath. There were legendary wizards here, but on top of that there were the Chosen, who were personifications of the gods. Leylin had no confidence in facing them.

Since the dagger did not give him any obvious boost, Leylin was already prepared to stop using it even if it had not been destroyed, and perhaps hand it down to his underlings.

‘When it comes to raising strength quickly, there are quite a number of ways in Beelzebub’s memories. They can all help one reach the realm of Legend and above… It’s a pity that there’s either terrible repercussion or the contamination of devilish energy. It’s far too troublesome to deal with that. I guess it’s better to walk the path of a wizard step by step… It’ll be even better if I can get the inheritance from the arcanists…’

Just when Leylin was deep in thought, a shy voice sounded from his side, “May– May I know if you are a wizard apprentice heading towards Silverymoon City?”

It pulled Leylin out of his thoughts, and he eyed the three females behind him– No, the three little girls behind him. They had evidently heard about the sea having calmed down and come on deck.

The one who had spoken was the youngest of all. She had brown hair, and under her fair forehead were a pair of azure eyes. The slight smile on her lips easily gave one a favourable opinion of her.

Beside her were two female companions, one taller than the other. They seemed to be sisters, with similar faces and both wearing blue checkered skirts with little flowers at the edges.

Tiff glared at the girls who had interrupted his young master. Though he concealed his strength, his aura alone left the three girls feeling suffocated and terrified.

“I– I’m sorry, mister! I– I was just curious!” The girl in the middle grasped her skirt, looking on the verge of tears. Though they had housekeepers and nannies sent out by their family by the side, they had never faced an old man so stern that it was frightening.

“Stop it, Tiff. You’re scaring our friends!” Leylin saw the figure behind him and chuckled like the warmest spring wind. It melted away the terror.

“My apologies, young master!” Tiff took a step back, “And the three young ladies as well!”

“It’s alright…” The girl spoke more fluently now, “My name is Bessany, and the two sisters here are Ena and Isadora. We’re all looking to apprentice in Silverymoon… Are you the same, mister?”

‘Wizard apprentices…’ Apprentice wizards were below rank 3. They had talent in wizardry and could use magic, able to cast rank 0 spells. Leylin scanned the girls to see that they all had the spiritual undulations of wizards, and they’d all made contact with the first level of the Weave.

“My name is Leylin, and I’m a wizard!” Leylin smiled, hiding his rank. After all, there was no point in that.

“As expected!” Isadora spoke from beside Bessany, “Where are you from, Leylin? Why do I hear a southern accent from you?”

These girls were like excited little sparrows as they surrounded Leylin, asking a whole bunch of questions noisily.

Leylin smiled as he conversed with them. This was the sort of infectious power he had, able to instil a favourable impression in the hearts of weak existences. Of course, this could also be attributed to his training as a noble.

From his conversation with the three girls, Leylin quickly came to know of some basic information. Bessany and the sisters came from two little families in the north. They had tested with talent in wizardry, and their families had sent them to train in Silverymoon.

Bessany was good-natured and spoke the most enthusiastically. As for the sisters, Ena was not as carefree and bright as Isadora, seeming more shy.

“My family gave me 500 gold coins this time, and I’ll need to use it sparingly. Hopefully, I’ll be able to train under a middle-ranked wizard…” Bessany suddenly sighed, looking worried.

500 gold coins was obviously a huge amount that was enough for even a noble to live liberally for five years! However, this amount was far from enough for the development of wizards.

But what could be done? Bessany’s family was merely the smallest of noble families. The 500 gold coins themselves had required quite a bit of effort, and they’d had to sell some property to raise that much.

Still, it would all be worth it if a wizard arose from their ranks. At this thought, Bessany inwardly gritted her teeth.

“The registration fees for the poorest wizard academy in Silverymoon is already 100 gold coins. As for studying under a middle-ranked wizard? That’s basically impossible… Apprentices like us from small noble families can only help others with experiments or copy scrolls to earn money…” Isadora laughed wryly. Evidently, she had a better understanding of the training of wizards.

Leylin realised something. These wizards were probably sucking up to him so that they could become allies.

‘As expected of nobles, huh? After studying so much, they consider more than the average person. It’s a pity that most of it is useless…’ Leylin sighed.

He looked less than 20, and without the emblem that showed his wizard ranking it wasn’t surprising for him to be mistaken as an apprentice. If he really was a low-ranked wizard, he might have played along for a while, but he had no intentions of doing that— they were not at the same level!

Chapter 889: Life in Silverymoon

‘Even the ordinary soldiers feel the looming shadow of war?’ Leylin nodded expressionlessly as he reflected on the issue in his mind. He didn’t remain in the barracks upon their return, instead returning to the property he’d bought.

‘I’m done with yet another mission. The contribution points I earned should be enough for me to buy that information, right?’

The database for wizards in Silverymoon could not be accessed purely with money. There were specific requirements to get things, and high-grade information on spells required contribution points to access. This was part of why Leylin had entered the city guard.

At this thought, he couldn’t help but glance at his stats.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 20. Race: Human, Rank 12 wizard. Strength: 10. Agility: 10. Vitality: 10. Spiritual force: 12. Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body. Spell Slots: Rank 5(3), Rank 4(5), Rank 3(7), Rank 2(???), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)]

Silverymoon City was truly the birthplace of wizards in the northern lands. With ample resources and research material, Leylin was able to move up a rank just by diligently working towards it. With more information, the progress on analysis of the Weave had also advanced at lightning speed.

‘Analysis of level 3 of the Weave has already progressed to 99.99%. There’s just a little left…’ Leylin sighed as he entered the workroom.

“Good- Good morning, Mister Leylin!” Three wizard apprentices jumped up just like startled rabbits. Bessany looked a little flushed, and the sisters behind her were obviously trying to clean up the messy lab table.

“Welcome home, sir!” Bessany spoke in the end, having gathered her courage. A year of study had taught them how difficult it was to cross rank 10, which meant that this young noble in front of them had a lot of talent and status in the wizarding world.

“Mm,” Leylin nodded sternly, “I hired you at the price of ten gold kronas per month; you also have permission to use my workroom. You don’t have to feel embarrassed…”

While helping with Leylin’s work, these girls had also been attempting to train their alchemy. It was a pity that without guidance from their mentor, it was difficult for them to improve by a large extent even if they had an alchemy lab.

“Oh!” Just as Leylin’s voice sounded, Isadora cheered, “I knew Mister Leylin wasn’t a stingy person…”

“So… that’s how you thought of me in the past?” Leylin rubbed his nose, scaring Ena into dragging her sister to apologise with her. There were countless apprentices in Silverymoon City, and their chances of finding such a good job were meagre. If not for their coincidental meeting with Leylin, the three of them wouldn’t even have been able to get this position. Hence, Ena treasured her current job.

“Forget it… I was just joking!” Even if it was what he had said only in passing, the beautiful apprentices in front of him were already cowering in fear. Such was the power of a high status. This power originated from Leylin himself, and nobody could snatch it away from him.

Leylin waved his hand with waning interest, approaching the sales counter on one side and opening its magic lock.

“How have the sales of magic items been lately?” Leylin took out a black boxing glove from the locked counter. The dark hide on the surface had a chilly glint to it, and looked to conceal some sort of strength. Under the guard was an incomplete magic formation. A few parts of the circuit were obviously broken off.

“The two items we asked Hawke’s Bazaar to sell have already gone on the market. We have received a total of 8000 gold coins. Based on the contract, they will receive 10% of the profits and the funds have been remitted to your account at the Goddess of Wealth’s church, able to be withdrawn at any time… Also, a few other magic item shops and auctions have contacted me, saying they wish to obtain your masterpieces…” Bessany reported normally.

Leylin was a Grandmaster Alchemist in his previous life. Once he made sense of the rules of alchemy in this world and got a hold of Permanency, his magic items were rather good. Bessany was definitely envious of Leylin given that the items he made randomly sold for thousands of gold coins.

It was a pity that she was only qualified to take care of the sales records and statistics. Whether it was delivering magic items or transferring money, this was something Leylin personally took care of with the clients. There was no way for her to interfere.

Tempted by greed, humans could abruptly gain terrifying strength and not even twitch in the face of death. Knowing this well, Leylin obviously would not give her the chance to betray him.

‘It looks like Bessany is rather skilled at this type of work. There’s some value in nurturing her…’ Leylin thought to himself, placing the boxing glove on the table while putting on a device over his eyes which was similar to a magnifying glass.

A fine powder mixed with mithril floated down softly from Leylin’s fingertips. It emitting a shiny silver luster in the ink bottle it landed in, after which Leylin used a fountain pen and dabbed at the ink before beginning to draw on the magic formation.

Bessany and the sisters immediately held their breaths, watching his actions closely. Alchemy masters all had their unique techniques. Even in Silverymoon, it was rare for people to let others watch without reservations. The other alchemy apprentices would go crazy over this if they found out!

His movements as fluid as water, Leylin quickly finished drawing the last magic formation. A radiance then appeared on his hands. With the incantation done and energy provided, the magic formation began to radiate energy that enveloped the glove.

“Now!” Leylin’s eyes shone, and he unhesitatingly cast a rank 5 spell. The gorgeous, powerful lustre of Permanency caused the girls to look intoxicated. With it, the rays from the magic formation grew in strength, and then began to be hidden within the guard.

[Beep! Glove of Strength successfully created!]

A prompt sounded from the A.I. Chip, followed by the item’s stats.

[Item Name: Glove of Strength. Weight: 525g. Materials Used: Giant Skin, Limestone, Mithril. Effects: Able to increase user’s strength by 1 point (limited to those under 10 points). Description: This is a glove filled with strength, the love of all warriors and knights. The maker used a unique technique in creating it, giving this guard even more power!]

“Hm, not bad.” An item of this rank was something Bessany and the rest could not even hope for. For Leylin, however, it is was merely something to practice his skills on.

After soaking the fist guard in a solution from a glass bottle, he proceeded with the last adaptability procedures. Leylin then spoke to Ena, “Tell the people in the shop to come over and get the goods.”

“Understood, Mister!” Ena bowed respectfully and left the room.

“How is it? Did you understand?” Leylin glanced at Bessany, a teasing look in his eyes. As for Isadora, he completely ignored her.

“No! Sire’s techniques are even more profound than those of the elven masters…” Bessany unknowingly used honorifics. She obviously wanted to become Leylin’s official student, but it seemed like he had no intentions of taking her on whatsoever.

“Alchemy needs to be learnt systematically. It’s natural you can’t understand it for now…” Leylin looked at Bessany, seeing her thirst and determination towards magic. Out of the three, perhaps only she would be able to succeed.

“In that case… Are you willing to give up your pay every month and work for three hourglasses more everyday? This will be in exchange for half an hourglass’ worth of time every week being mentored on alchemy,” Leylin asked. Passing on knowledge in exchange for manual labour was common amongst high-grade wizards. There were even cases of female wizards giving up their bodies in exchange for tutoring.

“I am! Of course I am” Bessany immediately grew so ecstatic that she kept repeating her words. With her background, truly studying alchemy was but a dream. Besides Leylin, no master would be willing to take her in as a apprentice.

“Good! Come to my room after you get off work.” Leylin nodded and headed out of the shop.

He could not keep staying here to create more magic items. Since Bessany had interest and talent in this area, there was nothing bad about teaching her.

“Congratulations, Bessany!” Behind him, Isadora’s congratulations and Bessany’s tearful delight sounded out. A ruminating smile was left on Leylin’s lips.

Things that belonged to a devil were not so easily obtained!

……

At the heart of Silverymoon, in the Wizards’ Guild next to the palace. After passing through a series of stringent tests, Leylin came outside the wizards’ vault.

The tower genie’s robotic voice sounded, “Welcome, Lord Leylin Faulen. As a middle-ranked wizard with the army, you can view the content at the first three levels. Level four and above can be accessed through contribution points.”

The wizards’ vault was a small library, and inside a few old wizards were reading. Leylin did not bother them as he found a book he was in the middle of. He began to read ‘Exploring The Sixth Level Of The Weave.’

The A.I. Chip continued to work, recording everything he saw.

Chapter 894: Ambush

The roars and howling of beasts filled the vicinity, putting everyone on edge.

Lanshire laughed hysterically, “Hah! All of you will die with me! You can never beat those werecreatures! Every one of you will be torn apart and then swallowed; your souls will be caged in the depths of hell!”

After spitting out her malicious curse, Lanshire’s face flushed and fresh blood spurted out from her mouth. Her aura completely disappeared as she died.

“Ignore her! Listen to me, engage defensive formation.” Seeing that Aulen wasn’t in a good condition, Leylin took over command.

It was only now that he found out what exactly had happened directly from Ogg, and began to organise the troops. In reality, everything that happened tonight was within Leylin’s plan. Firstly, he found Aulen and told her that they may have a spy within their ranks to win her support, which allowed him to plant the trap.

And to make things easy for the possible attack, the brothers, Ogg and Otto were sent out to be on standby.

“There were high-ranked werecreatures, so many of them, I– I can’t be sure of the exact number, but my brother tried to protect me- He tried to protect me and-” Ogg’s eyes swelled red with tears and his facial muscles began to twitch.

“Heal!” A spell flew forth from Jinx’s hands, and swiftly cured most of Ogg’s severe wounds.

“I’m gonna kill those damned beast bastards!” He stood up and grabbed his enormous claw hammer without waiting for his wounds to recover completely.

“Were you the only one who managed to escape in the close combat team? It looks like I underestimated our enemies this time round.” Leylin looked slightly ashamed, but a light flashed deep within in his eyes.

Whether it was done intentionally or not, the capture and exposure of Lanshire’s identity as a spy and her death had dealt a huge blow to Aulen. Moreover, the troops led by Ogg and Otto were now left with casualties, and Otto had even died; Silverymoon City would have to compensate Otto’s family for that later on. Jinx was a priest and under heavy restriction, while Rafiniya was a new member and did not have enough experience.

The event seemed to have cleared quite a number of obstacles for him, but Leylin would never admit to that. He would probably say that it was a coincidence!

By then, the werecreatures were already directly outside the campsite, their mountainous shadows and the screams of the guards causing horror to tinge the atmosphere.

“Everyone stay close, we’re in trouble.” An Eternal Flame spell lit up Leylin’s palm, and he managed to repel a large amount of the fog. As the soldiers gathered together, he managed to see the werecreatures more clearly.

This was a humongous group with at least 200 of the monsters among them, six of which had exceptionally strong physiques and savage auras.

“High-ranked werecreatures, and there’s 6 of them!” Even the perturbed Aulen was now anxious. The werecreatures’ strength had greatly surpassed their expectations. If they were at all careless, their troop would be completely wiped out.

Suppressing her emotions, Aulen returned to her cool-headed self and sent out commands, “Defensive formation number 2!”

How could she not have realised that Lanshire had conspired with the werecreatures to kill everyone here?

“Lanshire, my friend. I’m sorry!” Aulen muttered to herself and drew out her elven sword, the shaft decorated in plant motifs. Its lustre suggested that it was an enchanted item.

*Boom! Boom!* Giant footsteps sounded out, and several giants that were at least ten metres tall emerged from the fog. They were like walking hills clothed in coppery skin.

“G-Giants! These werecreatures managed to tame giants!” Aulen’s hand trembled ever so slightly as she watched these human-like but also bizarre creatures, and some soldiers even yelped in despair.

“Giants? Those extraordinary creatures from the north?” Leylin massaged his temples in distress as data of the creatures was presented to him.

[Name Unknown. Race: Giant. Strength: 15. Agility: 6. Vitality: 13. Spirit: 2. Feats: 1. Strong 2. Regeneration 3. Armoured Skin. Description: A unique creature that only exists in the north. Cruel and fierce in temperament, unintelligent, easily tamed by other barbaric tribes.]

“Looking at this strength, they’re most certainly connected to the Blackblood tribe. They might even be a branch! Cassley obviously wanted us to die.” Aulen laughed bitterly.

“Prepare to break through! We can only evacuate as many as we can.” She now seemed to have lost heart.

“Elf from Silverymoon City, and other humans!” A shadow walked out from the group of werecreatures.

He was 2 metres tall, and had an appearance similar to that of a human. The difference was that he had unusual beastly patterns all over his face, and certain body parts of a beast.

He choked in disgust after sniffing in the direction of Leylin and the rest, “Damn Silverymoon City! That is a place of evil, it should be wiped clean!”

As followers of Malar, the werecreatures were naturally hostile towards the civilised beings of Silverymoon City and hated all who dwelled within it. The city guards were undoubtedly their first target.

“All of you will die here today! You are all too worthless to even be sacrificed to my Lord!” The werecreatures growled, and more petrifying shadows headed towards them.

Werecreatures had robust physiques and a staggering jumping ability. The temporary barriers by the side of the campsite posed no deterrence to them. *Roar!* The giants grunted and every step they took was like a miniature earthquake, flipping tents and crushing soldiers under their feet.

“Damn it! Leylin, protect me!” The elegance of an elf was long forgotten to Aulen as her eyes were red with anxiety and she pulled the elven bow from her back.

Greater Magic Weapon! Leylin’s expression became heavy as the lustre of a high-grade spell burst forth from his hand.

*Phew!* Silver arrows went off like shooting stars, the spell-filled arrowheads hitting the giants right in their eyes, their weakest points. The giants’ defences still couldn’t match high-grade spells, and this was aimed at their eyes.

The giants roared as their eyes cracked apart in a soft explosion, copious amount of shimmering liquid and blood dripping everywhere.

One pressed a palm against his injured eye as he went berserk, charging towards Aulen.

Grease! Spell rays enveloped the giants as Leylin took advantage of this moment. He wouldn’t be himself if he let go of the chance to target the giants’ weakness.

*Bang!* Magnificent lights shot out of his hands like fireworks, and the group of giants immediately went berserk. Even the werecreatures were unable to calm them down.

Everything was in a frenzy as they roared wildly and attacked everything in their vicinity, including a handful werecreatures who were shredded into pieces.

“It’s a high-grade spell attack! Get rid of that darned wizard, I’ll dispel it!” A werecreature clad in a priest robe stood out in the chaos. He, too, had strange decorative motifs and paint on his face.

“Kill!” Aulen made use of this chance and charged forwards with Rafiniya and the rest. The only way they could survive under a situation like this was to go all-in. The soldiers were well aware of this too as they plucked up their remaining courage, following Aulen’s lead and charging ahead.

*Roar!* The clash of the two opposing sides created a fierce orchestra of howls and clangs of steel meeting steel.

And yet everything was in vain. Aulen’s numbers started to dwindle, and they could not win no matter how great their fighting spirit was. The werecreatures were just too many.

“Go to hell!” Having been enhanced by magic, the sword in Aulen’s hand was brighter than ever. It could easily pierce through the defences of the werecreatures and cause unimaginable damage to their internal organs.

With it, Aulen severed the heads of 3 werecreatures in a flash and attracted the attention of their companion— a high-ranked werecreature.

“I admit you’re strong. But too bad; you’re still going to hell!” The werecreature priest suddenly towered over Aulen like a huge and tenacious mountain which she could not scale.

……

“I’m your opponent!”

Leylin had already cast Fly, and was blocking the priest from saving his companions.

“Mid-ranked wizard, you’re not worthy to become a sacrifice!” The werecreature said in pity, and looked into Leylin’s blood-lust-filled eyes as if looking at his prey. It caused Leylin to furrow his brow uneasily.

‘I can’t be sure what other abilities this rank 15 or higher priest has. Hopefully Tiff and the rest will make it here soon!’

But of course, Leylin had more than one plan. He was also confident of escaping. As a wizard, there were countless life-saving spells. A simple Fly could get him out of the scene in a matter of seconds as long as he wasn’t shot down. Rank 15 wizards would escape death even more easily with Teleport.

This priest in front of him would just be a headache.

Chapter 900: Helen

Devouring divine power like this was a very dangerous thing. Even if incomplete, even Legends couldn’t resist a divine conscient. If any idiot devoured the power of an existing god, he would either go crazy due to the huge conscient or get devoured by the divine force instead and become an incarnation of that god.

Yet Leylin was different. His original body was equivalent to a demigod to begin with, and he had the conscient and memories of his host body. He wasn’t the least bit afraid of this incomplete conscient.

*Hiss!* An unnerving phantom of a winged snake emerged from Leylin’s soul, glaring at the disabled monkey in front of it. Even if it was only a conscient, the monkey screeched in fright. The monkey screeched out of fright despite that it only being a conscient.

*Boom!* The Targaryen looked at the monkey with disdain before swallowing it whole. Leylin’s body trembled involuntarily as the A.I. Chip made a report:

[Beep! Unknown energy absorbed by host body! Determined to be divine essence, near high-grade. Spirit increasing…]

[Beep! Energy fully absorbed by host body, Spirit+1.]

Leylin’s spirit force increased to a stunning 13 after devouring Malar’s divinity. His spirit was raised substantially, and he could make contact with more of the Weave.

Meanwhile, the A.I. Chip was still giving him feedback.

[Host body’s spirit stat has reached 13, host has advanced to rank 13 as a wizard.]

[Host has received one rank 6 spell slot, one rank 5 spell slot, and one rank 4 spell slot!]

‘Did I finally break through?’ Leylin looked at his updated stats.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 20. Race: Human, Rank 13 Wizard. Strength: 10. Agility: 10 Physique: 10. Spirit force: 13. Condition: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body. Spell Slots: Rank 6(2), Rank 5(4), Rank 4(6), Rank 3(???), Rank 2(???), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)]

[Weave Analysis Progress: Level 0: 100%. Level 1: 100%. Level 2: 100%. Level 3: 100%. Level 4: 56.77%. Level 5: 12.15%. Level 6: 0.01%.]

“A 20 year old rank 13 Wizard. I reckon there aren’t many like me in Silverymoon City. I’m almost on par with a Chosen now, though I guess I did advance with the grace of a god…” Leylin had fully digested Malar’s energy, and whilst the god himself realised that he’d lost some of his divinity he had no idea why.

‘Well, it seems like I’ll be entering an eternal feud with the God of the Hunt now.’ Even if he hadn’t devoured Malar’s divine force, Leylin would have made an enemy of the god’s church anyway. He had killed too many of his werecreature followers.

‘I’ll have to face a god sooner or later anyway. The God of the Hunt? Interesting domain.’ Leylin smirked.

…..

“My Lord.” Tiff, who was waiting outside the altar, was aware that Leylin had changed. However, he didn’t point it out. “We’ve detained and imprisoned a group of captives according to your orders and… I found something in the cell at the core of the campsite.”

“Oh? Bring me there to have a look.” Adrenaline rushed through Leylin as he came to a securely sealed cell with Tiff.

“I’m the only one who’s entered the place. I thought it would be better for few people to know about this.” Tiff bowed before positioning himself beside the door like a loyal guard.

‘Can it be…’ Leylin had a few guesses in his heart, but he was still hesitant as he pushed the door.

*Clang!* The thick and heavy door bellowed.

The light inside was dim, and it was covered in the distinct runes of the werecreatures that gave off a barbaric aura. Leylin could tell that it was a high-grade anti-demon spell formation to block off contact with elemental energy and the Weave.

It evidently a trap, and the person within the cell moved suddenly and raised their head.

“You– You’re not a werecreature!” They mumbled, so softly that Leylin could barely hear.

*Cling clang!* The chains scraped against each other as this prisoner moved, and Leylin noticed the unique cuffs on their hands. “Antimagic cuffs? Looks like they were really wary of you.”

Leylin sized the captive up—they were humanoid, but looked like a half-elf. Beneath their long viridescent locks were a pair of pure obsidian eyes and translucent fair skin. Their aura was distinct in spite of the long imprisonment.

A faint energy was emitted from their body, but restricted by the antimagic cuffs on their hands. It was clear that this captive was a wizard.

“A female half-elf wizard? Tell me, why did the werecreatures imprison you?” Leylin asked.

“I heard screaming and slashing just now. Have you eliminated all of them?” The female wizard raised her head and shot Leylin a glance with her unreadable eyes.

“Hm, I guess you can say that!” Leylin nodded in agreement.

“Then aren’t you going to release me?” She waved her cuffs in question.

“Nope. Law says you’re now my captive, unless you have something of value to exchange for your freedom.” Leylin shook his head. “Besides, you’re a half-elf wizard, you should know your value.”

This was the standard practice in the mainland, but things were different in Silverymoon. The city’s leader was good, and if she heard of the situation she might even have redeemed the half-elf with her own money. But Leylin didn’t plan on reporting it.

“Redemption? Hah, I guess you came because of ‘that’ too. Ignorant idiot. You don’t know the suffering it will bring you.” The female wizard laughed, her eyes brimming with complicated emotions. Leylin saw a brief moment of regret.

“Are you talking about the inheritance of the arcanists near the Nether Mountains and red dragon territory?” Leylin was sick of beating about the bush. And as expected, the moment he mentioned the Nether Mountains, red dragon, and arcanists, her expression changed. “So you knew.”

“Actually, I know more than what you think I do.” Leylin looked at her robe which was evidently different from the regular robes of other wizards and snapped his fingers.

A scorching light struck between her hands and melted the antimagic cuffs. Boiling molten iron dripped to the floor and sizzled, producing white fumes in its wake. But the female wizard had better things to pay attention to, as she stared at Leylin unbelievingly, “Instant cast? It can’t be! You- You are an arcanist!”

“An arcanist? I’ve yet to become one, I just have a few incomplete arcane spell models, just like you.” Leylin smiled at her.

The use of arcane spells was obviously different from that of normal spells. The biggest difference was that one didn’t need the help of the Weave to use them, instead using the elemental particles in the air.

Leylin had made these plans long ago, but the A.I. Chip was busy with the Weave. Still, he’d managed to build a few arcane spell models in his leisure. The scorching ray that he casted just now was one of them.

Given his abilities, it wasn’t impossible for Leylin to completely reconstruct the arcanists given enough time. Still, it could take tens of millennia. The transformation of normal spells into arcane spell models would be enough to keep him busy.

When there were ready-made ones, why would he continue to make them himself? Leylin’s real interest lay in the research of those arcanists and the inheritance from those Magi who had comprehended laws.

There was more than one Magus who comprehended laws in the final war, and countless rank 8s who were similar to the Mother Core. An understanding of their paths and laws would be extremely beneficial to Leylin. Being a localisation of Magi, arcanists must have received the teachings of the ancient Magi. It was quite possible that they possessed information in those fields.

‘Observing the different paths of law will be a great benefit. Though the ultimate path of every Magus is definitely different, it can at least give me a general direction.’ Leylin looked at the female wizard as multiple thoughts ran through his head.

On the other hand, she let down her guard after seeing Leylin cast that spell. Her expression loosened up, and a sense of pity and reliance overcame her. It was as if she had found her own kind.

*Bam!* A ball of green elemental particles started burning on the tips of her fingers, and she made a bizarre gesture, looking cautious.

“In the eyes of the Arcanic Fire, I will comply with the path of truth and abandon confusion, weakness and suffering. I will succeed the path of the arcanist. The light of Netheril will never be dimmed. My name is Helen. May I know who you are, my Lord?”

Helen looked over to Leylin after the ritual with expectation.

“Is that how ancient arcanists greet each other? I’m sorry, but I really don’t know how to do this.” Leylin spread his hands out and laughed helplessly, “Honestly, I’m just an ordinary wizard who got some fragments of arcanist inheritance.”

After a round of confusing explanation and using the arcanist notebook as proof, Leylin finally proved his identity. Helen’s own origins gradually grew clear before his eyes.

Chapter 901: Pretense

The half-elf in front of Leylin was called Helen Carter. She claimed to be a survivor of the ancient arcanist empire who dabbled in the arcane arts.

The inheritance of her family had been badly damaged by the oppression of the churches. She was actually a rank 11 wizard, and other than Arcane Fire which she used to prove her identity, she knew no other arcane spell models. If things were put in perspective, she was weaker than Leylin.

As for her motive in going north, she’d found something akin to the inheritance of an ancient arcanist in her old family tome. She was hoping she could find something there to revive her bloodline.

“Even with this world’s strict prohibition of them, arcanists still exist?” Leylin touched his chin. As a matter of fact, this was a very good thing. It meant that even if he managed to become an arcanist in the future, he wouldn’t have to work too hard to conceal his identity.

“Yes. Even with the disapproval of the churches, any wizard that has reached the rank of Legend will have to set foot into the essential step of Weaveless Casting. The Netheril empire didn’t leave their inheritance in a single place. Even though most were destroyed in war, some people have managed to luck across remnants of it.”

Helen tucked a few strands of hair neatly behind her jade-like ear. Her beauty was really on another level.

“That being said, Legends still have to do their research on arcane spells in secret, and once non-legendary wizards are found to be affiliated with any form of arcane spells, they’re absolutely done for.” Helen laughed bitterly as she spoke about it, as if she was was reminded of something she didn’t want to be.

It seems like she and her family had endured their fair share of suffering at the hands of the gods and their churches.

“In any case, thank you for saving me from the werecreatures. I can tell you everything my family knows about the arcanist inheritance in return.” Helen told Leylin sincerely.

That was a wise choice. Even if she rebelled, Leylin would have his own methods of achieving what he wanted, such as spells like Memory Retrieval. Helen wasn’t a match for him. Additionally, she recognised that Leylin was someone related to the arcane arts anyway. That alone had led to her lowering her guard against him.

“Thank you. When I find the documents and information I’ll make a copy for you.” Leylin didn’t reject her offer. He certainly thought that he deserved it all, “Before I discover any remnants of the arcanists, I’ll need you to move within range of my detection, is that okay?”

“Yes, that will be alright!” A consequence like this was already a whole lot better than being imprisoned by the werecreatures, where she might eventually become a sacrifice. Helen readily agreed to Leylin’s request without any negotiation, she was aware that her life was in his hands now.

“My Lord!” Tiff showed no signs of surprise when he saw Leylin bringing Helen out of the room.

“Right, this is Miss Helen. You can consider her our client.” Leylin said ambiguously. Helen wasn’t pleased about how she was being introduced but she chose to not voice it out.

“We’ve cleared the entire campsite. The high-ranked werecreature and tens of normal ones that we’ve knocked out have been put aside.” Tiff resembled a hard working housekeeper, reporting everything to his owner.

“There’s enough food for 200 people here, and enough weapons to equip an elite combat squad. I also found some half-done high-grade magic potions and other magic items in the leader’s room. They’re all very strong, probably intended to kill the dragon.”

“Got it, take away all the weapons and armour and leave half of the food.” Leylin kept the high-grade ingredients that Tiff handed him. These materials were valuable even outside their use for killing dragons.

“Bring me all the captives, I have some use for them!”

Things got simpler after he saw the people who participated in the battle and helped transform their bloodlines. He then asked Tiff to bring Helen along and lead the rest to bring the supplies away before changing his appearance back to how he looked before.

“Why took you so long?” Rafiniya’s grumble could be heard the moment Leylin returned to the campsite, “If you were a little more late, I will already be on my way to find you!”

“Something cropped up, gather everyone now and prepare for attack!” Leylin was flushed with excitement.

“Why?” Rafiniya mumbled to herself but the rest of the men had very quickly assembled themselves.

“I recced the area just now, and I found that the werecreatures’ campsite was completely transformed.” Leylin sounded ecstatic.

“There were attacked and a few of their leaders died. If we go there now, we will be able to wipe them out completely and uproot them! We can finish this damned mission!”

All the eyes of the soldiers’ lit up upon hearing Leylin’s words.

……

Alec opened his eyes, and that wizard’s face surfaced in his mind once more.

“Damn it! My head- Ugh-” Alec stood up with much difficulty and saw his almost-destroyed campsite and collapsed captives. Looking at the few survivors between the corpses, even if he wasn’t that intelligent, he knew that the mission had failed.

He kicked the fainted captives violently in an attempt to wake them up and ordered them to do the same to the others as he sat down. His head still hurt, and messed up his already chaotic thoughts.

“Human, wizards, attack…captives! Where’s the captive?” Alec ran to where Helen was imprisoned before, only to arrive at an empty cell.

“Those bloody humans–” Alec growled in anger causing everyone around him to cower in fear.

“I’m the biggest here, I’m the head of you all!” He struck a few of the stronger werecreatures to show his authority. The rest could only whimper in submission, he was a high-grade werecreature after all. He exceeded the rest in both strength and speed.

“We, go back— Blackblood…” Alec made a decision, he could only abandon the campsite in its current state. But before anyone could object, a voice sounded in his head.

‘Don’t go back! Those darned humans, I haven’t made my revenge on them. The others will mock me if I go back!’ The voice circled his head and overtook his previous decision. Alec got dizzy for a bit and decided to abandon his decision and gathered all his subordinates.

“Those despicable humans, me, Alec, your new head will avenge!” After announcing his decision, he received stares of fear instead of excited growling— Leylin’s previous attack had frightened them.

Before Alec could think of anything else, chaos erupted at the entrance of their campsite. A group of human adventurers barged in. No, it was the city guards, but they seemed to be few in number.

Alec scratched his head. He’d attacked both guards and adventurers before, the only distinction in his mind was that guards were greater in number and had more tender flesh.

“They want to attack us just based on that amount of people?” Alec was triggered despite his low intellect.

“Kill them!” He bellowed before charging forward in front of the rest. The first person he saw was an armoured young female knight emitting a dazzling aura.

“A strong one from the humans!” Alec was taken aback, but that didn’t last for too long before he charged at her.

“Kill them!” The remaining city guards were filled with bloodlust, charging forward for their future and life, as well as for vengeance. They burst forth with bloodshot eyes and the last remnants of their strength.

The werecreatures who had endured the previous battle were only at half their strengths, and the rest carried injuries that made them weaker than before.

“Perhaps we really can win this time!” The soldiers watched Leylin, who ran before all of them, with a glimpse of hope.

Mass Bull’s Strength! Cloudkill! Enchant Weapon!

“Charge! Victory is ours!” Leylin roared, spells shooting out from his hands as the knights slashed at the werecreatures with their swords, sending a werecreature’s skull rolling to the floor.

‘The paralysis effect is still not over, especially on the high-ranked werecreature. The spiritual suggestion is still working though!’ Deep inside, Leylin was actually observing the battle quietly.

He’d left these captives behind on purpose, to give the city guard some achievements, How else would he return? Light from a large-scale spell shone, and Rafiniya noticed in shock that her strength had increased greatly.

“A mass buff? Rank 6 spell?” She looked at Leylin in confusion.

Chapter 902: Reward

“He’s actually broken through!” Rafiniya’s eyes widened slightly. She obviously knew what the casting of Mass Bull’s Strength implied. It was a rank 6 spell that only rank 13 wizards could cast. This sort of spell that could boost a group was very popular in the army.

As a noble, Rafiniya knew more than regular people and definitely understood how terrifying this was.

“He’s only twenty!” Rafiniya glanced at Leylin, who was so young that it was ridiculous, and suddenly felt down. While she was considered a genius, she was nothing in comparison to him…

*Aoo aoo!* However, getting distracted during battle was very dangerous. The female knight had made this exact mistake. Alec thundered from opposite her, his muscles bulging bit by bit. His claws swept forth, seemingly severing even the air itself.

Wild Burst! He had clearly obtained this power from Malar.

*Boom!* Rafiniya felt a burst of strength from his hands, causing her double-handed blade to whistle sharply as it flew off.

“Crap!” She wanted to retreat, but it was already too late. The high-ranked werecreature charged forward, his coarse pores and nauseating skin distinctly visible to her.

Alec snarled, only having one thought in mind. Tear! He would tear this knight in front of him apart!

‘Am I going to die?’ Rafiniya slowly shut her eyes, ‘How could I let myself get distracted in battle?’

However, the pain that she anticipated did not appear. Rafiniya opened her eyes and found Leylin’s tall figure in front of her, blocking the attack.

A sabre fell, and the high-ranked werecreature’s head rolled to the ground, blood spurting out of his neck like it was a fountain.

*Woo woo…* The other werecreatures saw that their new leader had fallen at the hands of a human, and the emotions of terror that had been accumulating ultimately exploded. They whimpered and turned to escape pathetically, yet were easily pursued and killed by the human warriors. Most deaths in battle came when one fled in chaos, as such opponents were the easiest to take care of.

‘Is he a hero like in the legends?’ Rafiniya got up, gazing at Leylin with his sabre. Something glinted in her eyes, causing a slight flush to rise upon her cheeks.

……

A meeting was being held in Silverymoon, regarding Leylin and his men.

“I’m against this!” Cassley slammed the table, causing a small earthquake. “There’s something wrong with squadron 5’s mission completion!” His face was flushed.

“A huge camp with numerous high-ranked werecreatures, as well as an altar of the God of the Hunt. How could they have defeated them all?” He’d seen Leylin before, “I firmly stand against them being given credit and promotion!”

Cassley was almost on the verge of shouting at this point. Such ungentlemanly behaviour caused all of the other members to frown slightly.

‘He’s a sorcerer after all, he’s far too emotional. Not like a wizard at all, what a fortunate guy…’ More than one high-ranked wizard was silently thinking of this.

“We’ve already gotten our men to take a look and verify the bodies of high-ranked werecreatures and the others. What else do you want?” The elven wizard whom Leylin had seen once before asked coldly. “Besides, did you only just find out how dangerous this mission was? Who was it that had guaranteed at the beginning that it was only a ‘tiny’ camp?”

Unusually, the elf wizard was obviously out to get someone.

‘Looks like Cassley’s side is at a disadvantage…’ After seeing this, the other big shots all nodded, now having a better understanding of the struggles and strife between the elf wizard and Cassley.

But this was the truth! When both sides’ strength were about the same, it was impossible to deny or fake anything.

“You’ve seen the report! The camp had already been raided by some unknown organisation before, which was why squadron 5 got it easy…” Cassley still did not let up, “Therefore, we can’t consider this as squadron 5 completing the mission. We need to investigate this carefully!”

“Gods! How could you not distinguish what’s right and wrong here!” The elf wizard was so furious that he was trembling, “Our Silverymoon has never banned anything like that. Even if Leylin got external help, that’s because he’s capable!”

“Enough!” A deep voice sounded from the person sitting at the head of the table. He had an immense presence that seemed to have gone past some sort of boundary, entering the domain of Legends.

“Commander!” Cassley and the elven wizard were immediately discouraged as they saluted and apologised.

“The reason we have gathered is not to discuss the achievements of a subordinate’s squadron. There are more pressing matters at hand!” The old wizard spoke slowly, looking like a regular human. He had muddy eyes and wore a simple grey robe. There was nothing special about him whatsoever. However, it was this old man that had control over all the high-ranked military officials in the hall.

“Silverymoon is an open city state confederation. Obeying rules is the basis of our existence. Even if squadron 5 overstepped any boundaries, they still completed the mission and should therefore get what they deserve!” The old wizard made the final decision. Cassley’s lips twitched, but he did not say anything in the end.

After all, if Leylin had truly succeeded and completed the mission, he could at most only fault him for the process. Legitimacy belonged to the victor, and that had always held true. Seeing the elven wizard opposite him look all smug, his heart blazed even more.

He had brought up this issue and taken care of everything in the shadows himself. He’d thought that he could ruthlessly give Leylin a setback, but the result had surprised him. The defeat this time would mean the people in the faction would view him less favourably, and the effect on him was practically destructive.

‘Leylin, is it?’ Cassley thought over this name ruthlessly, ‘In a situation where the captain had to return with grievous injuries, he still finished the mission resolutely. On top of that, he was even lucky enough to get the werecreatures at their weakest… If he’s trying to be a hero, hehe…’

Leylin had gotten just a bit of attention before, but henceforth Cassley would ferociously attack this little wizard.

As a person in a leading position, he was now seeing a pawn have the guts to move in a way he had not planned it to, and one that was even baring his fangs at himself.

Even if that was the current situation, Cassley would never imagine that the fellow he’d treated as a pawn would be hiding something terrifying.

“Our next topic is the allocation of funds for the perpetual fortification on Sunrise Mountain Range…” Cassley perked up again.

One loss meant nothing. What was more important was the orcs’ upcoming attack.

……

“This is all thanks to you, Leylin!”

The sunlight shone through the windows of an infirmary room that was obviously of a high-grade. The motes of dust floating through the air were rendered visible..

Aulen looked slightly pale as she lay in bed, surrounded by the group of officers who had survived.

“With saving my life and completing the mission, you’ve helped me twice. I will remember it!” Aulen guaranteed.

“It’s nothing. I did it for myself too!” Leylin smiled. Aulen now looked nothing like she had been as a soldier, instead seeming rather delicate. It seemed like the matter with Lanshire had given her a huge shock.

“After this, I’m no longer fit to stay in the city guard. I’ve already submitted my resignation. I hope you can take care of our brothers for now. It won’t be long before you get your rewards…” Aulen smiled bitterly.

“Squadron 5 is my foundation. I’ll never give up on them!” Leylin guaranteed, looking enthusiastic.

“That’s good… cough cough…” Aulen began to cough violently for a while, and then eyed Leylin, “As for your rewards this time… You’ll definitely become a battalion commander.That’s a high-ranked officer in the city guards, and you might even be granted a hereditary title. Even in other countries, you will be recognised…”

At the mention of this hereditary title, the other officers began to look envious. Once one became a noble whose title could be succeeded by his descendants and held his own land, he would truly enter the upper classes of society. His children and grandchildren would become noble youths above the rest.

That was the dream of all the officers at the bottom tier, but in less than two years of entering the city guards Leylin had won it all. While some jealousy arose, these feelings melted like ice in the sun after seeing the wizard emblem on his chest,.

This was a rank 13 wizard at such a tender age. That achievement was more than enough for him to get everything, and the huge gap caused the feelings within them to dissipate.

By the time Aulen returned, Leylin had gotten his newest appointment and rewards.

“As expected, I’m now a battalion commander and a baron.” Leylin sent the soldier who had come to send the order away, and then glanced at the parchment paper with an enchanted imprint on it. He smiled as if thinking about something.

Individual strength was rather powerful in the World of Gods, especially the city guards of Silverymoon. It had a powerful army made of practically all sorts of Professionals. Having the authority to command over 200 people was already rather powerful.

If this was times of peace, Leylin would never get this role. However, they were expanding the army in preparation for war, and Leylin was considered an ‘old soldier’ from before, which gave him an advantage.

From this appointment, Leylin could smell the war that would soon arrive.

Chapter 903: Alustriel

To be given the title of baron, as well as receive a hereditary title, it was usually necessary to meet with the city’s ruler. To tell the truth, Mystra’s Chosen was also the Lady of Hope from legends— Alustriel. Leylin was rather excited to meet her.

In his two years within Silverymoon, he had never met with her. He had only caught sight of her a few times from the sidelines. Rumour had it that this lady had a very good temperament and even enjoyed blessing the celebrations of ordinary citizens randomly. She was even willing to help beastmen.

Leylin’s judgement of her was like this: A political idiot, an empty-headed and hot-blooded fellow like Rafiniya who, if not for her formidable power and the elders and the city hall wiping her ass would bring down the entirety of Silverymoon.

Leylin felt that Alustriel was more suited to be a humanitarian than a politician. Her naive and natural personality was ill-suited for politics and court, just like Rafiniya. That hot-blooded and righteous lady knight was a very good companion and friend, but she was not a good superior. If she was allowed to run a city, it would all end in disaster!

Now however, Alustriel governed Silverymoon City properly, and the most impressive thing was that she possessed even more formidable personal power. In times of peace, everything had been good. However, Silverymoon now faced the orc invasion which amplified every flaw in her governance. Leylin gradually grew aware that a great calamity would soon be upon them.

Court etiquette was a very big problem for newly-promoted nobles. They could not be lacking in manners during the ceremony to confer titles as well as their audience with the city’s ruler, else the other nobles would mock them. Nobles who had risen from nothing had always found this process very difficult.

It was also the main reason why those old nobles despised the new ones. In their eyes, those country bumpkins did not deserve such a position, and neglected the vitality that came with interactions between different social classes. In the end, they had only slowly declined.

Fortunately, Leylin had received instruction from an etiquette teacher. He had learnt it quickly and after a single afternoon, the etiquette teacher, who had been specially sent by the court, had left satisfied.

Alustriel also wanted to meet him before the ceremony. This sort of private meeting did not matter much to him, as he did not feel she would be able to see through his false identity unless he was face-to-face with her god’s true body.

……

Leylin had seen Silverymoon’s imperial palace in the distance several times. However, he did not care much about any outstanding wealth in the palace. He was only interested in the rumoured legendary spell resources that it could contain.

However, once he truly entered the palace, he drew his spiritual force firmly back into his body and did not dare to carelessly investigate.

‘There were at least five high-ranked magic probes at the gate. There will be many more high-ranked wizards guarding the palace itself…’ Leylin lowered his head but something flickered in his eyes.

Silverymoon’s palace and the Wizards’ Guild were the most well-defended and strict places. It was rumoured that the strongest in these places could not be bribed, and even Legends did not dare to provoke Silverymoon City, who had the backing of the Goddess of the Weave.

However, Leylin never had the intention of robbing the place, and was thus very calm. He was currently clad in the splendid attire of a noble, the clothes which were embroidered in gold thread stifling him. He looked like a peacock who had spread its feathers.

There was nothing that could be done. The clothes of a noble were rich and garish, as if they wished to put everything he had on display. Leylin normally wore robes or leisure clothes at home, but it would certainly be inappropriate to wear those now.

“Her majesty the queen wishes to receive her guest in the side palace hall.” At this moment, a female official trotted over and announced in a steady voice. Leylin then followed her to a separate part of the palace.

“Here it is!” Leylin was not left waiting for long. In a moment, he felt the security around him had increased to its utmost, and there were even two powerful soul forces near him. He immediately contemplated them inwardly.

“Good day, Sir Leylin Faulen!” A peal of laughter rang out like a silver bell, and Leylin finally saw Alustriel.

Her eyes were like moonlight, and she seemed like the very embodiment of beauty. She only wore a simple gown, but she was naturally breathtaking.

“I do apologise for my lateness. I went to Uncle Cooper’s roast meat banquet, and I brought a blueberry pie that he personally baked for you. It can’t be a more appropriate congratulatory gift for you…” Alustriel fixed her gaze on Leylin with a smile on her face, passing a basket of roast meat to Leylin.

“Your majesty!” Leylin rather speechlessly accepted the gift, and respectfully bowed exactly as he had been taught by the etiquette teacher.

“Your majesty, how could you see your vassal in such a manner! There are still a few more items on today’s schedule to address as well…” A white-bearded old man chased after Alustriel into the palace, with thick sheets of parchment and quills in hand. After seeing Leylin, he even smiled helplessly.

‘Scholar Buren, full name Buren Eustace. Alustriel’s clerk and the leader of the elders, as well as her most trusted subordinate. He’s actually the prime minister of Silverymoon…’ A string of information flashed across Leylin’s mind.

Naturally, what drew his notice were the powerful magical undulations coming from both Alustriel and Buren. It meant that they had both broken through mortal limits and had entered to realms of Legends.

Alustriel’s body possessed a trace of divinity from the Goddess of the Weave, and it in particular attracted a deep interest from him.

‘I really want… I really want to devour her! Such a pity. If I did that, the Weave Goddess will be the first to hunt me down…’ Leylin sighed in his heart.

“Haha, Baron Leylin! You don’t need to be so formal and stiff, you don’t seem like a 20 year old youth at all!” Alustriel undeniably had an aura that was as refreshing as a spring breeze. Conversing with her made Leylin loosen up considerably. Her charisma was great.

“Your title ceremony will be held in three days’ time. Tell me Leylin, tell me like a friend; do you have any requests?” Alustriel gently said as she looked at the wizard before her.

“If it’s like this,” Leylin took a deep breath as his eyes filled with determination, “I hope I can freely read through the court’s collection of wizard resources…”

“You may!” Alustriel agreed very readily, surpassing Leylin’s expectations and filling him with astonishment. Hey, hey! Wasn’t she meant to ask him to climb to her inner circle before finally being allowed to peek at those documents? Was it really alright to give it to him so happily?

“Cough cough… Your Majesty!” At this moment, the saviour of the show appeared. Scholar Buren coughed with all his strength, attracting Alustriel’s attention over.

“Although Baron Leylin is a genius, legendary spells will only pose difficulties for his current state. For his own good, we can give him those resources that are below the rank of Legends.”

“Oh, I apologise! I’ve forgotten that point,” Alustriel looked at Leylin, “Because of the rigid nature of Legends, the Legend-ranked resources would not be beneficial to your growth now. I can first give you those resources below that rank, and once you advance to become a high-ranked wizard…”

“Cough cough…” Scholar Buren looked at this failure of a queen and began to cough like he was choking to death.

“This is more than enough already. Thank you, Your Majesty,” Leylin smiled as he bowed, and his elegant demeanour astonished even Buren. Disappointment had indeed flitted across his heart, but he did not show it at all.

For those wizards below rank 15, research materials at or above the legendary realm really was too complicated, and Alustriel had meant well when she restricted them. However, Leylin was different. He was not some low-ranked wizard, and he could even understand information on godhood if it was given to him. However, he could not admit this.

Buren’s actions could also be understood. If this sort of thing was handed out now, then how would he be rewarded for outstanding service in the future?

Just because he could understand the reasoning behind the forceful interruption did not mean Leylin’s heart was not ill at ease. After chatting with Alustriel for a while and receiving the visitor’s pass for the palace library, Leylin left the palace.

It had to be said that Leylin had developed a new understanding of Alustriel after meeting with her. It could be said that he had a favourable impression of her, but maybe not of Buren.

“What did you think of him, Buren?” Alustriel asked with interest as she cupped her face with her hands. Even if she was naive, she had changed with the polish of many years of experience, although the changes were not particularly big.

“He did not have any traces of evil intent or the aura of a devil on him,” Buren’s eyes turned crimson, looking extremely terrifying, “And his thirst for knowledge is sincere, not faked!”

“If it’s like this, then how come you didn’t allow me to give him the authority to view those resources?” Alustriel said, feeling hard done by.

“Resources ranked legendary or above must be exchanged for contributions, this rule is the cornerstone that protects our Silverymoon City!” Buren looked at Alustriel, who was acting like a little girl, with a helpless and bitter smile.

“Also, giving an insignificant wizard like him those high-ranked and above resources is more than enough. After he reaches rank 15 and swears the oath of eternal loyalty to the Styx, then we can pass on the legendary-ranked resources…”

“Alright, alright,” Alustriel waved her hand, “You can make the decisions. Oh, tonight I have to attend Mister Nudu’s dinner party.”

“Please forgive me, but I must remind Your Majesty that as the ruler of our Silverymoon City and the alliance, it is highly inappropriate for you to suddenly turn up at the party of our ordinary citizens…”

Chapter 905: War

With their huge numbers, the orcs had many peak experts. The fort quickly changed hands. There weren’t even many magic warnings issued, allowing them to have the time to lay low in wait for the reinforcements once the original guard was taken care of.

After a few rounds, the teleportation rays no longer flickered, and the orcs controlled the fort with ease, setting up their own teleportation spell formations. The Unfallen Moon Fort had its own arrangements for escape routes. The wizards had left themselves teleportation gates that would allow for convenient access for assistance. The orcs in turn had messed up the spatial undulations here and sealed off all teleportation.

Just as the camp was in a frenzy, a pair of golden eyes looked down from above. In that moment, the Weave within tens of kilometres seemed to rebel, and powerful thunderclouds formed silently.

“Mystra, what’s happening? Are you trying to go against our contract?” A gruff voice sounded, and the thunderclouds in the sky dissipated to reveal shining moonlight. The orcs below did not even realise that they’d been at death’s door, and they all silently gathered their loot.

The dim golden eyes did not make any more movements, and instead seemed to streak through the sky and focus on an orc.

“Gruumsh!” The owner of the golden eyes called out the name of the werebeast, the flames of her fury growing.

“You saw that. I didn’t make the first move! It’s a result of the guys’ fight!” The orc god chuckled, sounding gleeful.

“Furthermore… We’ve gotten the support of many gods, for instance the guy who’s been following you…” Gruumsh reported another piece of news and then was satisfied to see the anger in Mystra’s eyes.

The powerful conscient left, looking exasperated at seeing such a conflict happen so close.

“I can’t suppress someone as powerful as the Goddess of the Weave even at my peak. However, the competition on this path is ruthless. Whether in the dusk of the Magi and Gods, or now…” Gruumsh mumbled, and then he disappeared after sending down a powerful oracle. With their priests, the maddened orcs seemed to spread throughout the north.

Survival and reproduction were the two main goals of living beings. The orcs were like locusts as they looted all that they saw, and much blood was spilt. The states that were lucky to survive in the northern lands sunk into an arduous battle after being summoned by Silverymoon. The situation was in a deadlock.

On one hand, the land that the orcs obtained needed to be governed, and the soldiers needed to be reorganised. On the other, with the sudden attacks, the Silverymoon Alliance had suffered continuous losses and desperately needed some respite.

Another great wave of attacks could burst forth, and small skirmishes were a constant thing these days. The mercenaries, adventurers and even dreamers of the human world risked their lives to come to the northern lands, hoping to get some part of the glory. More merchants and commoners fled, which was a huge headache for the country.

In this chaotic world, a name that had been in the shadows before began to grow in intensity and shone in the battle with the orcs, thus earning the name of a hero…

……

Unwittingly, a year passed. Year 37666 of the calendar of the gods, Silverymoon City.

A handsome black horse galloped along the road, its bloody hooves evidence of it having passed through a battlefield. The troops following behind it held orc ears, proof of merit and rewards. The knight at the head was astonishingly a female!

“It’s the Knight of Light, Rafiniya!” An adventurer along the road saw the female knight, their eyes filled with obvious admiration and worship.

“Mm! I heard that the lady became a high-ranked knight at a young age. She’s been shining in battles with the orcs as of late.” A young girl’s eyes twinkled, “Even more worthy of admiration is the fact that Lady Rafiniya is like the personification of justice. She treats commoners and nobles all the same and does her best to protect the interests of the weak… Just like the city master…”

“That’s why so many adventurers are coming from all over the world!” Someone who was obviously the leader beside the girl supplemented, though he was critical on the inside, ‘Few agree with the city master’s ideals and want to participate in battle. Most people prioritise benefits.’

Although he knew this, he wouldn’t say such a thing allowed. Merit was the best way for adventurers to become nobles. The city master of Silverymoon was known for her generosity, so what harm was there in keeping mum?

‘Her commander, Baron Violet, seems to be a great example of this…’ The adventurer leader thought inside and urged his people on, “What are you looking at? Go to the Mercenary Guild and get the rewards from the mission!”

Due to the war and the surge of many mercenaries and adventurers, Silverymoon strangely seemed to be prosperous. The citizens who had lived calm and comfortable lives had disappeared, and in their place were mercenaries and adventurers who reeked of blood.

Besides hotels and the shops at the sides of the streets, there were many shops that sold all sorts of steel weapons and low-grade potions and the like. In general, they were items that would raise one’s battle might. The Mercenary Guild’s business was going so well that they were filled with adventurers every day.

‘Mercenary missions can only give money… Who knows, after a period of time when the war eases up, I’ll want to take a walk amongst the city guards…’ The leader was still considering his plans for the future. These were the true thoughts of unimportant characters in a chaotic world. They did not care who was in charge and only bothered about their own benefits.

……

The female knight naturally did not care about this group of adventurers by the road, this was a common thing in Silverymoon.

The procession entered one of the camps, and Rafiniya took off her armour to change into a casual outfit. She entered Leylin’s tent. He was blanked out while looking at a huge map of the northern lands, as if he hadn’t noticed Rafiniya entering.

Upon noticing this, Rafiniya suddenly had a mischievous look on her face and sneakily ran to Leylin’s back.

“Stop playing around, Rafiniya!” Leylin spoke unenthusiastically, causing Rafiniya to deflate like a ball.

“Come on, can’t you just let a girl have her way? What happened to your gentlemanly attitude?” Rafiniya expressed her discontent to Leylin, who seemed to have grown a pair of eyes on his back.

‘Haha… With the spiritual force of a wizard, she wouldn’t be able to escape the detections of the A.I. Chip no matter how cautious she was, unless she was a high-ranked assassin or thief.’

“Have you completed your mission?” Leylin was now the main commander here, and Rafiniya was his underling.

“Yes! I’ve completely wiped out that group of scouting orcs. What bastards! They massacred three whole villages!” Rafiniya exclaimed, feeling indignant. This had always been a life or death struggle between two races, and Leylin merely raised his eyebrows a little but did not say more.

In addition, he had another thought in mind.

‘They’re killing so much in the areas of their enemies!’ Leylin sighed. His intel said that old, ill, weak, and disabled orcs were already entering the areas that had been taken over, and clearing the land for cultivation. They had scattered seeds and were clearly trying to restore life to the land.

What surprised Leylin more was that these orc villages already had signs of human slaves.

‘There’s someone capable among the orc invasion…’ This was not a short term policy, and that caused fear among the higher-ups of Silverymoon. Leylin, however, was unperturbed. As their desires and goals were different, their worries varied. Watching those nobles down on their luck, Leylin even felt refreshed.

‘A.I. Chip, show me my current stats!’ Leylin commanded. The A.I. Chip loyally carried out Leylin’s orders, and showed a group of stats.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 21. Race: Human, Rank 14 Wizard. Strength: 12. Agility: 11. Vitality: 10. Spirit: 14. Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body. Spell Slots: Rank 6(3), Rank 5(5), Rank 4(7), Rank 3(???), Rank 2(???), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)] [Progress of analysis of Weave: Level 0: 100%, Level 1: 100%, Level 2: 100%, Level 3: 100%, Level 4: 68.88%, Level 5: 37.91%, Level 6: 12.36%!]

Leylin had risen by a rank in the past year, which the other wizards found unimaginable. If not for the war, he might even have advanced faster. Given his continous outstanding military service, he’d even obtained Legend-ranked information.

It had to be said that the World of God’s structure of the high-grade magic strength system was still a great inspiration to Leylin.

‘I’ve already checked the Nether Mountains a few times, and can confirm that the red dragon’s cave and the ruins of the arcanists are there…’ Leylin’s eyes glowed brightly.

Chapter 908: Unscrupulous

At the sight of Cassley stealing his credit right in front of him, Leylin subtly lowered his eyes and concealed the strange expression within them.

“Then I have to express my thanks towards you, sir! I have already prepared a banquet to welcome everyone as well as rooms. Please come back to the castle with me and rest.” Baron Andrew naturally would not be able to tell what had happened in a single glance, and attentively received the guests.

After following the Baron into his castle, Leylin saw many refugees within with panicked expressions on their faces.

“These damned werecreatures, our harvest this year is ruined…” Baron Andrew grumbled as he walked in front of them. Afterwards, he instructed his housekeeper and his wife to make preparations for the feast.

A magnificent feast was held within the castle’s enormous great hall. Roast chicken which looked a little scorched, wine as red as liquid ruby, and mountains of white bread were brought out. It could be said that to host Leylin and the men, this Baron Andrew had taken out what remained of his store of quality items.

Naturally, no matter how the world changed, the lifestyle of those in the upper classes would always be much better than those below them. Leylin swayed his wine glass and watched the dark red wine swirling within it, a strange smile on his face.

“Please be assured, Baron Andrew. Silverymoon City will not sit idly by and watch these werecreatures attack. The tax exemption is an entirely different matter, and you will need to contact the city hall…” In the position of the guest of honour, Cassley was cheerfully chatting with the baron. His manner of speaking made Baron Andrew nod slightly, looking completely convinced.

Even those young ladies near him who were clearly his daughters had peculiar looks in his eyes.

“Wizard Leylin!” Just at this moment, Cassley called out Leylin’s name.

“Lord Cassley, how can I help you?” Leylin did not move from his seat and nodded slightly to indicate he had heard. His action filled Cassley’s eyes with dissatisfaction.

‘This fellow, he should have died long ago!’ Cassley raged within his heart. On the surface however, he still wore the smile he had on earlier, “According to military command, I will organise the nobles’ defences in the rear. I’ll leave the fighting on the frontlines to you!”

Baron Andrew looked at Cassley then at Leylin, his eyes filled with astonishment. He wasn’t a slow-witted person, and now he seemed to see something different..

‘This wizard Leylin, he seems to have rather good standing. However, he seems to have some conflict with high-ranked wizard Cassley,’ Baron Andrew would normally exploit this relationship for his own gain, however he was now worried.

‘In these times, infighting will just exacerbate the wear and tear on one’s own troops. What are those fellows in Silverymoon City thinking?’ Baron Andrew grumbled, and at the same time thought of his previous actions. Only until he had confirmed that he had not neglected Leylin and his faction did he secretly let out of a sigh of relief.

At the same time he also decided to disregard the situation between Leylin and Cassley.

“Of course, that is my original mission after all,” Leylin very readily agreed to Cassley’s demand, which went completely against his expectations and left him feeling rather astonished.

“Then, I’ll ask you to go towards Vaughan Village and station the men there,” Cassley replied, as if this was all as a matter of course.

“Please forgive me for this, but you have no right to interfere. The front line is under my command,” Leylin smiled as he rejected him, which made Cassley flush bright red.

“Very well…” After rudely huffing a few times, Cassley began to forcefully pressure him, “However, to maintain our line of communication, I need to send a contact member out with you. Your troops also need support in terms of rations from my group.”

This was a restriction and also an unspoken threat.

“I can agree to this,” Leylin expressed his approval after thinking for a bit.

Cassley watched Leylin’s troops slowly depart from the top of the castle, his expression immediately becoming malevolent.

……

Two days later, amongst Leylin’s troops.

“Lord Leylin, I feel that we should not continue towards Cade village,” A gorgeously dressed fellow broke formation and came to Leylin, a highly arrogant look on his face. Rafiniya watched him walk over with a look of loathing, and urged her horse ahead to leave them behind.

This fellow was named Malfoy, and he was the communication liaison that Cassley had forced on him. He reportedly was the heir of a Marquis and was well-placed in Silverymoon City. Unfortunately, he had Cassley backing him so he was rather unscrupulous. He did not even address Leylin with the minimum amount of respect.

“Oh? What do you propose?” Leylin calmly looked at this impertinent fellow.

“I believe we should follow Lord Cassley’s previous proposal, going to Vaughan village is the correct decision,” Malfoy replied fearlessly. He had the backing of a formidable faction and was a knight of Silverymoon. How would a bumpkin like Leylin dare to do anything to him?

“I refuse,” Leylin looked at this fellow with a trace of ridicule. Perhaps the strength of a faction would be useful in times of peace. Since they were in an era of war, however, the man who held greater military might would be the stronger power. This fellow who couldn’t even understand that would just die.

“What?” Sir Malfoy’s anger was out of this world, “You actually dare…”

His fingers trembled as he looked at Leylin, as if he was seeing his greatest enemy. Malfoy never thought that he would meet such a rude person, and thoughts of Cassley flew out of his head. Perhaps he did not realise that his life lay in Leylin’s hands. In this situation, how could Leylin dare to rebel against him?

*Thump thump!* Right at this moment, an enormous dust cloud swept over them. The dust had been kicked up by a great number of troops and their horses.

“Stay alert!” The alarm rang. Malfoy almost fell to the ground in fright, his face paling rapidly. His behaviour made those knights around him smile disdainfully.

The deafening sound of hooves clopping against the ground was followed by a huge squadron of troops appearing in their field of view. The purple flag of the Violet family was dazzling as it hung on the carriages.

“It’s the Violet flag! The insignia of the commander’s family!” The soldiers all cheered.

“This… This is…” Malfoy trembled as he saw the massive squadron ahead slowly integrating together with their own troops. An old man who looked like a housekeeper even personally came to pay his respects to Leylin.

‘Almost 500 personal troops, as well as so many carriages full of grain…’

Leylin’s carriages were full of elite soldiers, and there was even an enormous cart in the fleet with sacks filled to the brim with grain.

‘At this point, his power is really…’ Malfoy’s face grew pale. With this assistance as well as Leylin’s original 200 Professionals and 300 auxiliary troops, he commanded over 1000 soldiers. He could even provide rations for his troops by himself, and he did not need to Cassley’s support at all.

‘The most frightening part is that if these men only answer to Leylin, and if they decide to rebel with him, then perhaps it’s enough for them to…’ Malfoy grew even more frightened, and his voice grew shrill, “No, that’s impossible! How do you have so many men?”

“Perhaps you’ve forgotten that my Violet territory is here?” Leylin taunted him with a smile.

“Violet territory?” Malfoy stared at him blankly, and immediately thought of Leylin’s fiefdom which was only a huge wasteland. Even savages did not live there.

Looking at Malfoy’s stunned expression, Leylin laughed inwardly to himself. Although his Violet territory indeed possessed nothing, it served well to boost his position and aid his pretense.

After receiving this title, Tiff and the others in the organisation all became Leylin’s vassals. They could even transport their previously hoarded resources and rations, as well as weapons and other military materiel to this place.

Everything had happened in one go, resulting in this.

“Young master, we’ve received the news,” Tiff’s expression grew sombre as he murmured into Leylin’s ear.

“Oh, that? I understand…” Leylin looked at Tiff, who had broken through his limits to become a Legend.

“Spread word of my command, we will go west. Our target is the Nether Mountains!”

“What? What?” Malfoy was the first to blurt out, “Lord Leylin, please take note of the orders you are under! Don’t tell me that you’re thinking of disobeying Silverymoon’s army?”

“Even if I disobey, what can you do?” Leylin smiled as he ridiculed the man, watching as blood drained from Malfoy’s face.

“Did you really think that martial law and Silverymoon’s noble title would tie me down?” Originally, Leylin’s subordinates were all Silverymoon’s men. Whatever plans he had could not be realised unless he left by himself, and he would become a wanted criminal.

Now, everything was different. The private vassals of a noble would be absolutely loyal to him alone. With this power in hand, Leylin could now completely coerce all his subordinates.

In the beginning, he secretly controlled over half of this unit. After a year of leading them, he now no longer had any problems.

“What? You dare to disobey orders?”

“Mm, I’ve always found you an eyesore. Drag him down and behead him!” Leylin waved his hand as if he was swatting a fly.

Two bulky and muscular vassals immediately hoisted Malfoy up from under his arms, wringing him like a chick.

“Since you’re about to meet the god of death, I’ll tell you some news,” Leylin drew closer to Malfoy, a malicious smile on his face, “The orc hordes have already launched a surprise attack on Silverymoon City, and have completely surrounded it. In other words, that privileged noble status which you have been so intensely proud of is about to disappear…”

Chapter 910: Slaying a Dragon

*Roar!* A huge silhouette streaked across the sky, and a huge monster that was tens of metres long immediately pulled its terrifying meaty wings before disappearing into a dark cave.

“Mm, that truly is the red dragon.” Leylin nodded. Dragons in the World of Gods were like huge lizards with wings, though they looked far more sinister. Their eyes that looked like spheres of lava left an especially deep impression on him.

“Ye– yes, my lord!” Helen answered from next to him, her body trembling.

“Is this because of the dragon’s aura?” Leylin looked at Helen, suddenly understanding and shaking his head with regret.

‘Looks like the Professionals under rank 10 shouldn’t come. They can’t handle the intimidation from the aura…’ he concluded. In his view, this fearful draconic aura was a weakened version of a spiritual force domain. Just facing the dragon would be a problem if one lacked a strong mind or spiritual force training, let alone attacking it.

‘As expected, the regular troops can only fight in the surroundings.’ Without alarming this huge creature, Leylin brough Helen secretly back to the camp. Following that, the team did as Leylin ordered. Like a huge, intricate robot, they began to work automatically.

“My lord, it’s done!” Tiff brought a group of elite Professionals to Leylin. In each of their hands were weapons with high-grade enchantments, and they seemed to be coated with something else as well.

“Mm. This magic potion we got from the werecreature tribe is meant to deal specifically with dragons, it should hopefully be useful!” Leylin could not help but think back to the werecreature camp. They had obviously been making preparations to slaughter the dragon, but all their materials were now Leylin’s.

Now, what they had gathered would serve the same purpose.

“Mm. Give the dragon intoxication potion and other items to the high-ranked scouts to sprinkle at the dragon’s cave. Hopefully, it’ll fall for the trap…” While there was a large distance between the camp and the dragon cave, it was still unsafe considering the range that the red dragon could see. On top of that, it wasn’t hibernating like many of its kind, which left Leylin on guard.

This camp was too eye-catching. It would be found the moment the dragon flew out on patrol, and its fate then would be obvious. Hence, Leylin did not count on the high-grade assassins’ poison trap working. The next day, he brought fifty people to the entrance of the dragon cave.

The bare ground had not even a blade of grass growing on it, and seemed very solid. There was also a strange smell lingering in the air.

“This is the smell left behind by the dragon. Most animals wouldn’t dare approach this place…” Leylin glanced at the group behind him. They were all high-grade Professionals, including Tiff and Rafiniya.

“Based on the observations of our thieves, this is the time that it usually rests. Furthermore, the red dragon has also eaten the goat with special ingredients that we especially prepared for it…” Leylin muttered to himself. At this moment, a dark shadow emerged from the sides, calling out in a low voice, “Boss!”

“How’s the situation?”

A high-ranked scout began his report, “I can confirm that the red dragon is inside, and our route is very simple. There is only one pathway, and there’s a possibility of other creatures in the way!”

“Good. Guide the way in front.” Leylin let the thief walk ahead, and a procession of excited people clutched the weapons in their hands as they entered the cave.

The passage was long and seemed to go all the way to the belly of the mountain. It was very vast, and the walls were dry.

“It’s up ahead!” The thief ran to Leylin’s side as he spoke. Leylin nodded and ordered the group to stop. They were now extremely quiet, making no sound at all.

“Bring me there.” Leylin and the thief went forward. After they passed through a curved path, they came upon an even larger karst cavern. Boiling hot light flickered at its entrance, with some quartz and shiny items present within.

Two other strange creatures were standing guard at the cave’s entrance, as if on sentry duty.

‘Hm? Earth Dragons? A subspecies of the dragons? But it’s not exactly similar.’ Leylin looked at the two which were obviously subspecies with auras that greatly resembled those of purebloods. His eyes glinted with wit.

‘Rumour has it that once an adult dragon gains intelligence, it normally enslaves some members of other races into working for it. Ancient dragons can intimidate entire races, I never thought the red dragon would do this as well.

Past the two earth dragons, Leylin sensed an even more powerful life undulation in the cave. It was heaving with rhythmic breaths, evidently in a deep sleep. In this situation, any sounds could wake it up.

“Tiff!” Leylin immediately called the Legend in his team.

“Young Master!” Tiff arrived by his side and bowed slightly.

“Can you kill them without alarming the red dragon?” Leylin asked.

“It will be slightly troublesome. This type of subspecies have very tenacious life force. I can make one disappear without a sound, but I can’t take care of two in an instant.” Tiff frowned slightly.

“That’s alright. I’ll help you in that area!” Leylin answered lightly.

“Then that’s fine…” Tiff’s eyes flashed with strands of black, and he quickly disappeared.

……

By the cave, a red earth dragon was loyally protecting its place, occasionally looking towards its comrade. All of a sudden, it saw something that appalled it. A dark figure seemed to appear from the air, raising its arms as if opening up a black hole to devour its comrade.

Shadow Jump! Singularity! Just as this Earth Dragon was about to howl out in warning, it was surrounded in light that rendered it immobile. This was Hold Monster. The dark figure darted out, and the giant black hole swallowed its body as well.

The whole process was a hair-raising experience, yet only happened within a few seconds. Not even a peep was made.

‘Noiseless casting!’ Helen’s pupils shrunk from behind Leylin. She’d witnessed the whole process.

“Let’s go!” Leylin made a sign, and entered the cave with Tiff.

Inside, they found the target of their expedition snoring. The red dragon had dark red scales with smooth murky patterns on them that shone like metal. Its two meaty wings were ashen brown and hidden on its back. Its neck twisted sinuously like a snake’s as it buried its vicious head into its chest. Its nose occasionally puffed out two streams of white smoke.

A dense spiritual might was being emanated from its body, enough to cause the cowardly to break down.

‘It really is a dragon, and it’s an adult that’s reached the realm of Legends!’ Rafiniya’s palms trembled slightly, and she could not help but hold tightly onto her longsword.

Only she, Tiff, and Leylin were in the cave right now. The rest were standing guard outside; even asleep the dragon had powerful senses.

‘Based on its detection abilities, only Tiff has the ability to attack it once. After that, it’ll definitely awaken…’ Leylin gave Tiff a look with his eyes, and he immediately understood. Tiff drew closer to the giant, holding onto a golden dagger.

Rafiniya and Leylin also prepared their own attacks.

“Begin!” Tiff’s golden dagger pierced into the triangular scale under its neck. That was its reverse scale, and the largest weakness.

*Roar!* In that moment, blood splattered everywhere. The red dragon roared abruptly— it was now awake!

*Pak!* Tiff was sent flying by a red tail, his figure wrapped up by many shadows while in mid-air.

“You… You despicable mortals. How dare you harm the mighty Sylvester…” While the injury Tiff had given it with its dagger was much smaller than the area of its body, the red dragon still snarled in its fury, preparing to give these little ants a lesson such that they’d repent in hell.

“You’re even thinking of using something like a toy…” It roared, eyes like fireballs trained on Leylin. All of a sudden, its voice disappeared.

“My strength… What’s going on? You wretched worms, what have you done to the mighty Sylvester?” The red dragon’s voice was filled with astonishment and anger, while Leylin was very pleased with the results of Tiff’s attack.

The golden dagger that he had held was a Dragonslaying Dagger Leylin had specifically prepared for this. The powerful toxins and curses were something even a dragon could do little against.

‘A.I. Chip!’ Leylin ordered calmly. At this moment, the A.I. Chip immediately showed its stats.

[Name: Sylvester. Race: Red Dragon (Adult) Strength: 21 (25), Agility: 10, Vitality: 19 (21), Spirit: 16 Status: Weakened from curse. Strength, vitality weakened. Feats: 1. Intimidating Aura 2. Dragonscale Defence 3. Dragon’s Breath 4. Suggestion spell. Description: This is a creature that has reached the realm of Legends. It possesses extraordinary strength and can even destroy a small city or army. It has acquired the magic and memories of the pureblooded dragon race, and there is a chance that its bloodline can improve further.]

“Do it!” Leylin yelled, his attack and Rafiniya’s reaching the red dragon’s body at practically the same time.

The longsword was edged with sharp qi. The enchanted weapon glinted as it ruthlessly tore through the dragon’s huge meaty wings. Leylin’s attack struck just then.

Chapter 912: Ruins

“Where is this place?” Helen asked as she touched the solid metallic walls in the surroundings. They had a silver-white lustre, making them look like a product of science fiction.

“It seems like it is a pocket dimension made by an arcanist, though it’s quite small…” Leylin closed his eyes, and his astounding senses spread out. They allowed him to feel the undulations connecting the dimension.

“This place is already on the verge of disappearing. It was always sealed, but now that we’ve activated the dimension we’ve started the countdown to its demise.” Leylin had an interest in this spatial overlay technique that sprung from the depths of his heart.

These preparations showed that once the Magi who comprehended laws showed them the path, they’d combined those experiences with advanced technology to do amazing things.

“What a pity…” There was a trace of regret in Leylin’s eyes. The pocket dimension was incredibly tiny and only as large as two football fields. It was on the verge of being destroyed now, so it held no value.

If not for that, were this pocket dimension to be revealed all wizarding Legends would try their utmost to obtain it. A wizard tower constructed atop this place would make for a covert and stable den,

Once they became a god, this pocket dimension could even be transformed into a divine realm! Of course, with the current state of the plane, it was impossible to remodel it.

“A pocket dimension? Destroyed by this sort of spatial storm?” Helen shivered. A dimensional storm caused by destruction of space was something even Legends weren’t guaranteed to survive.

“Mm! But we should still have three hourglasses’ worth of time…” Leylin snapped his fingers, and light flashed as an Endurance spell enveloped him. The environment in the pocked dimension would not be the same as in the prime material plane, possibly more extreme.

Of course, this place shouldn’t have been that way given that it was prepared by an arcanist, but Leylin liked to be ready just in case. After seeing what Leylin had done, Helen suddenly came to a realisation and did the same, adding another layer of protection.

*Rumble!* The silvery metallic door was pushed open to reveal rooms that were arranged like in a honeycomb. The floor was spotless, and even one’s image could be reflected in it.

“That’s all the information I have. How about you?” Leylin looked at Helen behind him.

“I only managed to see some fragments left behind in my ancestor’s notebook…” Helen’s smiled wryly.

“Looks like we can only check them one by one…” Leylin glanced at the flickering chandelier, “The core energy is still working, so there might be some traps left behind by the arcanists. Be careful!”

While it was possible for arcanist inheritances to be here, Leylin wasn’t sure if arcanists shared the eccentricities of wizards.

“Don’t worry, my lord!” Helen nodded, her slender figure disappearing into the passageway.

‘Looks like she’s going to rely on luck to get her through…’ Leylin nodded before shaking his head, and then he placed his hands behind his back and entered a random room. The two of them went their separate ways…

Inside one of the secret labs in the arcanist’s pocket dimension, a light blue screen brightened to show images of Leylin and Helen. Lines of red text streaked across it.

“Beep! Invaders discovered. Activating rank 1 defensive measures.”

“Arcane spell elemental reserves 1.09%! Unable to activate… Legendary Golem, Dimensional Banishing Spell Formation scarce. Implementing plan B…”

“Scanning of alchemic golem complete, is 34.17% intact. Beginning charging.”

“Charging complete. Starting preparatory defensive mechanism number 0331.”

After the lines of text appeared, a door that had been closed for a very long time opened up ftom one of the rooms, and an alchemic golem that was almost three metres tall walked out.

“Number 2133 awaits commands. Received mission, beginning task.” Blood red light brightened in its eyes, and a screen appeared with a projection of Helen. Sounds like the cracking of knuckles rang out, and the golem charged in her direction.

*Rumble! Rumble!* Leylin was reading a book, and the slight vibrations caught his attention.

“Hm?” He put down the incomplete draft in his hand, and thought hard, ‘Looks like the defensive mechanism of the laboratories aren’t completely damaged. That makes things much easier…’

Besides deducing the existence of arcanists, Leylin knew nothing about the ruins. With the time limit till this place would break down, he would be unable to take too many things. However, as long as there was an intellectual core or tower genie, the laboratory would be the most valuable region.

Setting aside the items in his hands, Leylin headed in the direction of the vibrations.

……

“Leylin, save me!” Running for her life, Helen saw Leylin walking over and brightened up. She cut a sorry figure.

There was a beast skin scroll in her hands, with the energy undulations of high-grade magic on it. This wasn’t an enchanted item, the energy was similar to those of magic artifacts from the Magus World!

With the way Helen refused to let go of it, this had to be something good. Still, Leylin as he was now thought nothing of it.

*Thud! Thud!* At this moment, the alchemic golem that had been pursuing her appeared before Leylin’s eyes. It was like an armoured knight from the medieval ages, though there were two small barrels on its shoulders that looked to be a fusion of magic and science.

“Beep! Discovered primary target, annihilating…” After seeing Leylin, its eyes emanated a terrifying crimson luster.

“Beginning charging of miniature magic honing cannon!” A layer of terrifying energy undulations condensed within the barrel on its shoulders, causing Leylin to feel a slight sense of danger.

“This is completely different from the techniques used before.” Leylin looked interested, and he moved abruptly.

A rumble sounded out as the miniature cannon fired, hot light causing even the metallic groudn to show signs of melting.

*Pu!* Leylin was struck by those bright rays of light, but then turned into dark shadows and exploded.

‘It’s a high-grade illusion!’ Helen hid aside. A battle of this level was something she had no say in, ‘But as long as we hold on for some time, Lord Tiff who’s guarding us on top should be able to come down. With his legendary strength…’

Helen was still making calculations as she grasped the scroll tightly. However, she then gaped in shock.

“After tens of thousands of years, it’s still preserved to this extent. Not bad!” Lights flashed, and Leylin appeared behind the alchemic golem, noting the damaged armour, adamantine runes and other lines.

“A pity though… The energy here is about to be completely consumed. Even legendary teams can’t come in…” The passage of time was the most terrifying of attacks. With its tempering and developments, even the stup of arcanists would leave holes behind.

“A completely different tower genie from the World of Gods and the structure of this intellectual core… They’re all like decorative items in front of me…” Leylin sighed. With some light at his finger, he pressed the puppet.

[Beep! Attack beginning. Target interface scanned, searching database… Cutting off information]

The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice soudned.

Arcanists were mostly born of Magi, so of course they would’ve used or improved upon the ideas of many Magi. They were like kids playing house to Leylin, especially with the help of the A.I. Chip. Connected with the puppet, Leylin’s soul immediately reached the core control room through the network in the pocket dimension.

At this moment, a piercing giant red font filled the screen in the hidden room. “Warning! Warning!”

“External information attempting to rewrite core authorisations. Rejecting, activating defensive wall…”

“Activation of defensive wall failed. Beginning self-destruction. Countdown: 3, 2, … Beep! Core authorisations modified. Leylin Faulen is now the absolute master. Self-destruction halted.”

“Wha- What’s going on?” From Helen’s perspective, what just happened was like a magical show. Once Leylin made contact with the alchemic golem, the entire pocket dimension had begun to tremble, and the lights had flickered unsteadily. Huge blue arcs of lightning had sparked out, making it seem like the end of the world had come.

A moment later, however, everything returned to normal.

“Come.” With authority over the laboratory’s core, Leylin now had a different aura on him that compelled Helen further. She was astonished as he brought her all the way to the core of the laboratory, as if this was a familiar route.

Be it the password-locked door or any other hindrance, all obstacles were easily taken care of in his hands. It was like he was the owner here.

“Identity verified. Welcome, master!” A door with a statue of an angel on the left and one of a devil on the right opened with a rumble. Helen followed Leylin inside, watching the door with fear.

‘He passed through a legendary curse so easily?’ This ease was unbelievable, and it made Helen realise that Leylin had an increasing number of secrets to him.

Chapter 913: Arcanist

‘Who on earth is he? He’s just a minor noble of Silverymoon City on the surface, but secretly he possesses the power of a Legend. Besides, he seems to be very familiar with this place… So why did he lie to me earlier?’ Helen was completely puzzled, but she carefully hid all her thoughts. After all, Leylin now held the right of life and death over her.

The core of the control room was unexpectedly small, and it only had an area of 5 or 6 square metres. At the centre was a strange hexagonal prism with all sorts of strange screens next to it. Some of them had already lost their glow or were filled with a grayscale static, while others were working.

“Open!” The outer shell of the hexagonal prism opened with Leylin’s command, revealing a blue crystal structure within.

“This is…” Helen looked at the splendid and magnificent blue crystal which sparkled beautifully, it was like she had been bewitched.

“This core port controls half of the laboratory and is also a communication terminal. Many resources can be downloaded here,” Leylin said lightly, unconcerned as to whether Helen understood him. He pressed his palm to the surface of the blue crystal.

[Beep! Spiritual force interface established.]

In a split second, Leylin seemed to have become a demigod, and nothing in the pocket dimension could be hidden from him anymore.

‘Weapons, live specimen libraries, database!’ Various images and words appeared before him, and it was only at that moment that Leylin realised how fortunate he was to grasp it all.

‘Its energy reserves haven’t even reached 2%, and its powerful weapons cannot be activated at all. The magic and spell formations are also damaged, and half of the golems have been destroyed. It looks like I can only send out one or two defective items…’ Leylin sighed. He believed that this pocket dimension would have been able to hinder even high-ranked Legends at its peak. Now however…

Of course, it would have been very difficult to seize control of the entire core back then. Whether it was a legendary wizard, thief, or even an elf, they would not be able to attack the lab’s intelligence core through the communication terminal. After all, they were on completely different planes.

However, Leylin was different. He was very familiar with this type of structure in the ilk of those made by Magi, and the A.I. Chip supporting him had even more knowledge reserves. It was purely because of this reason that he managed to seize the entire core unharmed.

[Beep! Laboratory’s power source reserve has reached its critical point, and is unable to absorb more energy from the abyss. Time before collapse: 1h 13min.]

The A.I. Chip displayed yet another message in front of Leylin.

‘As expected, the demiplane has deteriorated with age and is about to collapse. Is it too late to stop it? If it’s like this, then the most valuable thing here is…’ Leylin’s eyes were filled with regret at first, but then his expression brightened considerably.

‘A.I. Chip, record all the information from the terminal.’

[Beep! Mission established, initiating download program.]

The A.I. Chip executed Leylin’s task immediately. The magnificent light shining from the hexagonal prism was projected onto the walls all around him, as well as onto all the screens.

Leylin was bathed in its light, and a multitude of data and characters flashed across his eyes. The most important bits about the arcane arts and spell models, various alchemic experiments, research, improved meditation techniques, and anatomical records were presented to him. There were also diaries and other useless news from the terminal, and that too was fully copied by the A.I. Chip.

The extensive library of data was transferred in a split second. Compared to this, the tiny little bit of information Helen had almost given her life for to obtain was worth nothing.

[Beep! Information about the arcanist profession has been collated, and overlaps with the host’s wizardry. Combine?]

“Yes,” Leylin replied without the slightest hesitation. Afterwards, his aura began to change. An arcane flame began to burn, and powerful force poured into his sea of consciousness and began to remodel and process his profession. Leylin soon saw his status change from that of a wizard into that of an arcanist.

*Snap!* Leylin almost blacked out at the acute pain that came from his very soul. He felt his connection with the Weave instantly break off.

Fortunately, this severed state lasted only a moment before it reconnected once again. However, the connection was now somewhat different. In this split second, there seemed to be a pair of golden eyes focused on him. However, it was immediately deceived by Leylin’s grasp of the first 4 layers of the Weave.

The A.I. Chip’s reminders continued to ring out.

[Beep! Host has become an arcanist. Profession changed.]

[Beep! The host has gained arcane specialties: Energy Detection, Amplification.]

There was a detailed description beneath each of the specialties.

[Arcane Energy Detection: Arcanists are able to supercede the Weave’s restrictions and directly perceive the arcane energy in the environment, drawing it in to form arcane spells.] [Arcane Amplification: Arcane energy is amplified by 10-20% when an arcanist casts a spell.] [Beep! Host’s spiritual force has broken through, Spirit +1. Host has advanced to become a rank 15 arcanist.]

Leylin’s mind suddenly jolted, and afterwards his spiritual force directly made contact with the 7th rank of the Weave.

Looking at the Weave from an arcanist’s perspective gave him a completely different feeling. The feeling of jumping out and watching the Weave from afar increased the speed at which the A.I. Chip analysed the Weave.

Leylin’s stats had also changed.

[Leylin Faulen, Age: 21, Race: Human, Rank 15 Arcanist. Strength: 13, Agility: 11, Vitality: 12, Spirit: 15, Arcane Energy: 150, Status: Healthy, Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body, Specialities: Arcane Energy Detection, Arcane Amplification.]

‘As expected, the greatest benefit of becoming an arcanist is to break away from the Weave’s method of performing magic. Additionally, arcane energy has replaced my spell slots,’ Leylin nodded. Moreover, his separation from the weave affected only that aspect. This meant that Leylin could now also prepare rank 7 spell slots, and wait to use them the next day.

Naturally, due to the restrictions of rank, he only had 1 rank 7 spell slot.

‘Using arcane energy to cast arcane spells would perhaps consume more energy than using the Weave to instantly cast low-ranked spells. However, it will use up fewer spell slots,’ Leylin stroked his chin in thought. After fully analysing rank 0 to rank 3 of the Weave, he could instantly cast low-ranked spells. Overwhelming his opponent with a torrential number of spells had always been his killing move, but it was of course established within the authority of the Weave. It was equivalent to stealing Mystra’s power for himself.

If he only used arcane spells, then he wouldn’t have this benefit anymore. However, the greatest benefit of being an arcanist was that he could retain wizard spell models instead of forgetting them, and at the same time he could use the Weave!

‘As a result, I’m now outside the system but I can still enjoy the system’s benefits. Just using its power without any of the obligations, it’s so straightforward…’ Leylin sighed, ‘It’s a pity that if more people like me are born, then the Weave would fall apart.’

“You’ve broken through?” Although Leylin had only taken an instant to advance, Helen distinctly felt that something was different.

“Mm, I have,” Leylin smiled. What he had gained today couldn’t just be described as a breakthrough though.

‘I’m now an arcanist, and I have a great number of arcane arts with me. My improvement from now will be rapid. As a rank 15 Professional wizard, I’m of the highest class…’ Leylin was turning the idea over in his mind. He was a genius who had advanced to become a high-ranked wizard at the tender age of 21. Apart from the gods’ chosen or demigods, he was near the peak of the prime material plane.

“This place is very dangerous, it’s best that we leave as quickly as possible,” Leylin furrowed his brows and took Helen away from the core database.

The trip had gone fairly smoothly, and he had obtained resources from the arcanists as well as many arcane arts. It all saved him a lot of effort, but he hadn’t accomplished his most important goal yet; he didn’t get the inheritance of those Magi who had comprehended laws!

The A.I. Chip hadn’t found anything related to such Magi amongst all the resources it had scanned, and it filled Leylin’s heart with disappointment. The direction and experiences of the ancients would have been of great help to him.

‘It’s a matter of course. Not every arcanist can receive the instruction of a being like the Distorted Shadow, and even if he left an inheritance it wouldn’t be here…’ Leylin comforted himself, ‘The profits this time are sufficient. Just what the A.I. Chip has stored in its database would be enough to fetch an extremely high price.’

“Let’s hurry up, there isn’t much time before the pocket dimension collapses…” Leylin suddenly stopped in his tracks and turned his head in astonishment. He discovered that Helen had disappeared into thin air without his notice.

‘Impossible! I’ve always paid attention to my back, and I even have an arcane mark on her. How can the A.I. Chip’s sweeps not discover her?’

‘A.I. Chip! Sweep the entire laboratory and find Helen!’ Leylin immediately ordered. He had seized the core authority in this place, and even if most of the equipment was depleted or damaged a basic search was still possible.

Very quickly, the results were sent back to him. However, Leylin’s expression turned even more unsightly at the information.

‘Nothing! There isn’t a single trace left of her, and she didn’t even leave a corpse. It looks like she just disappeared suddenly…’ He had not felt such a powerful sense of déjà vu for a very long time.

Chapter 915: Dying in the Line of Duty

This was a peak rank 8 Magus with the power to twist time and change the future! The thought of himself reaching that realm left Leylin with a sense of longing.

“Whatever it is… This operation ended well. Let’s talk after leaving this place…” Leylin swept his eyes across the information in the A.I. Chip. The plethora of data about arcanists in there was real.

Leylin’s complexion only improved after they left the dragon’s cave, once he breathed in the chilly air that smelt of nature.

‘While the pocket dimension crumbled completely, there’s a possibility of something being left behind. I shouldn’t get too involved with this sort of thing before this body rivals my main one in power…’

There was fear in Leylin’s heart, ‘If the Distorted Shadow truly had malicious intent towards me, that one streak of intent would be enough for me to die there. So why did he let me off at the end, and even give me this scroll?’

Leylin glanced at the black scroll in his hands and then at Helen, who clearly kept peeking in his direction with a terrified expression.

“Do you know more about this thing?”

“No, I don’t! I found out from an ancestor that the Distorted Shadow had some manuscript in one of the rooms in the ruins that recorded some information about arcanists…” Under Leylin’s gaze, she trembled as she spoke the truth.

“I’m afraid this isn’t what you were looking for, and it’s very dangerous. Just leave it with me for now…” Leylin did not seem to have any plans of returning the scroll. The Distorted Shadow had too many ways to mess with a little rank 11 wizard. He could have distorted her memories and implanted a fake, which were all easy tasks.

“Alright, my Lord!” Helen felt a little discontent with his decision, but still agreed. After all, what had happened had truly scared her.

Leylin looked towards this half-elf wizard and suddenly exclaimed, “Mm! I’ll compensate you based on an agreement. Let’s say the way for arcanists to rank up and a portion of an arcane spell model.”

“Tell me what you want.” Helen had developed a very good understanding of Leylin over this period of time. He would never do anything that would not benefit him. Of course, once an agreement was reached, he would treat all equally.

“Vow me your loyalty for a hundred years. Swear it upon your soul and with the Styx as the witness.” Leylin spoke nonchalantly, watching the conflict in Helen’s eyes.

She was undoubtedly clever, though. “Alright.” After struggling over the decision for some time, she agreed and immediately swore to it.

‘Mm, her soul is real, so she should be the real Helen…’ Leylin nodded inwardly. The vow of a wizard’s soul when resonating with the river Styx was something binding, and it could not be faked.

As he was now, a rank 11 wizard was dispensable to Leylin. The key point was the verification and authentication he obtained from the vow. This Helen truly seemed to be original, though her emotions were all over the place.

‘Then… what did Distorted Shadow want to tell me? Did he manage to survive the dusk of the gods, or did he fall completely? No, with his strength he’d leave some soul fragments behind if he died. They would await resurrection for a long time…’ At this thought, Leylin’s expression grew sombre once again.

……

After killing the red dragon and exploring the ruins, there was no point in lingering on the Nether Mountains. Leylin hence ordered that they return. The group, which had dropped to around seven hundred in number, brought with them the immense glory and wealth of killing a dragon.

Rafiniya, however, looked sullen. It seemed that after like she would part ways after they left the Nether Mountains.

‘“Slaying the dragon and exploring the ruins took less than ten days. The outside world must be in chaos now, no?’ Leylin’s thoughts were filled with delight at this disaster. He didn’t care about the female knight’s mood. Such was reality.

‘What’s going on? Why have they imposed this level of martial law?’ After leaving the mountains, Rafiniya could obviously tell that something was off. Many of the surrounding villages had been completely abandoned, and there were sometimes some who were very guarded, extremely alert against strangers.

‘Could the werecreatures have invaded again? Or have the orcs launched a huge attack?’ Rafiniya quickly came up with two possibilities, beginning to get anxious, ‘Leylin’s explorations will definitely have him accused of being a deserter…’

The female knight suddenly begun to get worried, but then she shook her head, ‘A sly person like him must have long since prepared an escape route. Even without that, why do I have to worry about him?’

At this moment, a scout ran over. “Report! A friendly force has launched a signal up ahead!”

“Mm, launch the signal. We’ll go over!” Leylin nodded calmly, knowing who was coming.

In the dark forest, there were no other people besides him. As expected, after the scout sent the message, dust could be seen flying in the distance, and a human figure was like a black falcon swooping in from the sky.

“Leylin Faulen!” Cassley’s neck bulged from his immense fury as he arrived in front of Leylin.

“Why did you leave your battle zone? Also… where’s Malfoy?” After seeing the group of over 700 people behind Leylin, Cassley froze a little, but that was then drowned out by his anger.

“Did you know that because you neglected your job, I had to deal with the werecreature attacks and give up on helping Silverymoon?”

“Stop! Wait! I still don’t know what’s going on. Saving Silverymoon? Why?” Rafiniya felt a little dizzy.

“You don’t know yet? What a terrible excuse. Have you all been hiding in the woods in the past few days?”

Cassley had a mocking look on his expression, “The orc armies have already surrounded Silverymoon! While I, high-ranked wizard Cassley, was engaged in a bloody battle, your wretched new recruits dared to give up on the area they were supposed to be defend! You should all be hung!”

“Orcs surrounding the city?” Rafiniya staggered backwards, eyes full of disbelief. She was now completely disheartened, “You must have known that this would happen… Right?”

“Then… Why, mighty high-ranked wizard Cassley, did you not bring your own troops, and the volunteer army belonging to nobility and help them?” Leylin did not bother himself with Rafiniya and instead looked towards Cassley, ridiculing him.

“That’s because I need to guard against surprise attacks by the werecreatures!”

Cassley glanced at Leylin haughtily, “While you neglected your duties and thus committed a crime, I won’t pursue this. Baron Leylin, in my capacity as the chief officer of the northern lands, I command you provide support to Silverymoon now. Immediately!”

Till this point, Cassley still had no plans to stop setting him up.

“Hehe…” Leylin looked straight at Cassley till he was almost exasperated, and then answered slowly, “Why…”

“Why? You mean you even have the gall to go against my orders? Are you forcing me to execute you right this instant?”

Cassley narrowed his eyes slightly. His strength as a high-ranked wizard was what he prided the most. His opponent was at most a rank 14, and even with his own troops and other men, he was nothing.

Furthermore, the documents that appointed him as the chief officer of the northern lands had been sent over through urgent channels. With his status now, it should be fine to kill a Baron, much less one that had committed the crime of neglecting his duties.

‘Yes, killing a genius wizard myself seems to be a good idea! However, I have to wait first. When Andrew sends the troops, and I take over Leylin’s army… Heh heh… They even have a great deal of rations, which is pretty good! In the northern lands right now, it’s best to have both rations and men…’

A myriad of thoughts swirled in Cassley’s mind, but before he could come up with another plan or decide if he should temporarily be nice to the other wizard, Leylin suddenly chuckled. “If you want to kill someone, do it. Why overthink it?”

“What… ugh…” Cassley suddenly felt an intense pain in his chest, and his body stiffened. He looked down and found that a black dagger had pierced through his chest.

“That’s impossible… I have a high-ranked wizard armour and instantaneously casted Mishap! Enemies definitely won’t be able to break through my defences in an instant, unless… Legend!” Cassley crumbled down, and what he saw last was Tiff’s expressionless face.

“Trying to control me once the organisation collapses and using its might for that… Should I say you’re stupid, or stupid?”

“You… killed him?” Rafiniya’s voice was hoarse.

“No. Cassley died at the hands of werecreatures, on the line of duty!” Leylin laughed without the slightest of scruples.

“Pay attention! All on guard!” Leylin looked towards the friendly army that had finally arrived, and then shook his right hand with a sardonic smile.

……

The light of sunset looked like blood.

Andrew and a few nobles were respectfully speaking next to Leylin, “High-ranked wizard Cassley died at the hands of werecreatures. Our northern lands are really in a pinch….” After saying this, they could not help but wipe off the tears. What happened that afternoon had scared them stupid.

“Oh! Also, the clash this afternoon…” Leylin spoke a bit louder.

“That’s a misunderstanding, a misunderstanding!” Andrew immediately took the initiative to say this, astounded and fearful of Leylin’s ruthlessness.

Chapter 916: Scheme

“Since that’s the case, could all of you please sign this report of battle merits? Don’t forget to stamp it with your seal!” Leylin produced a document and waved it around, laughing sinisterly like a big bad wolf.

‘We’re already at this stage. Who would dare go against him?’ Baron Andrew laughed wryly inside and signed it.

“Good!” After all the barons and officers present signed their names, Leylin was all smiles as he kept the document, changing his attitude entirely, “As the subordinate of officer Cassley, I do feel regretful and sad about what happened. Divide his team amongst yourselves as you see fit!”

After hearing this news, everyone’s eyes brightened. The army that Cassley had brought with him was composed of a few nobles’ personal troops along with those of Silverymoon. Just the regular soldiers, horses and rations were enough for them to go green with envy.

‘After getting us to surrender, he’s having us divide the ill-gotten gains amongst ourselves? How evil…’ Baron Andrew sighed inside, but did not have the guts to voice his objection.

In reality, they were now prisoners of the sort. Leylin’s personal troops had completely defeated their allies this afternoon. After all, his underlings were battle-forged high-grade Professionals. It would’ve been strange if they had’t won.

Leylin didn’t force them too much at that time, instead ‘inviting’ them to talk peace.

‘After returning to the northern lands, we still will have to see how he decides to proceed…’ Andrew tried to console himself.

……

“Have you finally gotten what you wanted?” Rafiniya glanced at Leylin, her gaze icy.

“You’re talking about this?” Leylin lifted the joint declaration of the nobles and waved the document around, “No, this is just all in name. Essentially, with the chaos of war and there being even a question of whether the Silverymoon Alliance will still exist, who would care about the death of a wizard?”

Leylin wanted this in writing because it was better than nothing. Its presence would make a huge difference in any cases.

“Silverymoon Alliance not existing? Are you that pessimistic?” Rafiniya was rather astonished by Leylin’s conclusion.

“That’s how it is…” Leylin sighed, “The might of the Silverymoon Alliance already threatened the status of the human countries in the south. Mystra is facing all the orc gods practically alone.

Rafiniya paled at his simple analysis. There had been many who realised this in the past, but none had the courage to reveal it so clearly. Leylin was now breaking all pretense, revealing the naked truth to Rafiniya.

“You saw it in Silverymoon, didn’t you? The queen only has control over the land of Silverymoon. The Silverymoon Alliance states might support her when things are going well, but now…” Rafiniya’s heart dropped at Leylin’s words. She’d long since known that this was how nobles acted.

“Since things have gotten this bad, let’s go back to uphold the justice and peace I desire!” Rafiniya took a deep breath, eyes showing her emotional state.

“You… you’ll help me, won’t you?” The female knight had already guessed at the outcome, but still watched Leylin full of anticipation, hoping for a miracle.

“I’m sorry…” This girl was practically shining, the true model of a hero. It was a pity that Leylin would never do anything like like seeking his own death.

“Silverymoon has now been surrounded by the orc armies, and they even have several high-ranked Legends in charge. This level of strength…” Leylin presented his reasoning point by point, causing the light in rafiniya’s eyes to dim. The Leylin in her memories and how he was right now were two completely different people.

“But… You are the hero of Silverymoon. At this point…” Rafiniya gave it one last try.

“Oh! Please don’t call me that, ‘Knight of Light’!” Leylin’s obvious rejection caused Rafiniya to finally give up.

“Even knowing that this will take my life, I will not give up on my sense of justice. This is my path as a knight!” Rafiniya’s voice resounded in the tent.

Watching her back as she left, Leylin stroked his chin and muttered to himself. “What conviction she has. It’ll be difficult to make her fall…”

She planned on using her strength alone to turn the tide of the losing battle, to become a shining hero! When he was young before, in his previous life, Leylin had read many novels of that type. He’d thought them to be chock full of emotion and hot blood, but in the end only bitterly smiled at it.

Reality and imagination were two completely different things. Turning the tables under such terrible circumstances was something only possible in stories, and it was just an author trying to please the readers. In reality, such a thing had less than a hundred millionth of a chance of happening.

Such shining heroes who were full of fiery passion were indeed worthy of respect, but Leylin would never join their ranks!

“Besides… such an impulsive person like Rafiniya will probably die halfway to her goal. In the end, will her achievements allow her to be reputed as a hero?”

……

The next day, Leylin received word that Rafiniya’s departed without informing him. Using her own charm, she had even persuaded some people and taken about twenty with her.

Leylin merely rolled his shoulders back in answer, “Since they’re fools, let them go!”

After gathering Andrew and other nobles, Leylin discussed their next move.

“Silverymoon is now under siege. As part of the Silverymoon Alliance, I grieve and lament the situation. I’ve already dispatched my knights to bring people to provide support. If there’s anyone here who wants to go, please announce yourselves!” Leylin exclaimed with a smile.

What came next was a difficult silence. The nobles who were seated all knew that the orcs were extremely determined. Their elite army of a hundred thousand had surrounded Silverymoon thoroughly, and going forth with the small numbers of people and horses they had was just suicide.

On top of that, Leylin’s army had low morale, and it had recently dropped even further. Hence, all these nobles wanted to do was bury their heads in their chests like ostriches.

‘The personal troops of the nobles will only be able to do as they please in their own territories…’ Leylin shook his head at this and then clapped, “Good. Next, let’s discuss the direction of my army…”

The nobles looked at each other when Leylin acted like the master here, but nobody dared oppose it. The term ‘my army’ obviously included them as well. Officially, Silverymoon had pulled back all of their forces. Leylin’s army basically had the highest power.

Alustriel had personally invested him with the title of a Baron whose power extended over generations. He was a noble who had been granted territory near the Moonwood. Who else had more power than him?

Most importantly, when it came to strength, Leylin alone would be able to eliminate the rest! The reason he had gathered them was only to nominally receive their agreement, and the nobles had all sensibly chosen to consent to this silently.

This was what Leylin had prepared. The moment any of the nobles dared go against him, he’d just slaughter them. In the turmoil of war, what would the deaths of a few people amount to?

A large military map was hung up on the wall. At the center of it was the wizards’ city, Silverymoon. The jewel of the north already had multiple red arrows around it, showing how it was surrounded.

The map also showed the surrounding terrain. Most of the lands in the north had fallen to enemy hands, coloured black. In the west were the Moonwood and Nether Mountains. As the orcs had expended most of their strength in surrounding Silverymoon, or perhaps because of the werecreatures’ Blackblood tribe, the humans were still somewhat in charge there. However, the terrifying werecreatures were already a huge threat, and these nobles were fleeing with all their might.

There were now three routes for Leylin and the rest. One was to provide support to Silverymoon selflessly, clashing head on with the orc army. The second was to stay here and pray that Silverymoon could hold on. After the war had ended, they could then settle their accounts. The last was to move to the south and abandon the territory and people here.

Leylin was more inclined towards the third. “Silverymoon is the wizards’ city after all. The queen is a Chosen, and even if the orcs can breach Silverymoon, they would have to pay a huge price, and that would make it difficult for them to go south…”

Such an explicit declaration put the nobles on the spot.

“Lord Leylin, SIlverymoon won’t be able to hang on with its strength…” While many of the nobles were greedy, despicable and shameless, there were also many who were clear-headed and unwilling to part with their territories.

This was the only source of their power! In order to protect their interests, nobles could even make a deal with the orcs or devils, and disregard the threat to their lives.

“It’s best to let the orcs and Silverymoon harm each other. This way, nobody would be able to bother with us.” There were also many who thought the same.

Leylin made a quick scan of the surroundings and understood their thoughts.

‘How childish… Do they think they’re out of the woods if they bury their head in the sand?’ Leylin snickered inside, though he knew that getting the nobles to abandon everything was not reasonable.

Thankfully, with the report just before and the joint declaration as well as the document, there was no change in whether they stayed or left. Besides, the negative effects of bringing these people along far outweighed the benefits.

“Alright! All of you can leave alone if you wish to. Any who are willing to head south with me can stay here…”

Chapter 918: Falling to the Enemy

‘Table manners’ were very important. Even Leylin needed something to cover up Cassley’s murder, those large noble families often investigated these things thoroughly.

Due to the racial conflicts, the rulers of various human nations had sent their armies to help in the north. However, even the most ferocious armies could only push the frontlines of battle closer to Yorkshire. There was basically no difference even with them around.

There was a solemness and tragedy to the paladins who were heading north alone. Leylin didn’t dwell on it long, though. Soon enough, the troops of Yorkshire brought the conditions of the city.

Leylin and the nobles could enter, but the army would have to stay outside. That was their bottom line. Leylin merely rolled his shoulders back and accepted this condition calmly.

The surge of nobles from the north had inflated Yorkshire’s prices greatly, to the point that even nobles found it hard to stomach it. Of course, there were still benefits to holding power. A luxury villa was arranged for Leylin, with everything free of charge.

Leylin then met the Marquis Lancet he had heard about so often in rumours.

“Baron Leylin, I’ve long since wanted to see the rare wizarding genius of the north!” Lancet had a head of silver, curled hair, and a poised appearance. After seeing Leylin, even the wrinkles on his face smoothed out. He had evidently conducted a thorough investigation before meeting him.

“I am extremely grateful for the Marquis’ generosity when the north has fallen into enemy hands!” Leylin’s behaviour astounded the marquis. Most geniuses were arrogant, but Lancet saw none of that in Leylin’s expression.

On top of that, he lacked the inflexible thinking and apathy so common to wizards, and instead seemed more like a scholar. His bearing even surpassed a few of the grandmasters he had paid a great deal of money to hire.

Lancet poured Leylin a glass of dark red wine, looking sorrowful. “Before we get to the formal discussions, I wish to tell the Baron something with regards to the north…”

“Has Silverymoon fallen?” Leylin’s eyes glinted as he asked indifferently.

Lancet’s hand halted pouring the wine for an instant, causing the stream of liquor to break off for a while. He then sat in front of Leylin as if nothing had happened, a profound look in his eyes. “It seems like you have your own intelligence channels, Baron… Indeed, Silverymoon fell just yesterday…”

……

One day ago, the north. Silverymoon City.

As the chief advisor to Silverymoon, Scholar Buren who was like the prime minister was watching Alustriel with worry in his eyes. She looked tired, her brows furrowed. The sight was heartbreaking.

Forgetting her real age for a moment, if one were to judge her based on her mental age and outer appearance, the life and death of the city had been put into the hands of a little girl. Scholar Buren thought this was just too cruel.

While Alustriel had great reputation and charm, she was not a qualified leader. The stress of war practically overwhelmed her.

“No, the Goddess has yet to give me an answer!” Alustriel now seemed to have ended her meditation, the wrinkles on her forehead deepening.

The Goddess of the Weave, being a greater god, was the cornerstone that maintained SIlverymoon’s existence. Now, however, she was rejecting Alustriel’s prayers and requests for help, which made things clear.

“It’s not just any god. Has even the mighty Mystra abandoned us?” Seeing this, even a powerful legendary wizard like Buren felt his heart sink.

*Roar!* The cries of distant beasts travelled into the palace, causing Alustriel’s expression to change.

“It’s starting again,” Scholar Buren sighed. A teleportation gate opened up, and Alustriel stood on the city walls next to Buren.

“Long Live Her Majesty! Long Live Her Majesty!” Seeing her appearance, the morale of the city guards soared. They were now full of hope.

Alustriel had displayed her might as the Goddess’ Chosen these past few days. Only the orc emperor Saladin could contend with her.

‘But the queen is the leader, her responsibilities do not lie here. Battling the opposing high-ranked Professionals should be the job of the military wizards!’ Scholar Buren sighed inside. While Alustriel had immense charm and strength, this queen was still too inexperienced.

Buren watched the orcs’ formation under the city. There were huge siege vehicles and terrifying behemoths with them, and the worry in his heart increased. Even with the aid of all sorts of smelted items, as well as high-ranked and legendary wizards in charge, they were now at a disadvantage.

‘We have too few men… Few in the Silverymoon Alliance contributed much, and the troops that were sent out with orders didn’t bring any others back. Less than half of the original city guards that could take on the most rigorous missions returned…’

Scholar Buren thought it over, and then proposed to Alustriel, “Your Majesty, things have gotten this bad already. Please consider my suggestion!”

“No need for that. I can’t abandon my people, especially at a time like this!” Alustriel resolutely interrupted Scholar Buren’s words.

“Look!” She pointed downwards, “There are still so many of my people, so many of those who believe in me here. How could I abandon them and leave?”

Alustriel’s face flushed red, an even greater might exploding forth from her body. Rafiniya quietly looked in the queen’s direction from a corner of the crowd. Powerful energy undulations were radiated outwards, and the golden light shining on her made her feel comfortably warm.

‘Is this grace? No! This… It’s a large-scale buff!’ Rafiniya’s face flushed, and she felt as if she could slay a dragon right at that moment.

Alustriel’s little face was now pale. Even with support from the large-scale magic formations under the city walls, such a large boost was still difficult to cast. She had even used up some divine force for this. However, she wouldn’t appear frail. The young, girlish voice resounded, “We will achieve victory!”

“Victory!” “Victory!” “Victory!” Countless troops roared.

Rafiniya was moved, her eyes glimmering with sparkling tears. As she watched the paladins around her whose faces were just as flushed as hers was, eyes showing their firm resolve, she felt as if she had truly chosen the perfect path for herself.

‘This is the work of justice! Fighting for well-being and happiness!’ Rafiniya clenched her fists tightly, ‘Leylin… Someday, he’ll definitely come to realise his mistakes and regret this!’

*Roar!* At this moment, the orc emperor Saladin had arrived at the frontlines.

“A large-scaled buff?” There was no emotion in Saladin’s eyes right now. The maids and other orc leaders beside him all lowered their heads respectfully, not daring to move at all.

“All preparations are done. Our master’s strength can descend at any time!” A few high-ranked priests headed over as they reported.

“Very good!” Saladin suddenly took a step forward. The earth’s surface seemed to tremble as a terrifying might burst forth from his body.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* Saladin’s body abruptly increased in size, and in an instant he turned into a miniature giant, five metres tall and still growing. His clothes, armour and all items shattered with the violent movements.

This was the legendary spell— War God’s Possession!

Finally, Saladin turned into a terrifying giant over fifty metres tall. Only one item scaled up with him, the Thunder God’s Hammer!

“Lightning Strike!” Rafiniya heard Saladin’s voice loud and clear. The loud, horrifying sound caused her eardrums to tremble, with a stinging pain.

Afterwards, berserk lightning filled the skies and tore the clouds apart as everything gathered at the battle hammer.

Lightning from the highest of heavens rumbled as it seemingly turned into a terrifying dragon, releasing the most powerful flames of its fury!

Violet! As if a new world was being born, violet light quickly spread around the area. Under this light, the city gates and everything else completely melted away…

……

“Just like that, the orc emperor Saladin brazenly went against the agreement in the continent and used a terrifying legendary spell. With the boost of a divine weapon, he defeated Silverymoon thoroughly in one shot.”

Marquis Lancet narrated calmly. However, from how he suddenly gulped down a mouthful of wine, it seemed that this strength of legends still caused terror to well up within him. Leylin listened to everything he said. While he knew this would happen, he was still unclear on the exact process, “Then… Where is Her Majesty Alustriel now?”

Seeing Leylin getting the main point, the Marquis’ eyes were full of praise, “It is said that her whereabouts are unknown, but there is a large possibility she survived. After all, the vitality of those with divine force is frightening…”

With Alustriel’s strength, few would be able to find her if she truly wanted to conceal herself. However, based on her personality, she was unlikely get back on her feet quickly after this. She would probably require a long time to recoup.

At the end, Lancet intentionally brought up something, “Leylin, I have a wine reception here the day after tomorrow. I hope you can come!”.

Chapter 924: Wizard Tower

Everything was happening in secret. The baron’s enemies were not so easily dealt with, and the person most qualified to do so was Leylin.

He now had control over the Scarlet Tigers and had even gotten rid of the Baltic archipelago. Baron Jonas had his suspicions about this, but the father and son maintained a tacit understanding and did not lay it bare.

“I understand!” Leylin nodded. In his opinion, the return of the Barbarians and the rise of the devils and demons was only to be expected. The period post calamity was a golden period for churches to expand, but so it was for demons and devils as well. The ripples caused by the Pirates’ Tide still hadn’t faded.

“And Cyric?” Leylin’s eyes shone. He had some things to settle with this church. What they had done before had left Leylin slightly discontent.

“I’d be at ease handing all this over to you. If there’s anything you need, do tell me. Prioritise your safety, I don’t want to lose an outstanding heir. Is that understood?” Baron Jonas spoke seriously.

“Yes, father!” Leylin nodded.

“Good! Go meet your Master Ernest. He has a surprise for you!” Baron Jonas had a smile on his face, “Spend more time with your mother now that you’re back. We can’t delay your wedding either…”

At the mention of this, Leylin felt a headache coming on. He found an excuse to leave the study room.

……

It was night, and Port Venus still had lights everywhere.

At the very least, there were huge torches burning at the pier, where ships hurried to unload their cargo. This would have been unimaginable in huge cities. With the labour and physical resources in the dark ages, the cost of illumination in the night was a huge burden.

Till now, Leylin had only seen one city capable of using lights to brighten the area, and that was Silverymoon. Port Venus was now added to that list. It was a pity that the port was several times smaller than Silverymoon, so it wasn’t comparable.

“It’s beautiful, isn’t it?” Ernest watched the pier that seemed to glow with stars, his voice showing his awe.

“This is the result of the effort of father and everyone else!” Leylin spoke in a very humble manner. He could tell the delight and fondness in his master’s tone. Ernest probably treated this like his second home.

“The more prosperous Port Venus is, the more people will come. The crime rate here is now almost at a stage that even the guards can’t deal with it. The Mercenary Association and the Warriors’ and Thieves’ Guilds will definitely increase the pressure on public security, as will the requests of other churches…”

Ernest stated calmly, while Leylin listened close. He was controlling the situation from afar, and what he knew was surely less than what the wizard who had been staying here all this while did.

“That’s why we planned to build this, right?” Leylin looked at the main part of the huge wizard tower, a smile on his face, “Once the wizard tower is built, those mice in the sewers should stop…”

Ernest nodded in agreement. The two of them were on a mountain next to the Port Venus, one that had a clear view of the port. The general structure of a wizard tower had already been built at the top of the hill.

With the power of wizard towers, even the most low-levelled wizard would still be able to control Port Venus without trouble. It would also serve to intimidate others. After all, a wizard tower was comparable to a high-ranked wizard! This was a loyal slave that was fully controlled and knew no exhaustion.

“Thanks to the batch of resources you brought back and our investment later on, we’ve finally built the main body…” Ernest caressed the sturdy body of the tower, a smile on his face.

“Want to see her?”

“Of course!” Leylin smiled and nodded.

The construction of a wizard tower would require an investment of at least two million kronas. Some high-ranked wizards might not be able to amass so much wealth even if they worked hard for centuries. There were plenty who were willing to sell themselves for it.

If not for Leylin looting the Baltic archipelago and retrieving the materials meant for the wizard tower, as well as the Faulen Family’s investment from Port Venus, the wizard tower would not have been built so quickly.

“The main material for the wizard tower is granite and wizards’ alloy. It’s a total of 32 metres tall.” Ernest brought Leylin into the wizard tower, making introductions as they walked.

“The strengthening runes and defensive spell formation of the tower have been completed. The mithril and adamantine that you brought have been completely used up, and we’ve even had to buy a new batch. The tower itself has seven floors, with the basement, drawing room, storage room, laboratory, leisure room…” Ernest seemed to be very invested in the tower.

He abruptly pulled a large door open. It was empty and very dry. “This is the storage room. It can hold enough rations to last two hundred people a year. There’s eternal warmth and maintenance spell formations, so the food won’t go bad. You can cultivate fruits and vegetables in the garden…

“Also, the spell formation connecting the four main elemental pools has been completed. Energy can be unceasingly drawn from the four elemental pools, and the pure water from the water elemental pool can create a water cycle…”

At this point, Ernest looked to be hesitating, but still spoke, “Also, based on what you said you wanted in the letter, the dimensional summoning spell formations and negative energy pools have been set up in the basement…”

As a traditional wizard, Ernest had a natural hatred for these things, but could not prevent this. Advancing from higher ranks to the realm of legendaries definitely required research in these two areas. He believed that Leylin knew to restrain himself and not deal with devils and demons, and was rather at ease.

“Of course, with your current strength and talent, you’ll be able to use these facilities within ten years…” Ernest spoke with confidence.

In his eyes, the strength Leylin displayed gave him a very good chance of becoming a high-ranked wizard within ten years. That speed alone would have been shocking.

After all, the advancement of wizards was not similar to other close combat professions or priests. There was a lot of accumulation required, which was also why many young wizards were weak.

“You didn’t call me here to discuss this, right master?” Leylin smiled. He had not placed his wizard ranking emblem at his chest. He hadn’t verified that he was rank 15 even in Silverymoon, so he was being treated like a rank 12 to 13 wizard. For Leylin’s age, that was already outstanding.

“Yes… uh… how do I explain this…” Ernest had a flush on his face.

“The structure of the tower has been completed. What’s next is vitalising the energy core and the constructing the tower genie…”

Ernest muttered, “You know that vitalising a tower requires at least a rank 7 spell, a high-ranked wizard is necessary… While we can discuss this after you’ve advanced, the safety of Port Venus is of immense importance. We have to activate it immediately…

“I think we should consider inviting a high-ranked wizard to cast an Activate Intelligence spell. Of course, they’d have to join the Faulen Family, sign an oath with the Styx and hand over the tower afterwards. However, that would only be used for observation for a while. This level of strength alone will arouse the interest of many high-ranked wizards, and can greatly increase the number of trump cards we have… After all, a wizard above rank 15 is a true high-ranked spellcaster!”

Ernest was very inarticulate at the beginning, but he spoke smoothly later. The control of a wizard tower was a sensitive subject, and anyone would hope for their own people to have it. Sadly, both he and Leylin were quite a distance away from meeting that requirement.

“While I’m still a low-ranked wizard, I never thought there’d come a day that a wizard’s tower would be right in front of me, yet I’d be unable to control it…” Ernest laughed wryly as he spoke.

“Bring me to the core room,” Leylin nodded calmly.

Upon hearing this, Ernest brought Leylin to the top floor and entered a narrow room, “Everything has been prepared. All that’s left is a high-ranked wizard who can cast a rank 7 spell…”

Ernest sighed, but it was followed by a look of surprise as Leylin walked to the core of the spell formation.

“Wha- what are you doing? Did you think you can start the tower?” Ernest was stunned as he watched Leylin place his hand on the core control crystal.

“While what you say makes sense, it’s too dangerous to let others control the wizard tower. Even with the restrictions from the oath, it can’t be guaranteed that the outsider won’t have their own methods. This could be fatal to the safety of the family’s land…” Leylin spoke.

While an oath to the Styx was binding, in his experience there were many ways to find loopholes. Of course, that would’ve been their course of action if left with a choice. However, he already met the requirements, so why would he give the control of the tower away?

“Alright, alright, little Leylin… I know you’re not resigned to this, but… I! Oh, god…” Ernest had been advising him while finding this hilarious, but then gaped immediately after.

Chapter 926: Legendary Item

The Barbarians had once been Leylin’s ally. However, with the defeat of Marquis Louis, the relationship between them had gradually turned into a competition. Leylin had no guilt whatsoever of beating them. If they had a chance, he was sure that they would do everything in their power to destroy his own organisation.

This was the law on the outer seas. Cruelty and logic prevailed, not allowing for a whit of emotion.

“Mm, the Barbarians are a large issue. When the imperial navy still existed, they lay low for a period of time. Now, though, they’re suddenly appearing and even attacking our commercial groups!”

Any huge merchant would hate these pirates to the bone. Only nobles could plunder, how dare those barbarians steal their things? Although there was a bias here, this was the general thought process.

“Don’t worry, they won’t be active for long!” Leylin promised.

……

“Good morning, Lord Wizard!”

In the blink of an eye, numerous days had passed. Within the wizard tower, a freckled girl saw Leylin approach and put down the book in her hands, shyly greeting him.

“Good morning! Your name is… Dylia, right? Work hard!”

Leylin answered without thought, and the girl instantly turned red, “Yes! I’ll do that!”

Leylin was not surprised by her attitude. Her rough skin and hands full of calluses made it obvious that this apprentice was a commoner.

If not for Ernest finding her talent at wizardry by coincidence and Leylin just finishing his wizard tower, it was impossible for her to get here. However, with all these coincidences piling up, the girl’s fate had changed.

She was destined to work the fields, marry someone, endure the rough treatment of her husband, and rack her brains over her children. However, now there was another possibility. She could become a wizard, serving a noble master and changing her fate! This hope alone was enough for commoners to fight hard for.

As he thought about this, Leylin placed the spellbook he had copied into the shelves, and then left the library.

The wizard tower had become more lively. After gaining permissions to a few laboratories and a pass to go around most areas, Ernest had moved in and brought five or six apprentices. The tower had been constructed like a fort, so it could guard two hundred people inside it for numerous years without much effort. It was completely possible for a few apprentices to live there, and even very comfortable.

Not bothering Ernest, who had become slightly deranged, Leylin came to the core smelting room at the upper levels.

“Tower genie, how’s the progress with the items?” Leylin asked indifferently.

A projection of the tower genie’s appearance formed, and it spoke to Leylin respectfully. “Master! The Red Dragon’s Sword has already been completed. What’s left is the last bits of processing and pyretic nourishment.”

“Good!” Leylin nodded, lips curving at an angle. He’d evidently thought of Ernest’s look when he gave him these legendary materials.

This was a dragon, a peak being in the World of Gods! Killing a legendary mature dragon required one to brave perilous dangers, and if not for the thousand elites and Tiff who was a legendary himself, it would’ve been basically impossible for Leylin to eliminate the red dragon. His life would probably have been lost as well.

Of course, once the dragon was successfully slain the profit was immense. Just the legendary materials from the red dragon was enough for any alchemic wizard to go green in envy.

“The Ring of Wizardry and a few other items before now give me very little benefits. I’ll need to crush the Barbarians as well, and things might be troublesome if I don’t have a few items I can use…”

Leylin came before a large petri dish, producing a red long sword from the silver solution. The slender blade of the sword emanated piercing light, and it had a beautiful arch. The hilt even had carvings of the red dragon. By design this was a sword for women, the draconic pride that was its motif causing a content smile to arise on Leylin’s lips.

The A.I. Chip projected the related information to Leylin. [Item Name: Red Dragon Sword. Length: 91.5cm. Weight: 2512g. Materials: Red Dragon Bones, Dragon Scales, Refined Metal. Item Effects: 1. Armour Break. 2. Sharpness. 3. Fireball (3 uses a day) Description: This is a sword made with materials from a legendary red dragon. Based on the categorisation of this world, it has entered the ranks of legendary items! This item has a terrifying sharpness and ability to pierce through armour. In the face of this sword, most defences are frail. The blade also seems to have a mysterious magic that thirsts to drink the scalding blood of its enemies.]

‘A legendary item? Not bad!’ Leylin nodded and wiped the sword clean. He then sheathed it in the dragonscale scabbard. This was not for him, but a gift for someone else.

With Leylin’s attainments as a grandmaster in alchemy in the Magus World, and mixed in with his skills of the World of Gods and the runes of the arcanists, there was no difficulty in creating legendary items.

‘But it consumes so much magic… I can only complete it with the help of the wizard tower…’ Leylin then headed to an area outside two glass rooms. Through the thick, reinforced crystal glass, he could see a dark red leather armour and a magic staff with a strange shape at the middle, enjoying the powerful force being channelled into them.

‘The effects of fusing alchemical methods from the two worlds has quite good…’ Leylin pondered over this once he witnessed the scene. If he were to do this based entirely on the methods in the World of Gods, creating a legendary item would require a lot of time. It would be astounding for him to make even one.

Now, however? The progress and innovation in production techniques was definitely a huge source of motivation for him. Leylin suddenly recalled something from his previous world and shook his head. Memories of that time were far too distant from him.

‘Perhaps the techniques there aren’t entirely useless. With my capabilities, I can begin to attempt fusing different laws together with various techniques. The antimatter experiment at the end would be very powerful even in the World of Gods…’

The A.I. Chip continued to twinkle, and the attributes of the two items were projected in front of Leylin.

[Item name: Dragon Armour (Incomplete) Weight: 1599 g. Materials used: Dragon Leather, Dragon Scales, Siren’s Hair, Rainbow Feathers. Magic Effect: Can materialise Mage Armour II twice a day. Description: This is a powerful defensive armour. As the leather of a legendary dragon was used in its making, it is immune to most low-ranked spells. It can also adapt well to the spells of a wizard.]

Though a legendary red dragon had a lot of leather, not much of it was the true, essential portion. Leylin had extracted the best parts to make this legendary armour, and the rest of the leather could only be used to make regular exemplary items, even if their defence wouldn’t be too bad.

Leylin then focused on the staff in the alchemy room, which had a strange structure. It had slender red scales on its body, and at the head was something similar to a dragon’s claw that held onto a large red crystal. Within it was the faint image of a red dragon, roars still resounding.

[Item name: Snarling Red Dragon Staff (Incomplete) Rank: Legendary 1. Length: 91.5cm. Weight: 3500g. Materials: Dragon Crystal, Dragon Soul, Dragon Bones, Dragon Blood, Dragon Scales.]

[Item Abilities: 1- Storage. This staff can store spell slots. Currently empty: Rank 7 (1), Rank 6 (3), Rank 5 (5) 2.Spell: Can materialise Dragon’s Breath thrice a day. 3. Ability: Dragon Aura Domain. 4. Burning. By extracting the power of the dragon soul, one can create a single-use legendary spirit attack (This will harm the dragon soul).]

[Description: This is a magic staff made entirely with materials from a legendary red dragon. Its creator has unreasonably confined the dragon’s soul inside it, giving it unbelievable strength. However, this will lead to the hostility of the dragon race.]

It was evident that this Snarling Red Dragon Staff was the true star of the show. Many wizards would covet this legendary staff, but few would have the gall to use it. Even Leylin had made up his mind not to use it unless things were dire, and then he would silence those who saw it.

The dragon race in the World of Gods were quite powerful. Those ancient or primordial dragons were beings the gods themselves did not have the courage to provoke.

‘The essence of a legendary dragon gave me the materials for three legendary items.’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘This is a very high yield. Other alchemist grandmasters would not be able to do this, and even I feel quite emotional…’

‘In addition… its bloodline seems to be quite useful…’ Even Leylin had to admit that everything on the legendary dragon’s body was a treasure. It was no wonder that they were coveted by all sorts of races.

“These two legendary items should be enough to allow me enter the realm of legendaries…” Leylin was rather satisfied with his work. “Once they’re complete, I should head into the outer seas and settle debts with the Barbarians…”

Leylin’s eyes suddenly glinted with a chilly look. He had plans for the outer seas, and it would be a great foundation to build on in his ascent to godhood. No outsiders could get a share of this!

Chapter 927: Dragon Warlock

For many sailors, the deep sea regions were fearsome areas comparable to the abyss and the nine hells. In the darkness under the peaceful blue surface were numerous strange sea monsters, greedily staring up at the ships. Or rather, at the beings on the surface.

If a ship was destroyed and a sea monster were to be around, there was basically no chance of survival. For sailors, those who had conquered the deep seas were the truly strong, worthy of reverence.

Night deepened, and the gloomy surface of the sea was like a terrifying monster opening its mouth, waiting for its chance to devour everything. Its peace was broken by a tremendous pirate fleet, cruising along with the might of a conqueror.

On the largest magically armoured ship was a crimson flag. The flag seemed to be dyed by blood, and had the symbol of a skull and dagger on it. In the Dambrath outer seas, this was a terrifying legend!

The Scarlet Tigers! They had wiped out the original Tigershark Pirates and Black Skeletons, and were a large-scaled pirate group that had taken over the outer seas.

It was rumoured that the leader of the Scarlet Tigers, the Scarlet Witch, was a demon of the abyss. She bathed in the fresh blood of the living, using their pumping hearts to maintain her strength and beauty. At this point, the Scarlet Witch’s name had even reached the mainland, terrifying little kids into tears at night.

This Scarlet Witch whose fearful name had spread far and wide was currently on deck, looking into the distance with a look of anticipation in her eyes.

“Long time no see, Cousin Isabel!” A dark figure descended from the skies like a night hawk, bringing with him furious winds.

Leylin observed his cousin, who seemed to have changed a lot yet not at all. She greeted him with a smile.

“So you only remember me now? It’s been four years. Four whole years!” Isabel exclaimed maliciously, though her eyes seemed to be glimmering.

Afterwards, she yelled at the pirates who had been alerted, “What did you come out for? This isn’t an invasion. Get back, or I’ll hang you on the flagpole tomorrow for three whole days and then cut off your dick to go with some alcohol!”

It was evident that Isabel held high prestige here. After the roaring came the sounds of doors and windows closing.

“Hehe… you haven’t changed at all.” Leylin rubbed his nose and laughed. Isabel was still the same as she had been years before, though her long golden hair become much shorter, and she was specifically hiding an area on her forehead.

“My lord!” “My lord!” A few other leaders rushed to the deck, looking emotional.

“Mm. Karen, Robin Hood, Ronald! Have you all been well?” Leylin called them by name, one by one.

“Gods, everything is going well!” Robin Hood had been a soldier of Leylin’s family, and was the first to speak.

“Good! Let us have a meeting after this.”

Isabel rudely sent the other leaders away and stared at Leylin, causing some fear. “Where’s my gift?”

“This?” Leylin laughed wryly and produced the Red Dragon Sword. “I think it suits you well. I already told you when we talked…”

*Rumble!* Isabel didn’t even listen till the end. The moment she saw the dragonscale scabbard, her eyes twinkled with a wondrous look. She was almost barbaric as she snatched the sword from Leylin’s hands before moving back.

*Roar!* A slight draconic aura burst out, accompanied with the enraged howls and roars of a dragon. Red light flashed on the blade, bringing with it traces of flames.

“Legendary! A legendary item that has even gone through an excellent enchantment!” Isabel had been a pirate for many years, and her judgement was much better than before. She saw through it instantly.

“What do you think? Do you like it?” Leylin asked.

“It’s mine!” This question didn’t need answering. Just Isabel’s expression alone was enough.

“Mm, it’s good that you like it. Also, we have some things to discuss. Shall we go to your room?” Leylin suggested, and he saw the flush that rose on her face. He could not help but rub his nose awkwardly, feeling like he had been impudent.

However, Isabel still did as Leylin wished and brought him to her bedroom. The pink curtains, the canopy, the crimson carpet, and works of art with varying styles mixed together to form a unique look. These were all the treasures that Isabel had stolen.

A pungent incense entered Leylin’s nostrils, concealing the smell of the sea. Females were obviously more attentive than males.

“Actually, I’ve come prepared to solve the issues with the Barbarians in one go. Odge and Tillen seem to be stepping out of line lately…” Leylin’s eyes were trained on Isabel, “But by the looks of it, there’s something more important that we have to deal with now.”

He went forward, lightly pushing away her fringe. A few strange scales had already appeared at the edge of the girl’s fair forehead.

“Has the demonification already come that far?” Leylin frowned slightly.

“Don’t worry about it. I’m actually feeling the summons from the abyss even more. Who knows, I might just fall at any moment…” Isabel had a resolute look on her face.

“Mm, I feel that as well. But this doesn’t seem difficult to solve!” Leylin stroked his chins, and saw the hope in her eyes.

“Well, do you trust me?” Leylin sincerely looked into her eyes.

“Who if not you?” Isabel lowered her head.

“Good!” With a flick of Leylin’s finger, a barrier silently appeared. “I need you to cooperate with me fully and do as I tell you to, alright?” he instructed her carefully, a test tube containing golden-red blood appearing in his hands.

“Mm!” Isabel nodded her head slightly, suddenly blushing a little.

……

The morning sun rose from the east, shining golden ripples looking like fish scales on the sea’s surface.

“How do you feel?” Leylin looked to be slightly tired, though his eyes were still bright.

“I feel… better than I ever have before!” Isabel touched her forehead. The scales had disappeared, and her original short golden hair had turned a dark red like fire.

“Thankfully, you didn’t choose to sell your soul and were only corrupted by the demonification. That can be concealed and neutralised with a more powerful bloodline…” Leylin evaluated.

“I never thought you could even transform people into sorcerers!” Isabel looked towards Leylin, as if remembering something embarrassing from the night before, and lowered his head. In front of her cousin, she truly no longer had any secrets.

“Not a sorcerer, but a Warlock! A Dragon Warlock!” Leylin corrected her.

“Warlock?!” Isabel tested out this word, “I’ve never heard of it before…”

“I’ve combined the legendary red dragon’s blood with your body. From hereon, you will control the power of the red dragon, and can even awaken magic abilities!” Leylin had no plans to explain further and handed a meditation technique to Isabel. “You can try training in this ‘Dragon King’s Mystic Might’ in the future. It will do you good…”

“Dragon King’s Mystic Might? Do sorcerers— no, Warlocks need to train?” Isabel expressed her confusion.

“Of course!” Leylin nodded sternly.

This Dragon King’s Mystic Might was obviously not the high-grade meditation technique Leylin had gained in Twilight Zone. It was one he’d refined with that as a foundation. Leylin had actually found information on it from the ruins of the arcanist, and with the A.I. Chip’s help integrated the two.

It could be said that with the meditation technique and bloodline modification, Isabel now had the potential to surpass sorcerers! In addition, the blood of the legendary red dragon would be enough to suppress the demonification for a long time.

“Alright! Let’s go meet your cute underlings!” Leylin got up to leave, and Isabel followed closely behind. For high-ranked Professionals like them, a night without rest was no issue at all.

Pulling the door open, they arrived at the deck and saw the dubious smiles on the faces of Robin Hood, Karen and the others. Evidently, news of Leylin spending a night in her room had spread and given rise to some associations.

Unexpectedly, Isabel had not gotten mad but instead rejoiced inside. However, she still glared at them icily.

“Alright! There’s a lot to do, so let’s discuss it over breakfast!” Leylin had long since passed the age of caring about this, and waved his arms with vigour, bringing everyone to the dining room.

Making use of this opportunity, he got more familiar with the leaders under Isabel. He knew some of them very well, but was complete strangers with some others. They must have joined some time after he left.

“We’ve been developing well in these few years, especially after the imperial navy left. There are no opposing organisations left in the outer seas…” Isabel spoke with pride, “We now have twenty large warships with over 1500 men…”

“Mm, you did very well!” Leylin listened closely and got a better understanding of the recent growth of the Scarlet Tigers, “How about the Barbarians?”

At the mention of this, Isabel immediately turned grim.

Chapter 928: Conspiracy

“Those darned barbarians are the only forces with the guts to oppose us. Half a month ago, they even launched a surprise attack on one of our fleets and sunk three of our pirate ships…” Isabel looked glum, “Also, they even control Pirates’ Cove. We’re barred entry!

“That’s not all. I have a feeling that they have something to do with the cause of turmoil in the outer seas recently. I mean the power of the abyss and hell, as well as the church of the God of Murder…” The half-drow assassin, Karen, supplied.

The female assassin had hidden her aura and would now be a Professional of at least rank 10. Now, she was impatient to show off in front of Leylin. This was obviously inappropriate, and under Isabel’s gaze Karen quickly fell back.

“Interesting… Interesting…” Leylin sat upright. His devilish ability to grasp the hearts of others allowed him to understand his underlings’ state of mind easily.

‘Karen… She was discriminated against because of her background and prior relations with me. What is she trying to show me? That’s not all… I have a feeling that she’s hiding something. This anxiety… is her race trying to rely on me for protection…?’

Leylin sent her a cursory glance, but this only made the half-drow nervous.

“My– My apologies, master!” The half-drow apologised miserably, tears almost flowing from her eyes. Leylin’s nonchalant gaze seemed to look straight into her heart, causing her little schemes and calculations to disappear.

The half-drow suddenly had a thought, ‘Perhaps even the matriarchs in the Underdark don’t have such terrifying gazes…’

“Isabel is the person I’ve assigned power. Before she gives permission, none of you are to speak out. Is that understood?” Leylin’s voice was low, “If this happens again…”

“No, I swear! I promise that there will never be another time!” Karen immediately knelt down, kissing the back of Isabel’s hand. “Please forgive me…”

“Forget it.” Isabel nodded. Leylin’s attitude satisfied her, and that was enough.

There had been a slight mishap with the female assassin, but after that the scope of the discussion returned to the Barbarians.

……

Pirates’ Cove.

Though the imperial navy had tried to wipe out this place several times, Pirates’ Cove still showed no signs of weakening.

Due to the Faulen Family quickly taking over trade of the Baltic Archipelago, the original golden shipping routes had not been abandoned. There were still merchant ships with all sorts of wealth on them travelling here, and the environment after the chaos of war made this a playground for pirates. Pirates’ Cove even showed signs of gaining more prosperity.

In a secret room in the barbarian inn. The Barbarians’ leader, Odge, was seated imposingly with the eternally beautiful Madam Tillen at his side. Now, however, her eyes were wary, and the fox tail at her back had been tucked in. Her fur stood on end, as if she was on her guard against some terrifying enemy.

Facing these two was a young noble with a head of black hair wearing gentlemanly attire.

“Well then… are the two of you interested in my proposition?” The young noble had a kind smile on his face, the manners showing his noble education. It felt refreshing, but Madam Tillen did not seem to be at ease.

This was because the youth in front of her was a devil! Compared to those evil beasts that specialised in seducing human souls and leading to their fall, the barbarians and goblins were great people.

To Madam Tillen’s knowledge, devils were always the synonyms of swindling and craftiness. This made her even more vigilant. The young noble in front of her did not seem to notice her fluctuating thoughts, and still continued on cooly, “Based on what I know, the genius wizard and successor of the Faulen Islands, Leylin Faulen, has returned. He also seems to have roped in some external support and activated their wizard tower, making Faulen Island a natural stronghold…”

A port with a wizard tower guarding it was entirely different from one without. Even Odge began to look grim. Leylin had become a high-ranked wizard in the Netheril Ruins, and had met with the chaos of war with the orcs. There was no way to determine his ranking. Naturally, this news did not spread.

“Leylin…?” Madam Tillen suddenly thought back to that little imp that had repeatedly caused her trouble, and could not help but tighten her grip.

He was like the devil in front of her, they were all very elegant and slippery characters. When it came to their own profits, they would never budge.

‘No… Leylin Faulen, the heir of the Baron, seems to be more terrifying than this devil…’ This thought suddenly rose in Tillens mind. This was a woman’s intuition. There was no reason at all, and she frowned.

“Not only does he have large armed fleets, he also has help from the pirates. On top of that, with the Faulen Family’s current status, they obviously would wish to attack the pirates in the outer seas to ensure that trade routes and trading remain unimpeded. Hence, you shall be their first target. You need my strength!”

The young devil spoke slowly, traces of darkness flashing in his eyes. Meanwhile, he was also astonished at the pressure the return of this noble caused to these two. It was above his expectations.

“Your name.” At this moment, Odge suddenly rose from his seated position and watched this devil from above.

“Neville! You can call me Neville. I would be happy to serve you…”

The devil named Neville had a sincere smile on his face. Behind his handsome features that could cause young noble ladies to go crazy Madam Tillen saw a poisonous snake. She could not help but shiver.

Blood-red flames rose, and the young devil bowed elegantly, disappearing with the teleportation flames. After determining that he had left, Madam Tillen set up an isolation spell formation.

“I think… We shouldn’t work together with devils. You know how they are…” Madam Tillen had a worried look, expressed with her eyebrows.

“We have no choice! Leylin’s faction is too powerful. We can’t go against them.” Odge spoke seriously, resulting in a wry look on Madam Tillen’s face. When it came to the strength of pirates, the Barbarians had no fear regardless of how the Scarlet Tigers emerged as a force to be reckoned with.

However, the Faulen Family was not just about the pirates! With their trade control and immense wealth, they’d rapidly set up terrifying armed fleets surpassing even Louis’ old ones. They were nobles, and in the name of protecting the shipping routes Leylin could openly expand his forces without restriction. Soon, it would surpass what Pirates’ Cove could control.

In the face of the purge on the surface and in the shadows, the Barbarians’ might in the outer seas had already begun to plunge. While it wasn’t a devastating decline, it wasn’t anything good.

At the very least, mobilising another Pirates’ Tide was impossible.

“The benefits of the Barbarians in the outer seas are never to be seized by outsiders. Never!” Odge thundered, his gigantic enchanted sabre seeming to sense its owner’s feelings and beginning to buzz along.

Odge was not just the captain of the Barbarians. He was also the protector of the barbarian race! The entire barbarian race relied on his protection to survive, which was why he would not fall back now.

“Dearest! I will help you. Even if it will send me down to hell, I’ll go there with you.” Madam Tillen had a tender look in her eyes as she hugged Odge’s arm.

……

Just as the scene was beginning to get comfortable and soft, Madam Tillen’s body suddenly trembled, rays of high-ranked communication spells shining.

“There’s another guest! It’s a priest from the God of Murder’s church!” She quickly rubbed eyes.

“Let him in.” Odge was blunt.

Soon enough, they saw the emissary. He was an old friend, the priest Leylin had seen in the Thieves’ Guild.

“I’ve brought the newest information regarding that devil!” It had to be said that when it came to scouting out information, the bunch of people under Cyric had exceptional talent.

“Speak!” Madam Tillen’s expression was icy.

“While we aren’t sure what their main body is, we can be certain that Neville comes from an organisation in the third hell…” The priest spoke slowly.

“The third hell? Is he the underling of the master of greed, Mammon?” She looked to be deep in thought. Mammon, or whatever it was, wasn’t the devil’s real name. It was only something similar to a nickname, and calling it would not alert him in any way.

“Yes! The continent has been noisy lately. The devils in the Dambrath Kingdom seem to have gone through some reshuffling of power, and it’s said that this has to do with the disappearance of Beelzebub…”

The church of the God of Murder seemed to have worked with the Barbarians more than once, to the point that they even shared such classified information.

“Also… We are working hard on making inquiries regarding the location of the Scarlet Tiger and where they get their supplies. I’m sure that there will be results in the near future! Under the gaze of my god, everything they do is clear as day!”

The priest’s eyes were bloodshot, and he looked a little sinister. This quickly dissipated.

“Sigh… Even the God of Murder can’t be trusted…” After the priest left, Madam Tillen lamented, looking worried.

“Could it be that powerful greater gods have fallen to the lower planes like in the rumours… This is truly a period of great unrest…”

Chapter 929: Emissary

Cyric was an ancient and very famous god. His divinities were in murder and conspiracy, and he was a powerful greater god. He was an ancient god that had even outlived the dusk of the gods! It was said that he knew numerous ancient stories, and had an undefined relationship with the gods, though it was one more of hate.

However, there was a strange rumour in the past few hundred years. It was that this god had gone insane, and was even becoming a demon. This deviancy could be like a matter of life and death for the gods.

Such a situation was growing more and more obvious in recent times. He was sending down all sorts of contradictory prophecies, and the priests could not get used to it.

“Sigh… the God of Murder has gone insane! The orcs in the north are building an empire, and there are traces of devils and demons in Dambrath and on the outer seas… Perhaps only the dark ages are comparable to this…” Madam Tillen sighed.

……

“I see a future with devils and demons around…” On the Scarlet Tiger, Leylin observed a crystal ball on soft goose leather padding. He was in a dark cabin, and there was a complicated look in his eyes.

Using the power of magic to foresee the future was something only astrologers and oracles could do. They had their own methods— Some used tarot cards, while others used the trajectories of celestial bodies.

Arcanists had a similar skill, and with his experience in the Magus World Leylin could do so as well.

“The opponent’s main forces should be in Pirates’ Cove. We will obtain absolute victory in this operation, and we’ll find traces of a devil there…” Leylin put the crystal ball down and used a white silk cloth to wipe at his hands, speaking with conviction..

“I think there’s something wrong with you…” Isabel was reclined on the door, looking like a loyal bodyguard, her eyes now filled with curiosity, “I don’t remember you training in prophecies. Also, the oracles don’t do as you do…”

“Hehe… This is a method I saw in Silverymoon. Don’t think too much into it…” Leylin laughed slightly. While the fact that he had become a high-ranked wizard was a secret, he had already told Isabel about it, giving her confidence.

Marquis Louis had been able to do as he wished in the outer seas with just the power of a high-ranked wizard as well. He had also absorbed the Black Skeletons and Tigershark Pirates, pushing the Barbarians to the brink. If not for Leylin’s appearance, he would probably have become the sole tyrant of the outer seas.

“But things are different now! The disaster of the Pirates’ Tide has attracted the attention of too many powerful beings…” Leylin sighed. The outer seas had not been developed that much in the past, and the terrain and organisations were very simple. A barbarian tribe was already terrific then.

However, in current terms, they were nothing. This was why Leylin was a little uneasy, attempting to predict the future.

While the World of Gods’ ability to screen this type of spells was too powerful, gods and legendary beings could do this easily. Leylin did not believe that the Barbarians could do the same.

“That’s good then…” Isabel was all smiles as she spoke, before her expression abruptly changed.

*Rumble!* *Kachak!* A slight noise sounded, along with voices of the pirates’ distress.

“Seems like they found something on the deck… Let’s go…” Leylin smiled as he followed Isabel to the deck. At this moment, the pirates were circled around two figures.

One of the two was Karen, while the other was an assassin dressed in black form-fitting clothing. Sharp blades clashed endlessly, and the winds they produced left the pirates with no courage to go forward.

“Karen, stop playing around!” Leylin tapped his finger, and a terrifying cone of flames blasted forward, accurately hitting one of the figures. The raging flames immediately devoured it.

“That was just a puppet,” Leylin look towards the mast, “Is that right?”

“Hoo hoo! As expected of the one who established the Scarlet Tigers and defeated Marquis Louis, Sire Leylin!” Laughter that sounded like an owl could suddenly be heard, and a distortion emerged from the side of the mast to form a human figure.

“We meet again, Lord Leylin! Let me introduce myself. This humble servant is Arfo, a priest of the mighty God of Murder. We met once at Pirates’ Cove!”

Arfo was currently dressed impeccably like a priest. It was unknown when he had arrived on Leylin’s ship.

“How dare you!” Karen had noticed that the figure in the flames had disappeared, revealing the original appearance of a high-ranked illusion and turned grim.

“Wait!” Just as Karen was about to charge forth, Isabel beamed as she pulled her back.

“You must be very gutsy, huh? How dare you pleay tricks on my people?” Isabel stared at Arfo, her eyes narrowing dangerously.

“The great name of the Scarlet Witch has spread in the open seas. I never thought it would be such a beautiful lady,” Arfo looked to be somewhat intoxicated.

“Good, good!” Isabel took two steps forward, a smile on her face. All of a sudden, she made her move. The Red Dragon Sword was instantly unsheathed, and faint draconic roars sounded out.

A tremendous spiritual force field extended and caused all the pirates to back off, while the priest looked alarmed, “Dragon aura!”

The fiery-red sword produced a clear cry, flames spilling over in the air.

*Hss!* The priest took several steps backwards, looking terrified at the charred marks on his wrist.

“Karen is one of mine. It’s not up to you to bully her!” Isabel looked to have no intentions to kill him and slowly sheathed her sword with a snort. This immediately gave rise to gratitude in Karen’s eyes, as well as some shame.

“I never thought the Scarlet Witch wasn’t a demon sorcerer. You’re someone who inherited the blood of bloodline of a red dragon, and even have a legendary item!!” Arfo looked somewhat awkward while pondering over this.

Such a huge difference caused him to flare up at the thieves that had collected this information,

‘While there’s a similarity between demonification and becoming a red dragon, it shouldn’t be to this extent. They should be killed!’ Just a slight deviation or mistake in intel could cause irreversible consequences. Such a huge change immediately put Arfo on his guard.

“Who do you represent?” Leylin asked while snickering inside. Using Isabel’s status as a Dragon Warlock to hide her demonification had also been one of his plans. After all, red dragon sorcerers also had the ability to manipulate flames and grow scales. This would be enough to confuse people.

Demons were beings the churches would always crack down on ruthlessly. It was better not to have dealings with them. Sorcerers, on the other hand, were fine. Most importantly, Leylin had not explained anything himself. Everything had been assumed.

“I come representing the will of my god!” Arfo looked serious as he spoke.

“Do you have a prophecy from the mighty God of Murder?” Leylin looked at him, a teasing glint in his eyes. However, that only scared Arfo.

“N– No, but our bishop has recieved intent from my god!” When it came to his faith, Arfo naturally did not dare lie as he recalled the order he had received.

‘Have the outer seas descend into chaos? Just for a massacre, you provoke the two largest pirate groups? What kind of joke is this? Damn it… Ever since the bishop received god’s grace, he’s become more irritable and crazy…’ However, as a subordinate, he had no right to make any suggestions and could only carry out the orders of his superior.

“Since it’s the intention of the church, let’s have a listen shall we?” Leylin brought Arfo to a meeting room. The pirates automatically stood at two sides, eyes trained on Arfo. It was as if the moment Leylin gave the order, they would chop him into mincemeat, and that gave him immense pressure.

“Well then, emissary, what are your suggestions?”

“The dark world of the outer seas needs to be unified. We believe that the Scarlet Tigers are more suitable for this than the Barbarians.” Arfo did his best to suppress the fluctuations in his heart, saying words he did not mean. Wizards could easily detect any changes in mind or mood, and he would be seen through.

“… To show our sincerity, we are willing to provide intel regarding the Barbarians and help you achieve victory…” Arfo placed a sheepskin scroll on the table as he spoke.

“Oh?!” Leylin found this hilarious as he took a look. This was an exquisite map of the sea, marking out the location where the Barbarians resupplied. One large island had obvious blood-red marks.

“These are the areas where the Barbarians resupply. The last mark is where the barbarian tribe resides.” Arfo glanced at Leylin and spoke with confidence.

“The island where the barbarian tribe stays?” Isabel gasped, “Are you trying to create a lasting enmity with the Barbarians?”

“Since you’re already enemies, why not take it to the extreme?” Arfo spread his arms like a scoundrel.

“Haha… haha…” After a long period of silence, all he was met with was Leylin’s crazed laughter, “You said it well. You said it well! Since we’re already enemies, how about we take it to the extreme?”

Just as a smile bloomed on Arfo’s face, something happened…

Chapter 931: Altar

The raging flames continued to blaze. The piercing screams and wails never ended, accompanied by the roars and manic laughter of pirates.

Barbarian corpses piled up in this place one after the other, the blood splitting to form little streams. Once Leylin decided to attack this place, the Barbarian tribe was completely done for.

As Odge had taken most of the strong and the young, all that were left behind were a bunch of frail, elderly, female or children beings. It could be said that in front of these vicious pirates, resistance was pointless.

“This barbarian tribe seems to hold some secrets…” Leylin touched his chin, a devilishly charming smile on his face as he arrived at the heart of the tribe.

The sacrifices were made here, but it was to some unknown god. A large piece of obsidian was carved into a firm altar, on which there was a large animal skin flag and strange crimson runes.

In front of the altar were a few struggling barbarians, all of them unbelievably old.

“You of another race, do not come here!” they exclaimed. They were so frail they looked like reeds. A few youths next to them held on to the last spears and weapons they had, trembling as they aimed at the invader with eyes full of fear.

“A barbarian priest? A sorcerer?” Leylin watched these barbarians who already had one foot in the grave and sensed the power of their bloodlines. He could not help but nod to himself.

“Scram!” Arcane spells burst forth, forming terrifying large elemental hands that tore the few sorcerers into shreds. Their stubborn resistance was futile, and such strength instantly left them at a loss.

A few arcane fireballs rumbled forth, burning the rest of the barbarians to ashes. Leylin stepped over the corpses to arrive at the altar, nothing in his way.

“Spirit? Soul? Or is it without a conscient…” As he felt around the coarse notches carved into the stone, Leylin closed his eyes.

‘Are these barbarians trying to gather divinity with the power of their community?’ With tons of experience, Leylin immediately saw through their plans. The power of faith far exceeded extraordinary force. With years of worship and sacrifice, this place had already begun to develop traces of a primal power.

The altar had strong faith within it. There were spirits of powerful beings mixed in, those who had died over time, and the foundation was currently very firm. Just a bit more time could really have given birth to divinity.

This was how many ancient tribal gods had been born. A high-ranked barbarian could use this bit of divinity to cross the threshold of becoming legendary. They could even become a demigod with their advance, combining that with their faith to ignite godfire.

As he too had plans to become a god, Leylin could comprehend this thought process.

“As for the person chosen to become a god, it should be Odge, or do they have another powerful pawn? How ambitious…” Leylin stroked his chin.

There had always been many intelligent people in this world. As the outer seas did not have the attention of too many gods yet, becoming a god in the outer seas was much less difficult than in the continent. For this reason, Odge had set his sights on this area, which coincided with Leylin’s plan.

“Is this a god of the barbarian race? With how weak the outer seas are, a demigod would immediately unify the place, making it a playground for the barbarians…”

Leylin’s eyes glinted, “Very creative, but it’s a pity that you met me.”

Leylin had long since treated the outer seas of Dambrath as his territory. While the barbarians had their own plans, he would have to disappoint them.

“The spirits are valiant, guarding the tremendous power of faith and soul origin tightly.” Leylin observed the obsidian carvings and animal skin runes, an unenthusiastic look on his face, “Seems like every barbarian that dies will return to this place…”

This was the hope of a race! In the World of Gods, a race without protection from a god would not have a future. Mixed with their hot-bloodedness and sacrifices, it was both inspiring and tragic.

Leylin shut his eyes, and he felt like these spirits had encircled him. A tremendous malicious intent descended, “Scram! Scram!”

This was no illusion, but the power of rejection from the altar itself.

“Tsk tsk… How powerful does the unified heart of an entire race get, with blood sacrifices urging it on?

“Such strength! I wish to defeat it. I shall strike down the ascension of your race, and crush your hopes completely!”

A deep and dark power could instantly be seen in Leylin’s eyes.

“Devour!” Leylin willed it, and the altar creaked like it couldn’t bear the weight. The ground began to shake as if there was an earthquake, creating numerous dark holes.

Heat! Lunacy! Energy that was filled with soul force surged out from the altar like a tsunami.

“Mm…” Leylin’s expression was incomparably sinister for an instant, all sorts of emotions flashing in his eyes. The barbarian spirits were extremely crazed and vengeful, launching forth with all sorts of snarls and counterattacks as they began their last struggle.

It was a pity that this was a minor issue for Leylin. After all, he was experienced with souls.

“Hss…” The phantom of a Targaryen emerged in Leylin’s mind, and in one mouthful devoured the numerous souls and conscients. In the face of Leylin’s soul origin, the attack from these valiant souls were as weak as ants.

Varied soul force burst forth as they shattered, carrying berserk emotions and numerous memory fragments.

“A soul is a small matter. The issue is that there’s still these berserk emotions within the soul force…” Leylin sighed.

The basic requirement to absorb divinity was that one was legendary, and this was not without reason. Those who were yet to cross that threshold wouldn’t even be able to live through the attacks of these souls.

“God… I pray that you protect our barbarian race!” “You must make the barbarians the most powerful race!” “Please ensure the survival of the barbarians…” “I want to have meat. I want meat everyday…”

Such chaotic thoughts appeared in Leylin’s mind that they could cause a regular person to go mad. Even someone with legendary strength could acquire a mental disorder, the chaotic soul energy causing cracks in their memories.

However, Leylin had the A.I. Chip. He also had prior experience in this area, and his own soul origin was near rank 7. He could still take this.

“Hss…”

“I am the limitless Jörmungandr, the master that devours all things!” The Targaryen phantom appeared in Leylin’s pupils, and the power of devouring appeared, forming spirals that devoured all the chaotic soul origins at one go.

After being converted, the strength surged into Leylin’s sea of consciousness.

The A.I. Chip’s prompt sounded at this moment.

[Beep! Host has taken in a large amount of energy, determined to be soul origin essence. Absorbed!]

Large amounts of icy streams of air converged in Leylin’s mind, allowing his spiritual force to revolve rapidly.

[Beep! Host has absorbed soul energy. Spirit +1]

The accumulations of the barbarian tribe over countless years had made things easy for Leylin, and even allowed him to raise his spiritual force.

Leylin looked at his hands and murmured, “My spiritual force has increased a bit. I feel like every small increase in stats past fifteen points is a huge advance.”

The A.I. Chip’s prompts continued.

[Beep! Host’s spirit has broke through, becoming rank 16 arcanist!]

At this moment, his stats were refreshed.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 22. Race: Human, Rank 16 Arcanist. Strength: 13. Agility: 11. Vitality: 12. Spirit: 16. Arcane energy: 160 Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body. Specialties: Arcane Energy Detection, Arcane Amplification.] [Progress on Weave analysis: Level 0: 100%, Level 1: 100%, Level 2:100%, Level 3:100%, Level 4:100%, Level 5: 67.35%, Level 6:41.91%, Level 7:22.33%.] [Spell slots available: Rank 7(2), Rank 6(5), Rank 5(7), Rank 4(???), Rank 3(???), Rank 2(???), Rank 1(???), Rank 0(???)]

The advancement of arcanists required growth in both spiritual force and soul force, as well as the comprehension and sensing of arcane energy. However, with Leylin’s attainments in magic with his main body, he already surpassed many legendary arcanists. There was practically no bottleneck for his advance, and his spirit breaking through automatically led to a rise in his rank.

‘The barbarian tribe hasn’t formed a divinity yet. Just a bit of the power of faith mixed with soul energy can help me increase a rank? Perhaps I should focus on finding information in this area…’

In Leylin’s eyes, the power of faith was the power of emotion, and also soul force. There had been no bottlenecks in his advancement, and all he needed was enormous energy and his ability of devouring. When all the conditions were met, he could quickly advance.

For Leylin, this was also a shortcut to more power. As long as there were barbarian worshippers, it was possible that they had formed great soul energy like this, be it in the outer seas or various other areas in the continent.

Of course, if an altar had truly gathered divinity, Leylin would not dare devour it. If not, his own temperament could change, and that was not something trivial.

Becoming the patron saint of the barbarians would be even worse than killing himself.

Chapter 933: Kill

At this moment, the victor of another battle had also been decided.

Dragon Breath! Isabel was still in the state of her draconic transformation. The flame-red scales on her body were just like a dazzling armour that looked like freshly-cut flowers. She looked like the incarnation of a valkyrie.

After she saw that the fight would drag on, Isabel activated her bloodline abilities without the slightest hesitation.

Dragon disciples would inherit the spellcasting abilities of a red dragon. The bloodline that Isabel possessed was indeed that of a Legendary red dragon. Her spellcasting abilities would gain an extremely powerful boost.

The frantic flames consumed Odge in a flash, and no matter how determined and how tough a barbarian he was, he now let out painful wails.

Sharp! Break! From the looks of it, Isabel had immediately activated the abilities of the Red Dragon Sword.

In a flash of light and a crisp snapping sound, Odge’s peak-ranked alchemised saber suddenly split apart.

With its obstacle removed from its way, the Red Dragon Sword unhesitatingly pierced through Odge’s heart. The blazing flames destroyed all the vital organs in his body immediately.

“Ah…” Odge lowered his head with great difficulty and looked at the scorched black flesh on his chest. The light in his eyes slowly dimmed.

“…No!” Madam Tillen let out a mournful wail. She summoned energy from some unknown well of strength and unexpectedly struggled to crawl next to Odge’s body.

“My… beloved…” She held Odge’s huge lifeless hand, her eyes filled with content as if she had grabbed hold of the most precious thing in the entire world, and slowly shut her eyes.

“What a sad and beautiful romance… Isn’t it?” Looking upon them, Leylin and Isabel did not try and hinder them in any way. They quietly watched this pair of eternal soulmates pass into the afterworld.

“I really do feel that it’s rather unlike you to say that sort of thing!” After hearing Leylin’s idle comment, Isabel speechlessly rolled her eyes.

“Also… Why are you this impatient?” Isabel looked all around them. Now, all of the barbarian pirate crew had been forced into a weak position.

After Odge and Madam Tillen had been slain, the remaining barbarians grew even more frantic. In the end however, they were ultimately left to struggle in the throes of death.

After the final few barbarian shamans had died, the entire barbarian pirate crew’s destruction was inevitable.

Under such heavy suppression, the remaining barbarians crumbled at last. They jumped into the sea one after another to flee, but they were shot dead by Robin Hood who had long anticipated their retreat.

This was the trouble of naval warfare. Once they had lost, it was difficult to flee. One could only win absolutely or lose completely, but once you lost it was very difficult to free oneself.

Leylin’s luck had always been good. Rather than calling it luck, it was better to say that he had the support of planning well-devised strategies.

Isabel turned towards Leylin. Since he was the planning type, seeing him choose to pursue a fast-paced fight and unhesitatingly massacre the barbarian tribe and even use their own people as bait was unexpected. His methods stank of shortsighted vision.

“You could tell? Then there is no harm in you guessing what guards I’ve prepared in advance…” Seeing his cousin mature, Leylin’s heart was rather gratified. She could be considered his greatest helping hand in the outer seas.

“It can’t be… The priest and thief from last time!” Isabel only needed to think about it for a moment before her eyes flashed in understanding.

“Mm!” Leylin nodded, waving his hand carelessly.

A translucent wave rose, with a small water screen floating atop it.

Although there was no indication of their identity, the sailors onboard radiated a uniquely murderous aura.

“Are these… Pirates? Ones which were groomed by the god of murder? They’ve always been hiding in Pirates’ Cove, I never thought…” Isabel breathed in sharply. Until now, she had always believed that the pirate crews in the outer seas now only consisted of the Scarlet Tiger and the barbarian pirate crew. She had neglected those fragmented little pirate crews.

In reality however, these fragmented, small-sized pirate crews were the most important strength of Pirates’ Cove! They formed the majority of the ships within the Tide of Pirates.

Even a small part of those in service could assemble into a power force to reckon with.

“Luckily you discovered them already, otherwise after we engaged in mutually assured destruction with the barbarians, these locusts would descend. The consequences would have been unbearable…” Isabel said, with a grave expression on her face.

She now no longer had the slightest doubt in her mind that the church of murder were not just ordinary fishermen.

“Mm, you’re absolutely correct!” Leylin agreed with Isabel’s point.

“In reality, the reason why I avoided using Pirates’ Cove as the place for this final battle, apart from not wanting the Barbarians to have a favourable location, was to avoid these maggots of the dark…” The corners of Leylin’s lips quirked up into a sneer, “However, now that we’ve discovered their plan and made the preparations after destroying the Barbarians, what have we got to worry about?”

“What do you mean?” Isabel hesitantly asked. She stood by Leylin and smelt the special scent of bloodthirst.

“Let’s welcome them and kill them all!” Leylin’s eyes flashed as he made up his mind, “Now is the best time, the entire church of murder in the outer seas have all assembled here. Once they’re all dead, it will deal a great blow to the church.”

“A blow?” Isabel had never thought that Leylin’s ambition would grow so large to the point where he would dare to strike down a true god’s church.

‘Without getting rid of them, how can i spread my own religion…’ Leylin smiled coldly to himself, ‘There is a dead calm here in the outer seas, and the dark world’s greatest religion is Cyric. Once he is cut off from his lackeys in the secular world, all the faith in the outer seas will belong to me…”

In reality, this wasn’t a question of benefits.

Leylin had long taken a fancy to the outer seas as his base, and had prepared to establish it as a base for his followers. Thus, there had been a clash with the existing religion here.

The first was Cyric, because he had the biggest influence in the outer seas, and even had quite a few of the pirates as his followers.

In addition, this god was an evil god. Publicly fighting him wasn’t an issue, and on the contrary it would perhaps earn him favour from the benevolent gods.

It was possible to predict that in the future, Leylin would sweep across the outer seas and possibly eliminate all the native religions and evil gods in one fell swoop.

“Don’t worry, cousin. The god of murder’s influence isn’t that strong in the outer seas, and he is suppressed by many other benevolent gods… Additionally, even the Thieves’ Guild is not entirely under his control…” Leylin had acquired a lot of inside information on the three great guilds after travelling in the continent.

Cyric could only considered a shareholder in the Thieves’ Guild and not a chairman. There were still many other gods supporting the organisation from the shadows.

The Warriors’ Guild was the same, and those gods would not permit some true god to monopolise their channels.

Even the narrow-minded Wizards’ Guild was not monopolised purely by the Weave Goddess, and still had the God of Knowedge Oghma and others dividing up the goddess’ believers.

Consequently, his fight against Cyric and attacking the Thieves’ Guild were two entirely separate matters.

“So it’s like this… After all, he’s a powerful true god,” Isabel’s eyes were full of anxiety.

Needless to say, not even a weak god would willingly relinquish his own territory, let alone suffer a big loss to their believers.

Even if Cyric’s influence in the outer seas was very weak, he wielded great power on the continent. He controlled many high-ranked military powers from the shadow.

Dispatching one or two Legends over to fight for him was something that was entirely possible.

Legends were the ultimate decisive force in the entire Prime Material Plane. Once such a high-ranked expert arrived, Isabel was very aware that there was no one on her side who could offer the least resistance.

Ordinary people could not reach the realm of Legend. Everything that the Faulen family possessed was nothing in the eyes of a Legend.

“Even if a legendary comes to hurt my family, they’ll have to step over my dead body first!” Isabel declared firmly, tightly grasping her red dragon longsword.

Leylin was naturally aware of the resolution in her eyes, but did not speak of his intended plans to her.

Cyric could possibly be fly into a rage and send legendary over from the continent. However, this required time. Perhaps by then, Leylin would have already advanced to become a Legend himself!

In addition, if one wanted to develop, it was absolutely necessary to forcibly plunder the benefits that originally belonged to others. Naturally, this would lead to conflict.

Leylin had chosen the outer seas, and it was already the least controversial decision he could have made.

If he had chosen to start developing in the continent, perhaps he would have already attracted Legend-ranked experts over to take him down.

‘Ultimately, it’s all a question of strength! With enough strength, even if I take over the outer seas and slay the priests of the church of murder, what else can i do?’ Cyric and Malar, these chaotic evil gods, were already held in poor opinion by the public. Leylin could thus use any means he wanted to deal with them.

‘Choosing the right faction is of the utmost importance. Since the good faction is out of the question, I must not lose the lawful faction…’ Leylin stroked his chin as he pondered the situation meaninglessly.

“My lord! The Barbarians have been destroyed! Only five ships have been sunk, the rest are now under our control!” Just when Leylin and Isabel were about to speak, Ronald had completed his mission and bounded over to excitedly report to them. There were still traces of barbarian blood on him.

“Mm, prepare to launch plan 2! Take all the heavily damaged captive ships away. We must prepare to fight the next battle,” Leylin lightly ordered.

“Hm? We still have enemies left?” According to Ronald’s thoughts, after destroying the barbarian pirate crew, the Scarlet Tiger was now the strongest crew in the entire outer seas.

Chapter 934: Assassin

“As long as we are the kings of the outer seas, our challenges will never cease…”

Leylin smiled, “This time, it’s only a few little mice who overestimate themselves… Ronald, how do you think we should deal with them?”

“Of course we should mercilessly cut off their heads and claws, and store them in oil bottles!”

Ronald answered with a murderous spirit. For those that challenged their status and profits, there was only one answer, as was law of the pirates in the outer sea— To kill them all!

……

The shadow of the sail danced. Numerous sailors and pirates yelled as they controlled the sail and steering oar, allowing the pirate ship to sail more quickly.

Amongst them all, on the largest ship, a bishop was frowning while having a bad feeling about this.

“Rogers, make the ship faster! We need to hurry there as soon as possible!”

“Understood, master!” A pirate captain next to the bishop answered respectfully, “But this is the fastest we can go…”

“Is that so? Then why is it that the Scarlet Tiger and the Barbarians’ Tsunami can go faster than eighteen knots?” The bishop frowned.

“That’s because those are large pirate groups. Those two are also the main battleships that have been enchanted!” Rogers thought inside but did not dare speak his thoughts. After hesitating for a while, he answered as if put in a spot, “Those are individual abilities and nothing to do with the speed of the fleet…”

“No, no. You’re all trying to deceive the mighty God of Murder and his priests!” The bishop watched Rogers, facial muscles contorting to become incomparably sinister.

“No, that’s not it… Master, my loyalty to the god… No, please forgive me! Please forgive me!” The captain of the pirates, who had seen the ruthless methods of the bishop, immediately knelt while looking absolutely terrified.

This accusation was not something trivial. Recently, this bishop had become strangely bloodthirsty and insane, and would occasionally kill people because of small matters.

The captain, Rogers, was now beginning to regret responding to his recruitment.

*Pu!*

However, before he could plead and beg for forgiveness, a black dagger had slashed through his throat and cut apart his windpipe. Large amounts of blood spurted out.

Rogers’ eyes rolled back, hands grasping at his throat tightly. Blood unceasingly flowed from between his fingers, causing guttural groans from his throat.

The struggles of a dying man ended quickly. The captain, who had been lively and frisky all this while had turned into a corpse in a instant.

The surrounding pirates froze, beginning to wish they could hide their heads in their chest.

“Dispose of him! Also… increase the speed. Any questions?” The bishop glanced at the assistant pirate next to him.

“No– None at all! I guarantee you, my lord, that there’s no issue at all!”

The assistant had been scared stupid, but after seeing the chilly glint in the bishop’s eyes, he immediately felt sober and shouted.

“Then go, or else this is how you will end up!”

The bishop waved his arms, no longer caring about those pirates who were doing everything in their capabilities. Gazing into the distance, he had a profound look in his eyes.

“Damn it! That darned little noble! I shouldn’t have let him off during Pirates’ Tide!”

The bishop’s plan had been perfect, where he would provoke both sides and help the weaker one. Once the Scarlet Tigers and Barbarian Pirates weakened, his team would gobble up these two organisations and become the king of the outer sea.

He even had plans to unify the dark world and make the outer seas independent, and even construct a godly realm on the ground here!

However, all of this had been wrecked by the darned noble.

Veins began to show in the bishop’s eyes. He’d never thought that the noble would be so gutsy as to kill the emissary he had dispatched.

“Such a fearless and disrespectful being must be executed immediately, and then nail his soul on the wall of the faithless as he howls in anguish…”

As a religious person, the bishop immediately loathed Leylin with all his heart.

A person who held no respect for the gods could never become a lamb of his master. If Leylin could not be subdued in terms of his mind, then he would have to destroy his body.

From ancient times, this was how power worked.

However, he had no idea that when the gods started out, they were also just as fearless. This was the joint belief of all those heroes whose names remained in historical records

If they could not succeed, then they could only roll of a cliff and turn into the corroding soil underneath.

While he did not know of this concept, the bishop determined to have blood.

He wished to eliminate this being as soon as possible…

“There’s still time. The Barbarians must have just fought them not long ago… Even if my plans are slightly affected, the Barbarians’ strength should be enough to cause immense damage to the other side. When the time comes…”

While the bishop was immersed in his fantasies, he suddenly gaped at the dense number of sails in the distance, at the horizon.

The Scarlet Tiger ship took the lead. The bloody skull and dagger symbol had all of the pirates becoming restless.

Gods! The Scarlet Tigers was the finest pirate organisation in the outer seas. He had basically heard them expand and gain reputation, and now that they were going to fight them, it was impossible for him not to feel stressed.

*Rumble!* *Rumble!* *Rumble!*

The Scarlet Tigers unhesitatingly opened fire. Like table knives, the many ships cut the huge fleet apart into numerous fragments like butter.

Compared to how the pirates at the lowest rung depended on their elite troops and morale, the Scarlet Tigers wanted to leave their opponent far behind. This was an unequalled confidence in themselves from cutting off the heads of countless enemies.

“Do you see it now?”

Leylin handed the commanding to Ronald and Robin Hood. After all, he was more proficient in casting spells. From the many years he had not been around, he was also unfamiliar with the group.

Knowing one’s flaws and doing his best to make up for it was the attitude of those looking to improve themselves.

While I’m not suited to some roles, I can choose people who would do better and control them.

If not, someone wanted to do everything well would only tire themselves to death.

“Seems like Robin Hood and Ronald are doing very well!” Leylin said to Isabel next to him while laughing..

“They are the people you’ve nurtured. Are you trying to brag about your extraordinary foresight?” Isabel was actually very astonished. Leylin seemed to have a pair of special eyes, and he would never go wrong when it came to judging people.

However, in order not to make Leylin too cocky, she worded her answer huffily.

“No! I just…”

Just as Leylin was preparing to answer, his expression suddenly changed and he abruptly pushed Isabel aside.

A translucent figure arrived before him, as if traversing through space.

Shadow Jump! The powerful ability of a high-ranked assassin, and a high-ranked technique that could only be comprehended by assassins nearing Legendary! It allowed one to shift locations through the shadow dimension and attack enemies instantly.

This ability was basically everyone’s nightmare!

When a wizard like Leylin was in close quarters with a thief and was the one who was being attacked in surprise, the result was obvious.

This high-ranked assassin did not have any excess movements, and lacked even the elation of completing a mission successfully. There was only an apathetic and dead look in his eyes. The black dagger that held a powerful curse inside had already pierced through the defences and into the area where Leylin’s heart was.

“No!” Isabel immediately went crazy, transforming into half-dragon form and pouncing over.

The feeling of meeting flesh and the scalding blood spurting out finally gave rise to a glimmer in the eyes of the assassin. With a burst of strength in his right hand, he planned to draw the dagger out and leave.

After all, fighting with a high-ranked swordsman was not something for an assassin to do. He had assassinated the leader of the opposing side, and that was enough!

Surprisingly, he was unsuccessful in plucking the dagger out. The assassin froze, and was stunned to see flesh ‘sprouts’ appearing in ‘Leylin’’s chest. They were like the vines of plants that bundled up the dagger tightly.

Just that moment of being stunned left him no chance to flee for his life.

*Boom!* ‘Leylin’s’ chest exploded, and numerous bloody tendrils burst towards him and bound the assassin tightly. Like suckers, they were already trying to pierce through the skin and absorb fresh blood.

“Necromancy? No, no…” A shocked, coarse voice sounded from under the assassin’s veil.

“That’s just a Flesh Puppet, a spell I made just for you!”

A teleportation door opened to reveal the real Leylin.

“You should be the high-ranked assassin who tried to assassinate numerous bishops of varying churches during Pirates’ Tide, right? This is a rather great gift!”

“So… you’ve already become a high-ranked wizard!”

The assassin’s eyes did not fluctuate at all, allowing the bloody vines to take over his body. It seemed that he had lost all will to escape.

“Stop pretending. All of your methods are visible before my eyes!”

Leylin spoke coldly. Numerous spells shot out. With Dimensional Anchor locking on, even the shadow plane had been sealed.

“Damn it… you!”

Now that his last trump card had been seen through, the assassin was now no longer as relaxed before. He was then killed with Leylin’s Finger Of Death.

“Bastard, do you know how worried I was for you? At least discuss this with me beforehand!”

Chapter 935: Pendant

“I’m sorry, dear cousin! At this point, it’s better to get things done before we discuss things…” Leylin waved his arm, and another teleportation door opened.

Isabel stepped out of the teleportation door and immediately heard the uproar from the surroundings, as well as enraged shouts. Without any excess movements, she activated her bloodline abilities and the hidden techniques of the Red Dragon Sword

Dragon Aura Domain! Fireball! The legendary dragon’s spiritual domain and blazing fire rumbled, causing all the pirates to cry out miserably as they were sent flying. There were traces of charring all over their bodies.

The other pirates in the distance were also shrieking as they lay immobile on the ground. There was no way out for the weak in the face of the spiritual domain of dragon aura, and they would only be massacred by their enemies.

In actuality, the dragon aura of a regular dragon was still just average. One from an ancient or primordial dragon could take out even most high-ranked Professionals, and even affect legendaries to a great degree.

“Teleportation doors? High-ranked wizards? And a dragon sorcerer!” The God of Murder’s bishop cried out in alarm, light shining around his body.

After seeing Leylin step out of the teleportation door as well, his pupils shrank, “It’s you! You’ve already advanced to become a high-rank wizard?”

“Cut the bullshit…” Leylin gave the bishop a disdainful glance, the arcane spell he’d already prepared launching forth.

Mage’s Disjunction!

*Boom! Boom! Crackle!* Numerous spell rays shattered, returning to form the original magic item. They returned to the ring in the bishop’s hand, then his necklace, followed by his luxurious clothing.

One after another, magic items exploded on the bishop’s body. As he had too many on him, he was unlucky enough but to have to flee naked.

“A rank 9 disjunction? A high-ranked wizard above rank 19?” Uncaring of his own image, the bishop sunk into shock. In a few years, the opponent had become a high-ranked wizard, which shocked him to no end. On top of that, he was already a rank 19, very close to becoming legendary.

However, the power of Mage’s Disjunction had been shown right in front of him, which was something he could not understand at all.

‘This is the might of arcane spells…’ Seeing the bishop who was now completely in the nude, Leylin sighed inside. He was a high-ranked priest who was at least rank 17, and his wizard ranking would not be enough to subdue the priest. The opponent possessed a large number of powerful magic items.

However, being an arcanist allowed him to bypass the limitations of spell slots and the Weave. As long as he had enough arcane energy and the correct spell models, any spell under the legendary realm could be cast for a price.

This rank 9 Mage’s Disjunction, for example, was a spell used specifically to deal with magic Professionals. Its focus was very powerful, and all items below legendary would be undone under this spell.

It could be said that arcane spells were the bane of all wizards! Most of the battle might of wizards depended on their magic items, and being stripped of them would be a deadly blow!

On top of that, the heartache of having the magic items formed with blood and tears, made of materials and resources that had been gathered painstakingly, was enough for wizards to cough up blood.

A prime example of this would be the bishop now. With his wealth and the numerous spells and items to aid his escape, Leylin’s surprise attack alone was not enough to kill the opponent.

Now, however, all of the preparations he had made had been unravelled under Leylin’s spell, completely losing their effects. Most high-ranked priests’ divine spells were for buffs and healing. There were few that were meant for killing. Leylin’s spell had taken out most of the bishop’s strength.

“Damn it… How did you advance so quickly?” The bishop’s face was almost green, eyes now bloodshot. No matter how much he had overestimated Leylin’s strength, he would never have imagined that Leylin was extremely close to becoming legendary.

It was this huge oversight that led to his failure.

‘This is just the effect of a Mage’s Disjunction spell. If it’s the legendary version, that would be the nightmare of all legendary wizards! Not only legendary items, even divine weapons could be damaged…’ Leylin’s eyes showed his thirst and intoxication. He then landed his gaze on the bishop.

“Wha– What do you want?” The bishop still held no fear for Leylin. There was only immense regret; regret that he had not prepared more.

“What I want? That’s what I should be asking you, my dear bishop!” Leylin answered with a slight smile. At this moment, Isabel had abruptly sent out a few Dragon’s Breaths and burnt a few high-ranked assassins to ashes.

Upon seeing this, the corner of the bishop’s eyes began to twitch. These high-ranked assassins had been great helpers that he had nurtured with care. While their power was lacking in comparison to the one that had attacked Leylin, they were all elites! Now, however, their corpses lined the area, destroying all of the bishop’s hard work over the years.

The defences of a Dragon Warlock’s scales were exceedingly terrifying. On top of that, she had a legendary item in the Red Dragon Sword. These assassins’ high-ranked enchanted daggers were no match at all, and once they crossed swords their lives were easily ended.

Meanwhile, the battle between the Scarlet Tigers and the bishop’s pirates began to show who was on the winning side. The high-ranked pirates that had been hastily gathered were no match for Leylin’s elites that had gone through countless battles.

The sounds of yells closed in, and even the warship that was the main force was caught up to and surrounded by the pirate ships. Numerous fleeing pirates surged out like the tide. Leylin seemed unruffled in the situation, a confidence inherent to his very being.

“Bishop. I haven’t dealt with your church before, but you show malicious intent against us. Care to explain?” Leylin watched him, the glint from the A.I. Chip strengthening.

This bishop gave him a very different feeling from many priests. He’d seen his fair share, like the Gold Priest Xena who was in charge of the church of wealth on Faulen Island. The bishop wasn’t like that.

[Beep! An abnormal energy reaction has been detected within the host’s body.]

The A.I. Chip performed a full body scan in front of Leylin’s eyes. Many dark red spots had appeared on the translucent model, making it look demonic.

‘As expected… Is this the contamination from abnormal energy?’ Leylin wondered inside, ‘It’s a high-ranked priest, so this contamination should come from divine force!’

In Leylin’s eyes, the holy light of a high-ranked bishop had now been contaminated so badly that it was beyond recognition. No matter what kind of god, divine force was better when it was pure. However, what Leylin saw was divine force that had been contaminated and warped.

‘Has the God of Murder really gone mad? He doesn’t even care about his priests… Also, this power of distortion…’ Leylin felt a chill in his heart.

Legends said that Cyric, the Greater God of Murder, had begun to go insane. He was even planning to transform into a demon. His divine realm had signs of falling into the abyss, and it looked to be a possibility now!

The only being able to influence him that greatly would be Distorted Shadow!

‘As expected of an ancient peak rank 8 Magus! Even after falling, he can still cause his opponents so much trouble…’ Leylin could not help but sigh inside.

“Hm?” The bishop’s eyes raised slightly. In this situation, Leylin’s words sounded like he was amenable to persuasion.

“This… I can explain…” The bishop immediately gave Leylin a reason. Backing him was a true god, and a greater god at that. It was understandable that Leylin feared him. In the prime material plane, there had never been anyone with the guts to go against a greater god!

This was his belief in his god.

‘The plan to use military force has completely failed, but it won’t be bad if I can pull him to my side and make him a follower…’ Traces of dark red light flashed in the bishop’s eyes. He could not help but unclench his fingers from around a pendant he’d been clutching tightly.

“Now!” Leylin’s eyes flickered, and an invisible spatial undulation flashed with a bright light.

“Hm?” The bishop was stunned, and immediately felt a sharp pain in his wrist.

*Pak!* His right hand fell to the ground, bright red blood seeping out. A miniature statue of a god fell down.

‘He had no plans of complying!’ The bishop’s eyes went wide, and insanity flashed within. The only hand he had left began to grab towards Leylin’s heart.

“It’s too late… Finger of Death,” Leylin sighed. The dark rays from his hand disappeared into the bishop’s forehead, causing the light in his eyes to dim.

*Thud!* The bishop’s corpse fell heavily to the ground, causing the pirates to break down.

The rest of the matter was naturally left to his underlings. Leylin stood beside the Bishop’s fallen right hand and saw the small pendant, looking deep in thought.

‘God Descent? The material is strange, and it’s even immune to the Mage’s Disjunction attack…’ With this thought, Leylin picked the pendant up.

It was rather small. It was a miniature statue of a god, with thin silver chains threaded through it glimmering brightly.

Chapter 936: Greed

*Buzz!* The statue of the god began to rumble, divine force rippling like waves in water. It was as if it was about to come alive.

However, with the external activation not coming forth, the pendant restlessly shook a few times and then unwillingly stilled, losing its sheen.

”The divine summoning failed, huh. Apart from the divine force here, there is also the presence of the divine realm’s coordinates and even the conscient of a god…” Leylin muttered.

At this moment, he felt an extremely bitter conscient radiating great power from the pendant, as if its rage was about to overflow.

‘I’d need to worry if this was the true body, even if it’s an avatar… But what’s a trifling conscient like this?’ Leylin harrumphed, and a Targaryen phantom appeared in his eyes.

”Hss!” The conscient of a near rank 7 descended, annihilating all signs of the conscient lingering in the pendant. Just before that conscient dissipated, the raging divine force calmed down like a wave in a tranquil sea.

”Not bad at all! The divine force contained in here could perhaps give me an unexpected surprise…” An expression of glee spread across Leylin’s face.

The divine force of gods, to put it bluntly, was just a high-ranked power in a different form. It was considered venomous to others, and clerics could only receive the divine force of the gods they worshipped. However, it was all a supplement for Leylin.

‘What a pity… If not for those powerful gods, I would have long since broken into many churches and robbed them of their divine force…’ Leylin began his deductions.

Divine force, divinity, godfire, worshippers, divine spark; these were what the gods needed the most in increasing order.

With his current strength he could barely absorb some divinity, but it would destroy the foundations of his own cultivation. Needless to say, godfire or divine sparks were even more destructive for his body.

As for divine force? That was still well within Leylin’s absorption capabilities. Moreover, Leylin had deliberately digested the divine force of certain gods. Until now, he had only managed to have chance encounters with Malar and Cyric.

These two crazy and sinisterly evil gods had overlapping domains, which laid out a foundation for Leylin’s future plans.

‘Looking at the divine force stored in this pendant… It should be enough to increase my spirit a little, or even balance the other aspects of my stats…’ Leylin rubbed his chin. After eradicating the original conscient in the pendant, the divine force was now ownerless. Leylin could now absorb it slowly, with the greatest efficiency.

Through digesting this divine force Leylin would be able to analyse the process, helping him understand Cyric’s divinity. If he met other gods of different domains, he would be able to create a whole new divinity all for himself!

‘After tossing away this thing, even if this bishop managed to survive, he wouldn’t have a happy ending… No! He would be even worse off after his death!’ Leylin looked at the corpse on the floor and sighed.

Gods held control over the souls of their worshippers, and this was a high-ranking priest on top. Leylin hadn’t completely destroyed his soul just now. Once it was inspected by the God of Death, this priest’s soul would definitely be sent to Cyric’s divine realm.

As for what punishments the cleric would receive, no more words had to be said.

“What a pitiful fellow… “ Leylin was, of course, not sympathetic in the slightest bit. He quickly tossed this matter to the back of his mind.

“It seems like they were small crews roped in from Pirates’ Cove. Apart from the elites of the churches, there aren’t many forces would could execute something like this!” Isabel trod on the face of a pirate captain, using their robes to wipe clean the Red Dragon Sword as she grumbled.

With the activation of the bloodline, she’d also inherited a warrior-like thirst for war.

“Yes. Had they been given time to train we would’ve had a much bigger problem…” Leylin nodded his head in approval, very soon ordering Ronald to clean up the mess.

As dusk approached, the sky above the sea was dyed a crimson red. The entire region was littered with the remnants of broken ships and boats. Splintered masts and flags covered half the place, and not too far from that scene were many floating corpses, blood continuing to ooze and trickle from their bloated bodies.

The enormous pirate crew slowly left, leaving a trail of destruction behind them. From this day onwards, everyone would know that two epic battles were fought in this forsaken region, devastating and annihilating two giants of the seas in one stroke.

“This atmosphere and scenery… I really want to lift my voice in song…!”

*Crash! Rumble!* A figure wearing lavish noble robes descended from the sky. He exuded an aura of charisma and elegance, yet a pair of black wings spread from his back. Apart from the difference in colour, this figure looked just like an angel, with many beautiful features. However, his image was shattered the moment anyone looked into his eyes.

“That Baron Leylin… He rules the outer seas from today, eh? I really am looking forward to it…” This person was obviously Neville, but his pupils had now turned a silvery hue, with no traces of affection in them. With just one glance into his eyes, one would feel their soul turning frigid.

Neville’s black wings shook slightly as they supported his weight. At this moment, this demon looked at the Scarlet Tiger ship sailing away, as he pondered deep in his thoughts. ‘Strong, determined, decisive, brave…Once a soul with these qualities falls, the strength that would manifest would definitely be able to give birth to a greater devil…’

“As expected, it’s a devil huh?” An indifferent voice sounded behind him, which turned made Neville freeze in his motions.

He turned his head around slowly, looking at the young noble wizard that should have left. Yet he was now floating in the air alongside him with his arms crossed, a hint of mockery flickering in his eyes.

“Hello mighty wizard, ruler of the outer seas! I am Neville, of the third hell. I hereby extend my greetings to you, with utmost respect!” After giving Leylin a once-over, Neville greeted Leylin decorously, with his right hand on his chest.

“I believe that in the future there will be a day where you’ll require my services!”

“One cannot trust a deal with devils. Not to mention that you tried to lure me into a ploy… Anyone who tries to challenge me will never live past the day…” Leylin uttered his words icily, and a silver spell formation wrapped Neville up.

“Wait… I can still give you… Many things that you would not think of! Material possessions of the prime material world, authority that cannot be challenged, and also many beauties…” The silver spell formation seemed to be able to suppress devils. As his black feathers came into contact with the light barrier, they burnt up to release a charred smell.

“The promise of a devil? Hahaha…” Leylin smiled faintly, his golden pupils turning a deep hue that was darker than the abyss. The phantom of a Targaryen appeared behind him.

A terrifying devouring energy burst forth from the spell formation, completely engulfing Neville within.

“This devouring power… as well as laws… You are…!” Neville’s eyes flashed with understanding, but before he could utter the truth his body vanished into the spell formation.

“The ruler of the third level of hell, the Duke of Greed… Mammon, huh?” Leylin uttered his breath and closed his eyes, relishing in the energy that he was absorbing.

[Beep! Host absorbed a large amount of energy. Agility +1, Vitality +1.]

The A.I. Chip voice intoned.

Very soon, another notification appeared, and it caused Leylin to become gleeful.

[Host has devoured a devil from the third hell. Laws of devouring have been activated, obtained information on laws of greed]

“Isn’t this the devouring technique of my main body?” Leylin muttered. His main body controlled the laws of gluttony, and through constantly devouring these laws he would gain a higher enlightenment of them. The devil from the third hell had enlightened him a little in that aspect.

“My main body’s injuries have begun to heal faster than normal then… Its support has increased…” Leylin was elated. His stats had now changed:

[Leylin Faulen, Age: 22. Race: Human, Rank 16 Arcanist. Strength: 13. Agility: 12. Vitality: 13. Spirit: 16. Arcane Energy: 160. Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Elementary Perfect Body. Specialties: Arcane Energy Detection, Arcane Amplification.]

“I have also absorbed some information on the laws of greed? It seems like Beelzebub was indeed one of the dukes of hell. Even after making changes to it, it is still highly adaptable to the laws from the abyss!”

Leylin gazed towards the horizon. “The outer seas are now my base, impenetrable to outside forces. Be it from hell or any divine realm, no threat…”

A high-level flight spell lit up, and very soon Leylin’s figure was just a black dot in the distance, slowly disappearing into the horizon.

More repercussions were brewing and intensifying in the aftermath of this event…

……

In another part of the continent, in the midst of a gloomy valley.

An aura of death permeated the air, and there was a black church at the valley’s center. Magical light filled the area, and even legendaries would perish within it.

Just as the bishop was about to perish, a white-browed priest raised his head in the church.

“Men!”

“Your holiness!” Several dark robed priests answered immediately with reverence in their eyes. Standing in front of them was a core member of the Church of Cyric, a legendary priest!

Chapter 938: Meeting

After giving them a tour of the tower, Leylin brought the priests to the drawing room. The metallic golems arrived quickly, presenting tea and snacks in elven porcelain.

“May I know why Lord Baron invited us here?” Xena took a look at these golems that were about as strong as rank 10 Professionals, and increased Leylin’s rating in her mind.

Beside her as a representative of the Goddess of Wealth’s church, there were also priests from the Gods of Knowledge and Suffering. However, Xena was the highest-ranked, and the influence of the Goddess of Wealth was the greatest here. It allowed her to act on behalf of the other two.

“Before all that, I’d first like to give you two gifts!” Leylin clapped, and another golem came forward, placing two boxes in front of them. Once they were opened, a pungent smell wafted out with large amounts of lime powder. It caused Xena to furrow her brows. She slowly drew closer.

“This is…” She suddenly took several steps backwards after seeing what was inside.

“Ah…” “It’s actually…”

If Xena had reacted that way, the other two priests had even larger reactions.

“Lord Leylin, are you using this to scare us?” Xena’s tone was of dissatisfaction, as the box contained two sinister heads. Showing heads to these priests was no sign of goodwill.

“Hehe… I’m obviously not offending you. Please take a closer look…” Leylin had an easy smile on his face.

After confirming that Leylin would not fall out with the church of wealth, Xena endured the nausea and discomfort and began to observe the sinister faces in the box.

After taking a closer look, she found something was wrong. “Hm? This …”

The two other priests also seemed to have noticed something as well, delight showing on their expressions.

“Lord Leylin, this is…” The priest of the God of Suffering, Avdonia, began sounding unsure.

“Indeed, this is the high-ranked assassin that killed numerous men of the clergy during the Pirates’ Tide.”

Leylin pointed at the box on the left, “As for the one next to him, it is the bishop of the God of Murder hidden in the outer seas, Jesfano!”

“Hah… On behalf of all my comrades that met harm, I thank you!” Xena covered the boxes and sighed. The two other priests also thanked him happily.

During the Pirates’ Tide, the God of Murder had dispatched his subordinates to assassinate those of godly duties without regard. This had resulted in massive losses on the gods’ end. The churches that the three priests in front of Leylin represented were also included in the scope of the attacks, so it could be said that they had a feud with these two people.

The fact that Leylin had given them these two heads as gifts made them rather pleased.

“Well then… What does Lord Leylin wish to speak about?” The priest that had come in the bishop of the God of Knowledge’s stead was one that looked like an elderly scholar. The man called Salilus questioned Leylin with an intelligent glint in his eyes. After hearing his words, Xena and Avdonia focused on Leylin.

“Actually, these two heads were surprises that I obtained when exterminating the notorious Barbarians…” Leylin explained slightly.

“The Barbarians? You mean the culprit that started the Pirates’ Tide causing heavy casualties in the outer seas? They’ve been wiped out?” Xena was rather surprised, while Leylin snickered inside.

By defaming the Barbarians over the long term, especially with the king’s announcement, the Barbarians were now complete criminals. There was no way to absolve themselves of this reputation.

“Mm. They weren’t just pirates, they were connected with the God of Murder’s church!” Leylin declared, which then earned him flattery reserved for young heroes from Salilus.

“But…” When Leylin continued however, his tone completely changed, which made the three priests aware that Leylin was about to come to the main point.

“I believe that the outer seas as they are right now are in urgent need of a purge of faith in evil gods. This applies especially to those pirates and natives…” Leylin spoke in a low voice, his true intentions now revealed.

“A purge of faith?” The three of them exchanged glances in their surprise.

“Yes, a purge!” Leylin nodded resolutely.

While he treated the outer seas as his trump card, he could not offend all of the gods. Cyric and Malar’s reputations were rotten to the core, so that didn’t matter, but the few churches on Faulen Island needed to be roped in to his side. They could be considered as the Faulen Family’s natural allies.

As for the unlucky bishop of the God of Murder, Leylin was sorry to say that he could only be treated as just another stepping stone.

“Also… when it comes to dealing blows to the devils and demons, there are many ways we can cooperate in the future. I myself have come up with many new spell formations to detect demons and devils…” Leylin looked extremely furious.

Getting the favour of the good faction via proclaiming his wish to attack the devils and demons was a part of his plan. He could keep subduing them in the shadows to expand his strength, which made it like killing two birds with one stone.

“Oh? Please allow us to discuss this for a while…” Xena looked towards the priests beside her and answered, finding herself put in a spot.

From Leylin’s actions, it was apparent that he was making a declaration to dominate the outer seas. Most importantly, with the annihilation of the Barbarians and uprooting the God of Murder’s church, there now seemed to be no other opposing forces on the sea.

As those of the clergy, they would first have to consider the benefits to their churches. Everything else was secondary.

Unifying the outer sea and cracking down on faith in evil gods and devils was unquestionably beneficial for the gods they had faith in. Of course, this was only if they stood on the same side as Leylin and worked together with him.

‘He has the ability to destroy the Barbarians in secret… Seems like the rumours that the Faulen Family has control over the Scarlet Tigers is true…’ Xena glanced at Leylin, who was all smiles, and pondered over this.

‘With huge armed fleets on the surface and a pirate group in the shadows, as well as huge trade benefits and shipping routes supporting him, it is undeniable that he shall be king of the outer seas. Rejecting his goodwill at this time is very unfavourable to the goddess’ upcoming plans…’

Xena was actually very unwilling to see a single organisation becoming the dictator of the outer seas. She would rather this region be a place for free trade. However, she was currently left without choice.

The moment she infuriated a large organisation like this capable of unifying the outer seas, there would be a huge blow to trades in this region. This was also disadvantageous to the spread of faith in the Goddess of Wealth. Xena kept weighing her options.

‘But… attacking the evil gods, devils and demons?’ Xena shot Leylin a glance. While she had no clue what he was actually thinking, doing this meant she could tell what faction Leylin was in. At the very least, he was not on opposing ends with the Goddess of Wealth.

“In this regard… Please give me some time, my Lord. I need to discuss this with other members before I can make a decision!” While she already had a general inclination to agree, Xena still answered this way.

“The same goes for us.” At the other side, Salilus and Avdonia gave the same answer.

“Of course! This is just my intent. My family also has no plans of sending out troops on a large scale as of yet…” Leylin knew that these priests needed the permissions of their churches and even gods, which was why he didn’t pressure them. Whatever it was, this would be beneficial to them. He was sure that those with foresight could see this.

“As for the new detection spell and spell formations that you mentioned…” Before leaving, Xena displayed her strong interest in what Leylin had mentioned.

“Those are things I put research into and created unwittingly. They’re about half a fold more effective than ancient detection techniques, and the same goes for the range!” Leylin spoke indifferently, but that only caused the priests’ eyes to glint.

Demons and devils were the most hated beings in the prime material plane of the World of Gods! Altars and spells that could detect and distinguish them, especially those as effective and with as large a range as Leylin had said, were definitely the dreams of the churches.

“To be able create new spells alone… I was actually doubtful of my Lord’s talent in spells, but my doubts have been set aside.” The priest of the God of Knowledge, Salilus, spoke with conviction.

Even if it was the simplest distinguishing and detection spells, being able to create a whole new spell model meant that Leylin’s knowledge in terms of spells had reached a very profound level. Wizards like these were more capable of reaching the realm of legendaries. This was how it was recorded in many documents. Leylin had exhibited his abilities here, and Salilus could not help but brighten up.

“Many thanks for the praise. I can discuss matters related to this more comprehensively if you wish to!” Leylin was, on the surface, still a follower of Oghma. Naturally, he had to give this bishop preferential treatment, as well as give the other two some pressure.

“Of course, of course!” Salilus nodded with his eyes wide, while the other two looked wary.

After sending the three priests away, Leylin strolled back to his room.

‘There aren’t anymore issues in persuading them…’ he thought, ‘I’ll have a reason to purge the outer seas and call for help. All that’s left is to make preparations…’

By purging the faith of the natives in the outer seas and stealing their soul strength, he could constantly advance, speeding up his contact with the legendary realm. In the meanwhile, he could also expunge the devils and demons. This was Leylin’s main plan that would never change!

Chapter 939: Demon Experiment

Faulen Island, the basement of the wizard tower. Within the negative energy pool.

This was a place where wizards conducted taboo experiments, with dimensional spell formations specifically to summon demons and devils. Hence, a powerful binding formation was an essential protective measure for this place.

Researching demons and devils! Obviously, once priests or paladins found out, he would become a wanted man, a sinner that all the humans would call out.

It was a pity that most high-ranked wizards had to make use of negative energy to advance. There were few who followed some lesser-known paths. After becoming a legendary wizard, those madmen might even completely disregard the gods and brazenly go against their ban, becoming involved in the domain of arcane spells.

In the eyes of those strictly forbidden scholars, the gods were merely a group of powerful wizards. Who exactly was up there was a function of luck and one’s birth.

Due to their pursuit of truth and their research, wizards often harboured thoughts of becoming treacherous, and were hated by the gods to the bone. They had then done all they could to create the Weave in order to limit the spellcasters.

Unfortunately, even with the annihilation of Netheril and the crippling of most wizards through the Weave, legendary wizards still walked the path of doubting the gods. The immense pressure they exerted caused even more vigorous backlash, which was in a way very ironic.

“A dimensional summoning spell formation? While I can only summon beings from various planes within the crystal sphere, it’s still not bad…” Leylin now stood at the edge of a spell formation with various runes drawn all over it, possessing an inquiring look on his face.

After sending the three priests away, he focused entirely on research in arcane spells. He was already a rank 16 arcanist, and it was obvious that he would perform practical experiments in this area.

“There seems to be a very powerful limitation in summoning spells within the World of Gods. There are also different factions. Of course… anyone can summon demons, as long as they are controlled well after that…” Leylin murmured to himself and activated the runes on the spell formation.

“Though it’s my first time using this, I guess I’ll summon demons. After all, I’ve gotten familiar with devils, but haven’t gotten the chance to observe demons myself…”

Demon summoning! As this was the first time, Leylin had not planned to summon a particularly powerful demon. However, after casting the spell, he suddenly found his spiritual force connecting with a large, deep, dark and chaotic plane.

“Is this the abyss? This power of space and chaos…” The abyss was currently known to have hundreds of layers, and most of it was definitely undiscovered.There were even rumours that the ninth level of hell had initially been part of the abyss and been separated.

With Leylin’s current spiritual force, it was impossible for him to advance to far into the abyss, even with spells and spell formations supporting him. He could only tour the surface layers.

“Mm! There’s a confusing and chaotic soul aura here, but it feels infinitely tiny. This should be a type of abyssal worm. That’s too weak… But then this one is too powerful. I think it’s approaching the rank of legendary. Everything is so different… I give up…”

With his fine spiritual force control, Leylin had more choices than other wizards. Finally, after a generally searching the area, he found his target, “A powerful soul aura and a strength that isn’t too strong or too weak. It’s you! Summon!”

The planar coordinates locked onto the target, and Leylin saw a teleportation gate opening. A strange, terrifying demon was teleported over.

*Kukaka!* What entered Leylin’s sights was a huge demon that looked more like a bald eagle on two legs. It was completely naked and had large wings on its back, the disgusting red chicken skin evident. Its human arms were tipped by incredibly sharp claws.

It did not hesitate to attack once it saw Leylin. The bloodlust, chaos and insanity within the soul caused his eyes to widen slightly.

“This should be a Vrock! While evolved from abyssal worms, it should be considered a mid-ranked demon! On top of that… this amount of chaos and level of attack… Hmph!”

Leylin huffed, the binding spell formation he had prepared beforehand flickered with dazzling light. Tens of lightning rays formed a huge prison. The Vrock’s talons clashed with the electricity, and it immediately caused a huge sound. Large amounts of black flames began to blaze within, causing even the Vrock to retreat pitifully. There was finally some fear in its eyes.

“This guy only knows to be tough on the weak but is afraid when treated harshly!” Leylin shook his head, his right index finger pressing on his temple, “A.I. Chip, scan it and gather data!”

[Beep! Mission established. Beginning scan.]

The A.I. Chip loyally carried out Leylin’s commands. Soon enough, a 3D scan appeared in front of Leylin, detailing its stats.

[Name unknown. Race: Vrock (Tanar’ri) Strength: 16 Agility: 17 Vitality: 15 Spirit: 13 Feats: 1. Demon Skin 2. Flight 3. Corrosive Aura 4. Ability similar to magic. Description: This is a mid-rank demon. There is chaos and evil of the abyss in its very soul. Unless its mind is controlled, one will definitely be met with a powerful counterattack.]

‘It’s the model of a high-ranked professional, and its stats in all areas surpass them!’ Leylin evaluated dully, and then saw its faction lights and soul temperament. ‘What kind of insane and chaotic soul is this! It even has such an evil feeling…’

It had to be said that while he’d heard of this before, actually meeting one had Leylin losing completely hope in demons.

“They’re just a bunch of evil lunatics with power in their hands!” After seeing its temperament, Leylin finally understood why the demons kept losing in the bloody battles with devils. While they were all evil existences, these beings that hid within chaos were just unworthy of his attention.

“The chaotic temperament from the abyss? Where is this coming from?” Leylin had a searching look in his eyes. He observed the Vrock trapped by the binding formation, the intense gaze causing even the insane demon to feel some fear.

“I don’t have much time, but I do have patience for my first specimen!” Leylin had an apathetic expression as a small, silver surgical knife and other tools suddenly appeared in his hands.

……

“While the flesh itself is filled with a filthy power of chaos, the temperament of demons seems to be rooted in the soul itself…” The laboratory was now completely empty, and there were only bloodstained bits of bone left here. Some creature’s last wails seemed to linger in the area, filling the place with a frightening aura.

However, this did not affect Leylin at all. After washing away the blood and dirt on his hands, he focused on studying the potion in the test tube he held. A dark red liquid could be seen in the test tube, a dark light within shining with varying amounts of intensity as he shook the tube. It seemed evil and frightening.

‘This is the potion that was made from extracting the demon’s energy. A.I. Chip!’ Leylin’s eyes twinkled as he ordered.

[Beep! Item Name: Middle Demon Potion. Effect: Raises vitality and strength of all beings below 10 points by 1 point. For those with these stats below 15 points, vitality and strength increases by 0.5. Ineffective for all professionals above rank 15. Description: This is a potion with powerful demonic energy. Drink it if strength is desired, although be fearless of the corruption to your soul. You might fall to the abyss forever.]

“Not a bad result. What a pity…” Leylin sighed. While this potion was pretty good at boosting his underlings’ strength, the demonic corruption that would result was a huge issue. If he wanted to continue working in the prime material plane, then his underlings could not be a group of demons!

However, his underlings could not be too weak either. He was preparing to nurture talents for the church he would build.

“What a bother! While I’m unafraid of such corruption, it won’t be the same for others…” Leylin muttered, “I need to adjust the soul to remove the corruption, which would increase the costs too much. This can only be used as a reward, and not an ordinary potion to be passed down…”

‘And… the abyss?’ Leylin stroked his chin, recalling that mighty surge of chaos he had felt before.

‘Chaos is a rather powerful law. After grasping it, I might even be able to command strength even more powerful than greater gods and work together with the abyss. Unfortunately, it doesn’t suit me at all… I should head to the abyss and hell after becoming legendary to take a look.’

With Leylin’s abilities, the abyss and hell were good choices to reincarnate in. However, Leylin had pondered over this and then given up. Compared to the prime material plane, these two areas were far too dangerous. There were battles everywhere and basically no peace whatsoever.

Right after reincarnating, Leylin would be at his weakest. How could he gamble on this?

“Even if I wanted to try my luck, would I, an invader, still be cared for by the World Will?” Leylin had a feeling that even while the World Will was in a deep sleep, its malicious intent towards Magi would not disappear so easily.

However, with his law of devouring, he would certainly be able to let his talents shine if he were to enter the abyss and hell. Leylin had no hesitations when it came to that!

Chapter 940: Mid-Rank Perfect Body

Within a dim room. Powerful golden divine force was raging like stormy waves as it gushed out of a small statue. It was then absorbed by a huge black vortex in mid-air. Completely transformed, a pure energy gathered at the body of a quiet figure sitting there.

Powerful divine force condensed to form a faint figure of light, a thread of divinity sparkling as it emerged.

‘The analysis of divine force has slowly given me information over divinity…’ Leylin pondered over this. In the eyes of Magi, this so-called godhood was merely an elementary understanding of the power of laws.

A true god had comprehended one law completely. From there, one would ignite their godfire to join the ranks of the other true gods, a process improving comprehension of laws as they grasped them.

“But… The World of Gods has unique rules of their own. With the power of faith, comprehension of the laws can be hastened. The power of laws possessed after becoming a true god can also be boosted through faith. With the comprehension of laws as the core, one can rob or present this divinity that comes from faith…”

It was extremely difficult for the inhabitants of the World of Gods to surpass the limitations on their own bodies and obtain divinity. Unless one was lucky enough to get into the good graces of the gods or pick up a divine weapon with divinity hidden inside, this was basically impossible.

However, having already grasped the true essence of laws, Magi didn’t find it too difficult to create divinity as long as they had enough materials.

‘Honestly speaking, divine force is actually the material to form divinity. It takes other gods too much energy to transform it, to the point that they’re unwilling to do so…’ Leylin studied the statue in his hands. The divine force within was almost completely depleted.

“Even with all the divine force stored inside being able to raise the my average stats, I still can’t form any real divinity…” Leylin muttered to himself. After absorbing all the divine force within the statue, his strength had improved just a bit. He now had a better understanding of Cyric’s godly duties and domain, but he still could not condense divinity. This was not an issue in technique, but just that there weren’t enough pure ingredients.

By his estimation, he would require all the divine force from a god’s avatar to condense the divinity he needed.

“Eliminating an avatar?” Leylin stroked his chin, beginning to ponder over the feasibility of this matter.

It wasn’t possible for a god to descend on the prime material plane in their true body. Their personifications were at most high-ranked legendaries and saints, about as strong as rank 5 or 6 Magi. They would also lose their holiness, and could therefore be killed.

Of course, even the avatar wasn’t someone Leylin could deal with easily.

‘I completely understand Cyric’s divine force…’ Leylin reflected, ‘With multiple domains like murder, massacres, conspiracies, and death, he has entered the ranks of the greater gods. An avatar from him would be the cream of the crop…’

In Leylin’s eyes, however, of all of Cyric’s laws, the only ones Leylin found worthy were those of massacre and death. These two domains were very formidable, and they were what Cyric had relied on to enter the ranks of the greater gods.

It would take a tremendous amount of divine force to condense a divinity in these domains.

‘Even if he’s gone insane, this is still far too difficult… I should change my target…’

Ever since Leylin had started out here, he had only offended two gods; the God of the Hunt, Malar, and the God of Murder, Cyric. This had naturally been done after some pondering. As the path he had chosen caused conflict with these two gods, becoming hostile was obvious.

‘Malar is only a lesser god, and his avatar would be easier to deal with. I don’t want anything to do with his domain of hunting, but it won’t be hard to transform it into a divinity in massacres…’

Only middle gods and above in the World of Gods could transform divinity between similar fields. However, any rank 8 Magus could do so This was the result of differences in comprehending laws.

With Leylin’s temperament, those benevolent and honest roles meant nothing to him. Not only was his soul unsuitable for that, it would also pollute his path to becoming a rank 8 Magus. Hence, he had few choices.

With research on ancient Magi like Distorted Shadow, he now had a better understanding of his own path.

‘My path is definitely inclined towards ‘evil’ for this world. Will I completely walk the path of a rebel?’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘Based on the novels from my previous world, rebels never lead good lives. That’s rather… interesting…’

‘But… the power of devils will definitely gives rise to massacres and death. That’s rather fitting…’ The corner of Leylin’s lips suddenly turned up in an evil smile.

He did not fear sin on his path to eternity, nor did he mind grasping evil laws.

*Boom!* At this moment, the miniature statue in his hands exploded. His continued absorption over this period of time had completely exhausted the divine force within.

“Is it depleted already?” Leylin closed his eyes. The cells all over his body greedily absorbed this pure energy that had been transformed, and there was even a huge improvement on a genetic level. At this moment, the A.I. Chip’s robotic voice sounded.

[Beep! Host has absorbed pure energy. Effect similar to eternal grace from the god. Strength +1, Agility +2, Vitality +1, Spirit +1.]

[Host’s spiritual force has broken through, rank increasing. Host is now a rank 17 arcanist. Arcane Energy +10.]

[Obtained spell slots: rank 8(1), rank 7(1), rank 6(1), rank 5(1)]

All his stats had now exceeded 15. Power erupted in Leylin’s body, and it felt as if every cell was dancing in elation as if they had broken through their shackles.

[Beep! Host’s stats have all reached 15. Feat Elementary Perfect Body has become Middle Perfect Body.]

The A.I. Chip’s prompt continued to show.

Afterwards, the explanation of the Perfect Body feat was refreshed.

[Middle Perfect Body. Host’s genes have been optimised. Characteristics of exemplary beings has been strengthened, and host has obtained mid-rank resistance to toxins, fire, cold, and corrosion. Endurance in varying environments has been increased by large degree.]

Leylin’s stats changed.

[Leylin Faulen. Age: 22. Race: Human, Rank 17 Arcanist. Strength: 15. Agility: 15. Vitality: 15. Spirit: 17. Arcane Energy: 170 Status: Healthy. Feats: Sturdy, Erudite, Middle Perfect Body. Specialties: Arcane Energy Detection, Arcane Amplification.]

[Spell slots possessed: rank 8(1), rank 7(3), rank 6(6), rank 5(???), rank 4(???), rank 3(???), rank 2(???), rank 1(???), rank 0(???)]

[Analysis of Weave: Level 0: 100%, Level 1: 100%, Level 2: 100%, Level 3: 100%, Level 4: 100%, Level 5: 100%, Level 6: 53.33%, Level 7: 34.97%. Level 8: 0.11%.]

‘So all of the divine force and demon potions recently have allowed me to rise to this point?’ Leylin nodded, looking satisfied.

The rise in his arcanist ranking allowed him to reduce the consumption needed for arcane spells. Besides for rank 9 arcane spells, he would not need to pay any price at all. The rise in his wizard ranking also allowed him obtain a rank 8 spell slot, which was pretty good.

“And then… Middle Perfect Body?”

Leylin wondered about this. The advancement in his perfect body meant he was transforming into a higher-grade lifeform. Once he became a legendary, he would probably have a Greater Perfect Body or even Legendary Perfect Body as his feat.

“Even those old legends must have endured long periods of training to improve their stats, allowing them to possess a Legendary Perfect Body. However, at the rate that I’m improving, my feat with the Perfect Body alone after becoming a legendary would allow me to catch up to the Legends who have been amassing strength for so long…”

“Also, a powerful vessel would allow me to make preparations to take on more power!” Leylin had a feeling that once his Perfect Body reached the legendary domain, there would be huge advantages to absorbing divinity and even igniting his godfire to become a god.

“Whether it’s the remaining evil organisations in the outer seas or dealing with the God of Murder, all this would require me harnessing great power…” The Faulen Family might have become a king of the outer seas, but lacked the power to completely control the situation!

Only by quickly becoming a legendary could he fearlessly take on the attack from the God of Murder’s church, and therefore make the outer seas a solid foundation for him to become a god.

“My speed of advancement is already very fast. If I want to continue, the only method would be making use of the faith of the natives in the outer seas…”

Chapter 941: Agreement

Leylin’s progress slowed once he became a rank 17 arcanist. He performed experiments on negative energy and other planes everyday within his wizard tower, and occasionally taught some apprentices. He led a leisurely life.

As he possessed crucial techniques and strength, he was not in the least bit anxious. And just as he expected, others could no longer hold themselves back.

“Lord Baron… Were you really the one to create these three spells? Detect Demon, Detect Domain, and Sense Devil?”

Xena did not seem to be in the best mental state. There were dark bags under her beautiful eyes, and it was apparent that she hadn’t had a good rest in a long time. For her, this was something unthinkable.

“Yes!” Leylin answered with a smile, and he then saw Xena’s eyes that were full of shock and astonishment that she could not hide.

“The many gods will definitely notice your contributions to the World of Gods!” After obtaining an affirmation, Xena immediately guaranteed.

This was because Leylin’s invention was far too astounding.

Even if the paladins had spells like Detect Evil, its categories and scope were far too narrow. After personal testing, Xena found that the spell models that Leylin provided far exceeded the detection methods from before, whether in terms of accuracy or scope.

The effect it would have on the operation of dealing with demons and devils was obvious.

Xena’s eyes were now full of fervor as she watched Leylin. If she could offer up these techniques to her goddess’ church, she might even have the confidence to compete the next ‘Holy Coin’ church election!

“I’ve always had zero tolerance for evil organisations!” Leylin’s experiment showed how ‘righteous’ he was, but he was snorting away inside.

He himself was half an Archdevil, so making a few techniques to detect devils was far too easy. Having met a high-ranked person from their faction, being betrayed and sold out was just the devils and demons being down on their luck.

With this, Leylin could also show his resolution in his faction.

Of course, as the person who created these detection techniques, Leylin had long since come up with their respective defences and counter spells. Of course, he had given all those to his own devil underlings.

‘It’s wonderful to use another’s strength to eliminate your enemies…’ Leylin assessed to himself, ‘If these spells grow widespread, then all the devils and demons hiding in the mainland will face heavy losses. It’ll be a chance for my worshippers of gluttony…’

Thankfully, Xena had no idea of what Leylin was thinking, or else she’d definitely attack him.

“But I can only sell the spell scrolls and alchemic items related to this to you. The basic spell model has to be kept a secret. At the moment, I will only be selling them to you three and your churches,” Leylin’s next words caused Xena’s expression to change.

“After all… my Faulen Family is merely a small power that’s unable to go against the devil and demon forces of the whole continent. You wouldn’t wish for our Faulen Family to be massacred by violent devils and demons, would you?” Leylin watched Xena, looking helpless. While this Gold Bishop’s expression changed, she still had no choice but to acknowledge this.

Even Xena had no confidence to say that the church of wealth would definitely protect the Faulen Family, because this was impossible.

Those devils and demons definitely did not care for the Goddess of Wealth.

“Mm, alright. You will also need to swear that you will never leak news that I am the seller!” Leylin spoke seriously. While dealing blows to devils and demons was good, he did not want to invite trouble. This was why it was necessary to take all these steps as well.

Most importantly, there was a limit to the spell scrolls and alchemic items that he was selling, so that the effect could be regulated. With the ability of Magi and arcanists to seal things, Leylin was confident that he could press this advantage for over a century. Even a legendary wizard would not be able to decrypt his spell models.

In addition, with his ‘pitiful’ speed, there was a limit to the spell scrolls he could make. Part of the time was also needed to be spent on research. Hence, the actual damage to the demons was rather slight.

Based on his speculations, being able to wipe them out of the Dambrath Kingdom within a decade was something very amazing.

This would prevent certain powerful demons and devils from being driven to action in their desperation. With such a long period of time, they would have the time to come up with plans and deal with it.

By selling this stuff, he could also rope in the three churches. He’d already considered the possibility of them joining hands to pressure him. Firstly, the three of them were in the lawful good faction, and would never use sinister methods. With their three gods controlling each other, he would also have the chance to benefit from them all.

Only a legendary, with decisive power in the prime material plane, would be a sufficient foundation to protect the interests and safety of his organisation.

“… I understand… After this, I’ll contact the other two churches.” Xena gave Leylin a look, having thought of many things in that instance, “Our church of wealth is very much in favour of the Faulen Family expanding in the outer seas!”

“Thank you very much! Oh, I’ve already prepared the specific spell scrolls. The price is ten thousand gold kro, so please come and get it anytime!” Leylin smiled winningly like an unscrupulous businessman. The church of wealth had money after all, and who was he to say no to that? They were more than capable of paying for this.

……

After the exchange of benefits and agreement, the Faulen Family’s inclination of unifying the outer seas was unstoppable. They’d already subdued other, smaller nobles, so they met no opposition on that front. The rest were like Marquis Tim of the Gold Thornblossoms, too afraid to oppose this.

After seeing the three churches standing by the Faulen Family, he was already scared shitless. Tim knew how ruthless Leylin was. He had dared massacred the Baltic archipelago, and after gaining support from the churches he was fearless. If Tim had the courage to fight back, he would end up in an even worse state than the old Marquis. He was a smart man, and obviously made the right choice.

In that moment, the outer seas belonged to the Faulen Family’s to do as they wished. Only the ships that had the family’s flags could move around in the outer seas uninhibited.

Recently, there were even rumours that Tim and his band of nobles were planning to petition to the Dambrath King to consider the Faulen Family’s expansion and ‘outstanding contributions’, in hopes to raise Leylin’s feudal rank and give him more land.

With all the troubles on the surface dealt with, Leylin focused his attentions on what was going on in the shadows.

“There are actually only two forces in the dark world of the Dambrath outer seas. One is the evil force with the pirates in power, but with the annihilation of the Barbarians, they now pose no threat. The other is the native islands with their faith in evil gods…”

Using a conjured water mirror, Leylin was now deep in a frank conversation with his cousin Isabel.

She had already completely taken over Pirates’ Cove and turned it into the Scarlet Tigers’ base. It could be said that the fall of Pirates’ Cove meant that the outer seas’ pirate world had been unified. There would no longer be any forces on the sea that could match the Scarlet Tigers.

“Also… The native tribes’ belief in the evil gods is something very troublesome. They are rather ignorant, greedy, and savage, and believe in natural spirits. They rely on beings with great might to shelter them, and become a huge threat to passing ships…”

As the noble child of a merchant of the seas, Leylin had long since gotten a deep understanding of these native tribes. Even if the Dambrath Kingdom had entered an age of discovery in the seas and gone through generations of migration, there were still few ‘civilised people’ in the outer seas than natives.

It was said that further into the deep seas, there was a large continent where an empire built by the natives existed!

Hence, in order to completely unify the outer seas, he could not let go of these natives’ tribes, especially since they had natural spirits that had formed after hundreds or even a thousand years worth of offerings.

These primitive totems had, with years of faith from the natives, obtained immense strength. Possessing divinity or even igniting divine flames was nothing special from them.

“I hope you can head the elimination of the native tribes in the outer seas, in the regions that we know of.” Leylin spoke to Isabel through the communicator.

He now somewhat had a group of underlings with reasonable strength, and there were some things he did not have to do himself. In that sense, he’d turned from a pawn into the player.

In order to truly leap out of the chessboard, he’d at least need legendary strength. To take part in the games of the gods, he would need to be a member!

“Make records of all the natural spirits and totems with legendary strength and above, and also the native tribes that believe in the Goddess of the Ocean. Let them off temporarily.” Leylin had consistently been taking advantage of the weaker ones and afraid to go head on with the powerful. Nothing changed here.

“I understand!” As a senior pirate, Isabel knew full well the terror that the Ocean Goddess could inflict. There were many amongst her own men that followed her. Once she was provoked in the ocean, then one would only be engulfed by boundless storms.

Isabel could even imagine that once she ordered those pirates to attack the Ocean Goddess’ church or altar, those pieces of trash would collapse in their fear.

Chapter 944: Ritual

“Ready a ship and men. I’m going to leave immediately!” Since he had confirmed the location, Leylin would obviously go on a rescue mission immediately. Robin Hood and Ronald listened respectfully. Not long after, they had everything prepared…

A day later. Isabel had just met her life’s largest crisis in the rainforest.

“What… what the heck is this?” A powerful draconic aura spread out, and a few black monsters were burnt to ashes.

These black monsters had a strong, dark-red fog around them. They were shaped weirdly, as if formed of soil.

*Rustle… Rustle…* Even if it was burnt off by the flames, the dark red gas gathered once more to spawn more monsters/

“Damn it! They can’t die?” Karen used her dagger and pierced into a monster with three human heads, one each belonging to an elderly, a middle-aged man and a youth. However, the injuries quickly recovered and even swallowed her dagger. Sensing the immense danger, Karen could only abandon her weapon and leave.

“Only powerful attack spells or the explosion of qi from a high-ranked Professional can truly hurt them!” Isabel was now in her half-dragon form. Those fog creatures quickly evaded a powerful Dragon Breath, and that finally gave the two a path to retreat.

“I never thought that there would be such strange things in the forest!” Isabel gazed at the moon on the horizon. The moonlight, which should be bright, was now stained with a layer of purplish-red and looked incomparably evil.

Things had originally been going smoothly. After withdrawing from the rainforest, the attacks and searches of the natives had weakened, and she was even considering escape routes. But the night held a huge surprise for them.

“It’s like the whole forest turned into a ghost region!” Isabel looked alert. The danger here far exceeded her expectations.

“Hehe… play with me!” The forest seemed to change under the purplish-red moonlight, dark red fog filling the area. A large banyan tree twisted abruptly, and numerous vines turned into flexible arms that grabbed at Isabel. A baby’s face appeared on the trunk.

“Even my dragon aura is useless? What the hell is this?” The crimson Red Dragon Sword exploded with burning qi. The conical flames from Dragon’s Breath were launched unceasingly, causing the giant hands that formed webs to be ignited and fall off. This finally allowed Isabel to clear off an area to move into.

“Hehe… It doesn’t hurt at all!” The large banyan tree had pulled itself out of the soil, the many roots turned into countless tendrils. Dark red fog lingered, and the vines that had been cut off and burnt regrew.

“I won’t be able to hold on at this rate…” Glancing at the other side, where her subordinates were heavily injured, Isabel could not help but force a smile.

……

Many natives were gathered outside the rainforest, looking solemn. At their centre was a tremendous altar.

Twisted and evil runes, dark red in colour, were present around the altar. Blood plasma was smeared on it, and the droplets of blood that rolled downwards along the cracks of the stone made it look exceedingly terrifying.

Many of the natives now wore fancy feathers and hide. They kept chanting and praying to the altar. On the altar was the face of a young female native who seemed pure and holy. However, her eyes had lost all signs of life, and there was a large wound on her wrist.

Evidently, an extremely evil sacrifice was being done here, and the target was no known god, devil or demon.

The chief looked like a worthless person in imposing clothing to Special Envoy Agikikro. He glanced at the man and suddenly asked, “I never thought the enemy would enter this forest, that’s a great help for us. I wonder if this will affect us from getting our offerings?”

“Please do not worry! Our ancestors have carried out the sacrifice numerous times. There won’t be errors…” The native head could do as he pleased in his tribe, but he did not dare show any sign of negligence to the envoy of the empire. Droplets of sweat even appeared on his forehead.

“I’ve even invited our tribe’s great priest for the sake of success. With a group of powerful followers of another religion being the sacrifices, the effects will be much better than before. The number of offerings might even be several times more than usual!”

The native head had a flattering smile in his eyes, “When the time comes, I can gift you a few extra!”

“Thank you very much then!” At the thought of the miraculous effects of the product, Agigikro immediately revealed a smile.

Meanwhile, however, scorn flashed in his mind, ‘These darned swines who only roll around in the mud all day! If not for the offerings only appearing here and needing to be extracted with specific talents found in their tribe, the empire would long since have occupied this place!’

“It’s beginning!” The head called out. He naturally had no idea about how the envoy of the empire was scorning them.

“Hm?” Agigikro focused on the altar.

A layer of murky dark red fog shrouded the top of the forest, breaking through some boundary with the deaths of the pirates. It began to extend towards the altar, causing the chief to look delighted as the chants increased in volume.

Dark red fog continued to spread, like a huge beast that had opened its ferocious mouth. A lot of it gathered to form a large eight-clawed spider.

“Leave this place quickly!” The great priest was the first to run upon seeing this fog spider, fast and nimble. The other priests did the same.

“Ah…” “Save– …”

A few native guards that ran a little too slowly were swallowed by the fog. Before they could even complete a sentence, they collapsed and died. Their bodies withered in an instant as if they had lost all life energy.

The fog spider grew more vivid after swallowing all this life. It came to the altar, its terrifying, ferocious, and ugly mouth making contact with the girl.

*Ka-chak! Ka-chak!* With the fog spider’s work, the young native girl’s body made a few strange movements, like a puppet controlled with strings.

Upon noticing this, the great priest halted and that focused his attention on the altar unblinkingly, “Alright. The mighty Balulukulu has already taken in enough lives. It will no longer be dangerous.”

The purplish-red moon was at its most dazzling, practically a little sun. The fog spider seemed to have met its goal, and it dove into the orifices of the native girl.

*Gulu! Gulu!* The girl’s flat and smooth stomach strangely began to expand, and numerous warts began to move, as if a colony of mice was living under her skin.

“It’s a success!” The great priest cheered, and brought the other priests to the side of the altar. They flipped the girl over to reveal her stomach. She looked like a woman who was ten months pregnant, with a dark red tattoo in the shape of a spider on her fair back. It was like a living image, and very vivid.

“The grace of Balulukulu!” The great priest looked solemn as he took an obsidian knife from an apprentice and began some chants. After cutting his own forehead and thumb and smearing a few markings with blood, he placed the black blade at the swollen stomach of the girl. There was a cold glint in his eyes as blood spurted everywhere.

“Is this the sacrificial ceremony here? As heard from rumours, it’s very unusual!” After seeing something so bloody, Agigikro could still converse with the head next to him at ease.

“Hehe… this is the best method that my ancestors found after thousands of tries!” The head now had a prideful expression on his face, “Well then, envoy! Please accept my gift!”

With the chief’s nod, a priest took a golden circular plate and brought it over. On it were a few blood-red crystals the size of chicken eggs, still stained with blood and pus on the surface.

“Balulukulu’s crystals!” Agigikro’s eyes were fixed on the item on the plate, and he looked intoxicated.

This crystal was a specialty of the natives, only found on this island. If someone strong swallowed this, they would gain extraordinary strength provided they survived the aftereffects.

That was not all. The higher classes in the native empire had even found that burning these crystals produced a unique gas. It would give rise to an incomparable ecstasy, and was a luxurious item that the higher class enjoyed. It was extremely expensive.

“Being able to obtain this on this trip makes it worth it!” Agigikro looked impatient and nodded to a warrior to take the golden plate.

At this moment, however, an abrupt voice interrupted them.

“This really is good stuff. Can I take a look?” It was as if an invisible force pulled at things in the air. The blood-red crystals flew from the golden plate, entering the hands of a noble youth.

“Hm? Who is it? Take him down!” Having had such an important item stolen, Agigikro roared hysterically. Immediately after, many native warriors pounced forward.

Chapter 945: Nightmare Island

As a special envoy from the native kingdom, Agigikro had also brought a batch elite fighters with him.

This included the Forest Hunters and Amazon Warriors. They were the ones who had attacked and held Isabel as well as her underlings back, and forced them into the dangerous forest.

Now, however, a youth had suddenly broken through all these people’s defences and arrived at the core circle. He was even threatening the safety of the two leaders here, so how could they not be furious and terrified?

Along with Agigikro’s enraged yell, countless Forest Hunters brandished the lances in their hands and, alongside the Amazon Warriors with strange tattoos on their bodies, immediately surrounded Leylin . The sharp weapons even formed a storm that aimed to tear Leylin to shreds.

However, Leylin’s expression was rather interesting. He cared little for these enemies and instead stared unblinkingly at the crystal in his hands, as if it was the only thing that mattered.

“When I got onto the island, I already had a feeling that something was off. My instincts shouldn’t be wrong. This power…” Leylin’s eyes glinted with wisdom.

“Kill him!” At this moment, numerous natives roared as they pounced forward.

“Die, you weaklings!” Leylin, who was immersed in studying the crystals, waved his hand in annoyance.

Arcane spell— Missile Storm! Explosive Cloudkill!

With immense penetrative force, the arcane missile ruthlessly went through the neck of an Amazon Warrior, and then opened a gaping wound on one Forest Hunter’s chest.

Numerous spells were launched, giving rise to waves and waves of blood being spilt.

After the Cloudkill spell, it converged to form a black tornado that disintegrated all the natives that had fallen, and even caused the corpses to begin corroding.

In the blink of an eye, the native elite fighters surrounding Leylin turned into one corpse after another.

“How is it possible? Is– Is he a death god? Or a devil? Or demon?” Agigikro watched Leylin who was standing within the tornado, muttering in disbelief. He knew the strength of his subordinates very well.

The Amazon Warriors could use their bare hands and kill a Sawtooth Tiger, while the Forest Hunters could wrestle with pythons and alligators in the tropical rainforests. Now, however, they were falling in large numbers like grass being mowed, the speed at which they were going down far exceeding his expectations.

“Go!” “Kill them!” Now, yells were sounding from all directions. The pirates that Leylin had brought along were beginning to make their move.

“Get here!” Leylin pointed, and Agigikro as well as the native head was grabbed by a huge stone hand, pushing them till they were before Leylin.

“Agubaba… Klagila…” At this moment, Leylin saw a native smeared with oil all over his body and feathers stuck on him. Like someone having epilepsy, he began to twitch while facing him.

“A spellcaster? Is this a curse? That’s so weak! This is just too weak…” He pointed lazily, and a ray of light struck the head of the great priest, white and red spilling everywhere.

Seeing the honourable great priest’s body falling headlessly, all the natives completely crumbled. Leylin, who was standing in front of them, was like an enemy that they would never be able to resist. He was as omnipotent as a god in the sky.

The voices of the pirates outside gradually drew closer. In no time, Robin Hood and Ronald arrived before him.

“Boss! There are approximately a few thousand people in this tribe, but those here should be their military. They’ve been defeated…”

Robin Hood reported. Those who had come from Pirates’ Cove could be said to be the best of the best, and there were already a thousand powerful pirates. Compared to the natives, they had an absolute advantage.

“Mm, clean things up here. Try to catch them alive if possible. I have uses for them!” Afterwards, he sized up his own prisoners and the blood-red crystal in his hand. The crystal now emanated dazzling rays that gave rise to a look of intoxication in Leylin’s eyes.

‘My instincts can’t be wrong. This is dreamforce! While there are slight differences, this is power that belongs to Dreamscape!’ From the moment Leylin had gotten onto the island, he had sensed that the native island was enveloped by a layer of strange power. After seeing the dark red fog forest and the natives’ offerings, he could confirm that there was actually dreamforce here— a power that hailed from Dreamscape!

This discovery immediately aroused his interest.

“My– My lord, please forgive me. I am an envoy of the empire. You can’t…” At this moment, Agigikro who was being grabbed by the large hand suddenly spoke in the language of the continent. While he stammered, Leylin could somehow understand him.

Leylin came before Agigikro, and as if seeing hope, he began to speak with as much energy he could muster, “Let me… go. I can… pay the price of ransom…”

“Seems like there really is a native empire!” Leylin’s palm landed on Agigikro’s forehead. “If it were me in the past, I might be very interested in this, but now… I think I’ll do it myself!”

Memory Retrieval! Leylin’s pupils were shrouded in white in that moment, and Agigikro looked to be incomparable pain, as if he was experiencing some torture.

“Grace of the Balulukulu? Using this as anesthesia? What a waste…”

Leylin, who moved his palm away, had a general understanding of what had transpired. Agigikro, who had experienced magic, had now turned into a drooling idiot.

“Envoy of the empire. The skills of the native races, and Nightmare Island…” Leylin arrived before the native head and did the same as before; he immediately found the information he wanted.

“So… that’s what it is?” The general context appeared in front of Leylin in its entirety.

During the dusk of the gods, not only was there the invasion from the Magus World, other powerful beings they had subdued had also entered this area as retinue. Amongst which was a powerful Magus who used dreamforce!

Of course, due to the unique laws of the World of Gods and the gods being unexpectedly stronger, the Magi of laws from the Magus World met with huge losses. Even the Magus who was proficient in dreamforce had fallen here.

It might be just a part of his body or some item he brought with him in battle that fell into the prime material plane. Coincidentally, it fell onto the island, causing such a unique environment here.

The powerful radiation from high-ranked Magi could easily modify an island. When it was the night of a full moon, the forest in the island would usually see strange events. The first to notice this were the native tribes. They could not explain this occurrence at all, and could only pray as if the reason for these happenings was a godly spirit.

After tens of thousands of years of exploration and bloody, unreasonable experiments, they finally had a better understanding of the laws of dreamforce, and attempted to extract and use it for themselves.

Perhaps it was because of the contamination from staying here long-term, but only the natives in the tribe had the ability to extract the dreamforce crystals. Of course, they called this grace from Balulukulu and tried to eat them in order to gain strength.

“They say the ignorant have no fear. So true!” Leylin stared at the crystal in his hand. In his eyes, this ‘refined’ item was still full of many impurities. If swallowed directly, there was a 90% chance of death, while the survivors would obtain some specific ability after incitement from dreamforce. This efficiency was far too low.

“As for the ecstasy from burning the crystals? Dreamforce definitely can give people great mental joy, but that will also lead to contamination. The upper class in the native empire must be in a terrible state…” Leylin shook his head, and began to use the A.I. Chip and scan the crystals.

[Beep! Mission established. Beginning scan…]

A ray of blue light shot out from Leylin’s eyes, not letting off any corner of the crystal.

Soon enough, the A.I. Chip gave an answer.

[Beep! Scan completed. Determined to be Dreamscape Origin Force Crystals. Similarity to that in database at 98.77%. Discovered unknown mutated composition.]

‘Mutual complementation? That’s not a surprise. For the World of Gods, dreamforce is the most adaptable force. Regardless of where a being is, dreamscape can exist as long as they have intelligence. Hence, there’s a very high compatibility…’

Leylin observed the mutated composition chart that the A.I. Chip and sank into deep thought.

If it was some force from the Magus World, the World of Gods would definitely expel it. However, dreamforce’s compatibility was rather high, and after modifying a portion, it could still live on here tenaciously.

‘Just from this, it’s obvious that the Magus who had control over dreamforce had attained great power and was at least rank 8. He had probably even found his own path, and was a peak rank 8 existence that had already fused laws…’

This discovery had Leylin sighing in awe. The ancient times was truly the Magus World’s golden period. Any Magus was incomparably powerful.

There had been the peak rank 8 Distorted Shadow, and now he’d discovered another powerful Magus who grasped dreamforce.

‘Dreamforce… is powerful. If I can tell the rhythm at which it weakens, then it’s much more powerful than the average law… In addition, dreamforce can accommodate time and space, and it’s very good choice!’

After all, in Dreamscape, all time and space could be warped. Using Dreamscape to sustain the power of time and space wouldn’t be dangerous. For Leylin, this was like a pillow being presented to him while he was taking a nap.

‘The powerful Magus who could grasp dreamforce must have known the rhythm at which dreamforce weakened and made use of it. He found a way to evade that…’ Leylin’s eyes twinkled.